Jai Shri Ram Jai Shri Krishna Welcome to Our
YouTube Channel Refine Vedic Astrology
[Music]
Today's session is our Navtara Chakra.
To understand.
See, the Navtara Chakra is a very good method
Which lets you know that your planets
In which constellation are you sitting and that constellation?
How does that constellation look during your lifetime?
Will role-play. Before you begin, you need to
Let me tell you one thing. You may have noticed that Mr.
Krishna has a flute and a crown on him.
The peacock feathers were always there. Actually,
What was that? What did they want to show?
What did you want to teach us? Their lives
Understand about the personality that we have
It is beyond the reach of the common man's intellect.
But still what is written inside the books
From there we get to see that their
The peacock's feather on his head, somewhere he
It used to represent a constellation. He would show it.
It was like Shri Krishna ji was born in Rohini.
It happened inside the constellation. This of the Moon
There was a constellation and a constellation before the moon.
First comes the Sun's constellation Krittika
The constellation that shows that it is a
Adhimitra comes under the category of nakshatra.
Before you understand this Nakshatra Chakra, you can understand this
Understand. As you will be looking at
It will be visible in the photo that Navtara Chakra
How it is made. Then, I will give you
I will explain what we have done to Shri Krishna ji.
What do you mean by just talking about it?
is. See, this is the category of constellations.
It is divided into nine parts. So most
First you will be able to see the birth
Sampat Vipat Keshma Pratyari Sadhak Vadh Maitri
And Adhamtri means very beloved.
Here's when you look at your constellation
What do you do first if you want to?
Where the birth constellation is written is your moon
Write the constellation in which you are
Give. You can also watch from Google 27
Nakshatra Names and Moons
You start it from that constellation.
Collect. In this way, you will have to create three columns
And because every single planet has three
The constellations come. So neither 9 * 3 27 Nakshatra
You have counts. It has a Navtara Chakra
Divided the constellations into nine categories
(a) Yes, Sir. When you start writing from the birth constellation
There will be constellations of planets one after the other
I'll go on writing. Birth has to begin
From the constellation. As you can see this
The constellation of Mars that comes inside the chart
That is the birth constellation. So after Mars
Rahu comes. Jupiter after Rahu
The constellation comes. In this way, you can find nine columns.
Inside you will go on writing the constellation.
So, what we said first thing that is the most loved one.
Kari Krittika Nakshatra of Shri Krishna Ji
About the Sun that comes before Rohini
The nakshatra of Krittika is the Adhimitra for them
It was in the category of Nakshatra and Krittika
The peacock's feather is shown inside the constellation
So it shows that Shri Krishna Ji has
Somewhere they have told us this.
From the personality that if you are your 27th
Do you take the constellation or you  can take your 27th?
They are connected with the constellation in such a way that
If he is with you all the time, then it will be your life.
Very high quality fruit for
It will be. That is, it is inside the Adhimitra constellation.
What you are able to see is whatever your overfriend
There will be a nakshatra i.e. either those 27 nakshatras
The ninth nakshatra will be the 18th nakshatra
It will be. Okay? 9, 18, 27 Which is three?
There are constellations and they will belong to the same planet. all
It will be for the same planet. Your
According to the birth constellation when you write,
Which will be the 9th and 18th and 27th constellations,
It will give very fruitful results.
So, when you move your 27th nakshatra to your
When he begins to cultivate in life, he
Gives very fruitful results. Then it has to be done.
We will now talk about the condition. This is also the point
You'll do that with the person in front of you.
How can you add? Many of it today.
We'll talk about secrets. But most
First you have to understand that you have to understand that you have to
How to create a cycle. Now here we see
What is our birth constellation?
You have to write it first after birth.
Inside the birth constellation. After that, your
Write down all the constellations. this
It will also be found inside the app. If you don't get it
If you do, then you make it this way. Such as
This is the photo. You can make it this way.
Now what will you find that when we are in this situation?
What do we get to see if we add up?
Is it? Now let me tell you this first time.
Let me tell you that this
The new stars who have been named after these stars
What's going on inside? Such as the birth star
This is your birth star. In which you have ...
This is the constellation that you have taken birth in your life.
I will always be connected somewhere.
Somewhere. Then it shows the Sampat star which is the second
Tara Hai Wo shows Sampat Tara. this
Shows the Prosperity of Life
Inside the Prosperity Wealth Family with you
How will it be? Now, if you want, this
You can also add Tara with you. Third
Comes the catastrophe star that shows a little bit
Somewhere in life, see the struggle
It can be found. We can say that it
This star can cause obstecals. so
Such events can happen in life that
When sitting inside this star of this constellation
Planet means to look at it this way.
Suppose you are in a state of affairs planet.
And what do you see that birth star
Which planet's condition is going on?
The introspection is going on. Suppose this chart
According to the people of this person, if we
Let's see that there is a constellation of Mars. Okay?
If there is a planet in their horoscope of Rahu
If you are sitting in a constellation, then for this person
There will be very good results. The Reason Is That
Inside that Naksha Navtara Chakra from the Birth Star
It is the one that shows the Sampad star. at that time
This Dasha or Antardasha is very much for this native.
It will be good. Now let's see if someone's
Planet is sitting in the constellation of Jupiter
Like according to this chart, if this person
No planet inside Jupiter's constellation
If Vishakha shows the star.
Punarvasu or Purva Bhadrapada of this nakshatra
If there is a planet of this person inside, then birth
From the constellation, you will count that such a person
The condition that is going on is a disaster somewhere.
Inside the star constellation
When the constellations come, their dasha dasha is going on.
So, it shows the native that inside it
There can be dangerous events in life. a few
There will be obscures. Ah, you can say that this
It won't work quickly. So you are in a state
You can see your horoscope in this way.
Inside the constellation of the planet.
Sitting you are looking inside this Navtara Chakra
Can this plan be able to do it for me?
Inside the constellation is inside the Vipa Sampat Tara
The plague is inside the star, inside the kesma.
Suppose you have Ah, who is of Keshava Tara.
If the constellations that come inside that planet
If the dasha is going on or the antardasha is going on, then
What you'll find here is what it is.
Happiness shows blessings
Shows. It shows good health.
If the health of a person is fine for a long time
No. Now what does that person see that
I got the state or the difference of that planet.
Which is the constellations of my Keshma Tara.
I am sitting in the Table. That is, in this chart.
If you look at the according, it is like Saturn.
The constellation of Saturn is the Keshma Star.
Let's come in. So if this person is like this.
The condition of the planet which is in the constellation of Saturn
If he is sitting, then his health will be fine.
Because it shows happiness and health.
It is very good that it is a retort star that
Our fifth star is that we show him that
Challenges to see in the life of the native
See you. There will be limited fulfillment. purpose
The desires will be fulfilled but
It will be a limited one. It shows that
Responsibilities are very high on the native
There will be.
But the main thing in this retort of Tara
Somewhere inside you, there is patience
It will raise the level that you need to be patient.
She will teach. What is the meaning of patience.
Then we see if the seeker is a star
Seeker Tara Inside the Nakshatra of Sadhak Tara
If there is any constellation inside it.
The planet is sitting inside those constellations.
It shows the native to have desires.
Success is very important in achieving its goals.
It's more helpful. Like Achievements
It's a star. This seeker is the four stars.
She is the star of achievements. If you want to see this star
The constellations that come inside the planet of this
If the dasha is Antardasha i.e. this star
Listen very carefully inside. This star
If there are as many three constellations as there are
Inside those three nakshatras in your horoscope
If someone is sitting on planet, then this is a very good time.
is. Dasha Antardasha is very good for you.
(a) Calculate the value of Next is Naidana Tara. This is called
It shows that what it is, it shows death.
That is, when there is a dasha of the eighth house.
For example, what is the eighth house?
Shows? A little bit of transformation. bean
That's how it works, too. Bath Tara Yeh
Shows that a little bit of health in you
The problem can be seen. You Can
Here Some Bad News Some Kind of Death Key
You can hear some bad news. Someone's
No death within the family within the relatives.
Heard such news or may have died
Seeing the same suffering comes inside Naidana Tara
It's the seventh star in it.
What would you find if you were born now
You see inside Naidana Tara
Constellations come if the condition of that planet
Are you in the back date or are you in the back date?
You can go and test. If this star
In the constellation that is inside, if anyone
If the planet is sitting, then you saw it somewhere.
Maybe you've heard of someone's death.
Have seen or heard and maybe someone
Heaven for an elder in the family
You are afraid to hear something like this.
(a) The Government of India has issued a notice After this, the eighth star is
The friend shows Tara. If inside it
A planet sits in the constellations that come
And if his condition is going on in the intersection, then you
You will meet people who are very fond of you.
There will be wishers.
What follows is the Adhimitra star, which is
I was the first to tell you sir, sir.
About Krishna's crown and peacock feathers
in. When you are in the constellation of the Adhimitra star
They would have been coming out of the state of the coming planet.
Or constellation whatever is inside that constellation.
If the planet is sitting, then that condition is always for you.
It will be fruitful. That state is never wrong.
Maybe. Even if he is in the eighth house.
Why isn't the planet sitting? The Reason Is That
Tara is sitting inside you who just
It will give fruitful results. The You
What will you see? You have to pay for the eighth house.
Positive results will be seen. This is that.
The thing that shows you the chart from above
You can see it when you see him from Navtara.
If so, the results would have come out in full contrast.
are. Therefore, understanding Navtara and Navtara
It is very important to understand the results
goes. Now you understand that the Navtara Chakra
How do you make it and how do you deal with your condition?
It has to be seen. If anybody's unappointed.
Pratyari or Vadh Tara you call it Naidana Tara
You can say or you can say the slaughter star. her
What do you do if there is a dasha antardasha?
You will find that within a short life, obscals
You will be able to see it. Now in his life.
How do you add? If you're having a bad time.
There must be no cure. Try to Use 27
Nakshatra in your life. i.e. 27th
The nakshatra will be the one which is the most from the birth nakshatra.
The first will be the constellation. If your birth of Mars
If there is a constellation, then the one that comes before that
The constellation of Rahu comes. Oh, sorry before that.
The constellation that comes is the constellation of the moon
arrives. And if you need money for your family.
If you want prosperity inside, then your birth
Move from the nakshatra to the next nakshatra.
If Jupiter's Nakshatra is your birth constellation
That is, if you are born Punarvasu
Vishakha Purva Bhadrapada inside this nakshatra
If it has happened inside the constellation of Jupiter, then
You take the constellation of Saturn in life.
Wealth Prosperity Inside You
I said now it will start to grow.
There was a thing in the thumbnail that we
How can we know that this person is for us?
How is your life partner you want to see?
How is he, your birth constellation?
He made a star accordingly. Your Life
What do you do with your partner? Birth Nakshatra
See the moon of those who are born.
Under which constellation is the life partner's life partner?
is. Now look at that. Those who are constellations
Where does your string come in the Navtara Chakra?
If then the Vipat Pratyari Naidhan Vadh or this
If you are inside the star, then there are a few somewhere
The results will be seen strangely. If he
It is in wealth,  it is in friend, it is in friend.
If he is in a seeker, then it shows that this person
When this partner entered the life of
If Lee had been, his life would have changed.
Because your birth is Ah Nakshatra and that
The birth of the planet in front of you
Nakshatra which is inside the Navtara Chakra when we
If you add the two, then it will give the results.
It does change.
You will find that if Joe is very dear to you
Is it a friend or a friend in your life?
After life changed. Somewhere, he
Friend friendship will not be inside Tara or
The hegemony will be in Tara. That native's
The moon will definitely be inside that constellation.
The constellation which is your friendship or
The lords must have come inside Tara.
So now I will tell you a very good tool.
Don't assume it as an example.
Check on. Even if in the 12th  house
Be the moon. Be in a sense of spending. but
One of those three nakshatras in the 12th  house
Inside the constellation is that which is your perfect star.
Comes in the constellations of. So what do you do?
Will you find? Moon in the 12th House
Money will also come in your account.
Let me tell you more as an example. The one you
Money comes in your account every day, don't you?
Go check it. Either your Dasha Nath Sampath
Tara will be inside of. At that time it transits.
Happened or your moon transiting
The star will be among the constellations. TRAI
Do it and then tell me. Now or go ahead and see.
That the day in your account
Money is credited on that day.
Tara was inside. Most Probably.
I think those three of Sampat Tara
One of the constellations will be inside the constellation
Those who fall inside your Sampath Tara. at that time
Here's how you can see if you have to
You will get more money from this Navtara Chakra
It can be very fruitful that
The person I'm meeting is for me.
How is it. You should know his birth constellation.
should. Inside your Navtara affair you
See if it's even right for me? if
So he is coming inside the Vipat Tara
The birth constellation is coming. i.e. Vipat Tara
The moon of that native inside the constellations of
is. So somewhere you see the obsculous.
You will get that person coming into your life.
After. So there are a lot of things you can do with it.
It's hard to tell you all the things
And all the things.
You also have to learn a little by researching.
So this is how you can see the Navtara Chakra.
There are many other techniques to it.
Different types. You are in this case.
Let's see. See also the intersection of this.
Assume me to be the condition of your Viptara
engaged. At this time inside the Vipatara which
There are three constellations, the condition of yours is
They are inside these constellations. But in that
The introverts that are coming have come to Keshma.
She came to Sampath. So the result changed there too.
Will go. Even though the state of calamity star is going on.
But the inertia that are coming
The planet of the inner state is that constellation.
I am sitting in the house of your Keshma Sampath
If it comes inside the constellation, then the result here
You will change and you can get into it.
You can go very deep. Maine Now
What is the important thing you have to do? You can use this
See 27th Nakshatra Maitri Nakshatra 18th
Nakshatra or the second nakshatra from your birth which
Is his
The Karaka Elements of Ah Nakshatra
Add symbols to your life
Collect. Somehow as much as you add them.
Will go on somewhere in life.
Stability will be seen. The Reason Is
You have seen that 27, 18 , 9th, or 2nd nakshatra.
You have achieved this in life. Somewhere, you have ...
You have added that constellation to you. as
Shri Krishna Ji gave the flute peacock feather to his
Life was always simple. Always your
It was kept together. So that's any circumstance.
They used to cross over. And by the way, theirs
No one can equalize. He is God.
are. But still he
Tried to explain this to us by personality
is. Those who grow up speak less.
He shows that with his personality.
What you have to do. So we need to
You should understand from your personality. Actually,
What did he want us to explain? So from here
It makes sense that you are in that constellation of yours.
Always keep your 27th birthday with you.
Nakshatra is the 18th nakshatra is the ninth
Be it a nakshatra which is your second nakshatra or
Whatever constellations come inside Sampad Tara
Always keep that constellation of yours with you.
Fruitful results in life to see you
(a) The Government of India has decided to meet
We'll talk about another session next time.
I have kept the topic a little short so that you can understand.
I can come in. If there is a question then you can ask.
are. I'll try to answer. then
Take care of yourself for the time being. Jai Shree
Krishna. jai Shree ram