Jai Shri Ram Jai Shri Krishna Welcome to our
YouTube Channel Refined Vedic Astrology
Today's session will be our exclusion.
You have to understand the planets that are your life.
How do they work inside or
How do you decide your life path?
are. Maybe a lot of people  have D1.
There is no ejected planet inside the chart.
You are inside D9 but you can also find it in D10.
You can see. What we see is that
When  an ejected inside the D1 chart
We get a planet, so we present
I'm working on that.
But that's where when  we get inside the D9  chart.
Do you get an ejected planet or the one that
If it is inside the emotion, then the nature of that emotion
We get very good fruits or
He depends on who he is
They meet in the house. In that sense
Fruits are obtained prominently.
But when you see it deeper, you
Go to yourD10 chart and see that
Is there a planet ejected there?
Mine?
Which  went to D10 and got the planet ejected.
is. Kiss in his D1 chart or D9  chart
Kind of the situation? Someone inside the D10 chart
It's also straightforward to be a planet ejected.
What connects you to your deeds is that your
deed
Or the fruit of it in the nature of your deeds
How to get it.
Now let's understand about all the planets.
We'll try that when all the planets are exalted.
If they were, how would they do their job?
So that you can understand that
Okay, like myD1 chart.
Not found. I want to do it in the present.
I haven't got it. But I don't know the inside of D9.
Ejected has found a planet. So okay
is. If my destiny is linked to
If I do this, then it will give me the result.
He will, of course. Inside yourD10 chart you need to
Have you got a planet? So this will give you this understanding.
Even though I am in the present,
I can't get it by doing anything, even if my
Nothing is written in destiny, but
God has definitely sent me this thing
That, son, you should act. After I have done my work,
I will give you the fruits of this house.
I'll give it. You have written this thing down. at that time
So inside all kinds of shud wax when we
Let's look at the planet inside the shed work.
If a planet is ejected, it is D1 or
Which House Lordship will be taken inside D9?
What's going on is that that's ejected inside D1.
Or  is it exalted in D9  or D10  of the chart?
It's exhausted when you go inside. D1 Your
Tells the present. D9 Your Future
explains. &D 10 of your deeds
Destiny tells you that in this life,
What actions will you do? What is in its form?
You will get fruit. Therefore, you should not allow yourself to be excused by someone
Adapting to the appearance of the planet or can be
You are doing that work in his own form.
Yes. Such will be your nature. You get it.
It will come to me when I see it actually.
I am understanding myself that this is my nature.
It comes out as the form of a planet.
So as first of all, let's talk about that
First of all, the general who runs away from today's world
Behind a planet is the planet Venus. When
Venus is exalted in the horoscope or any
If Venus is exalted within the six works, then
What is he trying to tell you?
Venus means that he will give you all kinds of gifts.
Creativity or indulgence
Shows. Like all kinds of luxury
Where does Venus Exalted go?
Inside the pysis sign which is the sign
of Imagination. And Venus is the factor
It's about creativity. That is, creativity.
What did you get the support for? of Imagination.
Such a person is so artistic or his
The tendency is such that he has any kind of tendency
The ability to turn things into positives
Keeps. Imagination power so high
It gets stronger that every creativity
Or I can say that he does any work.
will. He will take it in a creative form.
Everything in his imagination will keep him going
That's how I have to do it.
He will try to make everything beautiful.
The Pises sign is about spirituality
And Venus talks about love here.
In general, what we understand is love.
Factor. Love, love,  love, infatuation
The cause of everything that is the planet is Venus. at that time
Normally, who would such a person fall in love with?
It will be through spirituality. Towards Detachment
Will be. That is, he catches anything
It won't happen. He renounces everything
It will be. So when it comes to love
If one becomes a yogi soul through spirituality, then one becomes a yogi soul.
It is born. That's why Venus is there.
When you go and go to the high, when you fall in love
You get the light of spirituality. i.e.
A person understands in his life that
It's better to leave me, isn't it?
In holding on to something. When a human
This disposition should be created in the mind that detachment
I am getting peace from this.
What would be a good situation? A human being is someone
Holding the thing in more pain and one
Humans are happier except for something.
So this is called a Venus exalted.
Here's when you see Venus Exalted.
So what do you find that such a person is also like?
He is the one who sacrifices whoever he is.
Loves or loves something
Do you love your mother?
If Venus is exalted in the fourth house, then you
Sacraments for their mother
Will be
That is, in whichever house Venus is there
Exalted in your D1, D9, D10, then D10 if
If you are in the fourth house, then you can use your house.
Sacramenting yourself for things
There will be those. Because what did karma get attached to?
He became attached to the things in the house. Ninth House
Inside yourD10 in Suppose Venus
If it is exalted, then what is it about the human being?
It's time to get rid of the illusion.
It's his turn to make me spiritual.
After taking knowledge, my moral ethics is this.
In such a way that I will become my own in my deeds.
I don't want to understand that my
I will get something out of karma or not. The Hire
Knowledge of Spiritualism if you are having
The Exodus Venus in the D N Chart in the
In the D chart in the Ninth House Moral
There is a change in ethics
is. Which is the lowest form of Venus, isn't it?
A sensual
Desire and which is the highest form
There is a universal love. I mean, if one of someone's
If Venus is exalted inside the Week House,  then
He will think about himself first. 6 8 12 Inside
Exalted. First of all, about yourself
Will be thoughtful. But that's what if the center
The triangle is excluded by going inside the emotion.
So such a person has something to give to the universe.
I want to be able to give them something.
You can see here that Venus
When Venus comes inside the sign, he
Destroys your ego. Not here.
The best thing about Venus is that it
Delving the ego I must be one
Word that Venus in Pysis is Like a Love
Beyond Ego. Where love, self-esteem and
He transcends self-respect.
Thankfully, it's high. Where humans are
Doesn't matter what it said to me.
His nature is such that it is his
It is nature, it is my nature,  it is the giver.
Exalted Pisces Venus doesn't even mean
Everything will be good for you.
Sometimes such a person has the most
It has to be sacrificing. Over
Idealization of such a person is done
His idol is the source of all his spiritual practice
In the middle, it means that you are trapping the leg like that.
He wants to do it, but he is not able to do it.
Because it becomes a sacrificial
He's human. Planet exalted then
When the planet is at its highest means its
Can express the highest quality. Like that
He's exalted. He is of that quality of his
He's come in where he finds himself
Can express. So here I am.
I speak love plus devotion
Elevated Venus above lust and devotion
Teaches you to walk on the side. That he
The property has reached where it
Desires are over. Where only
One goes the path of spiritualism or devotion
is. When Venus gets to see the highs
is. Inside any chart you will see if
Then we see if the value here
Let's say Saturn is exalted. Viceversa.
For example, if Venus is a luxury, then Saturn is
There are factors of natural solitude. So here we are
Let's see Saturn which is inside the Libra sign
They are exalted. The Sign of Justice
& Balance. And Saturn is the factor that he is.
The gods of justice have been said to be any
Type of Joe
Deceit is deceit in a human being or in any other person
He is doing something wrong.
The Justice That Is Needed to Fix
It is Shani Dev who comes and does it. So Saturn here
But the ability of a person to come and make a decision
Provide that The Native Will Be Fair
In the Decision. The work that will be done is great.
He will do it by watching. It would have been thoughtful.
is. Saturn like a cold ditch environment.
They like these things. and
Libra is an Ari sign. So here we are.
Let's see a little bit of rationality coming to humans.
Inside. A Structure of Relationship
To, to mature relationships, long
to term commitments. Saturn here
It doesn't make commitment serious. If
Libra sign by balancing something.
Used in conversations or Libra
The sign makes you interact so when you
If you are interacting with someone, then Saturn
Worth sitting here and giving you a commitment
Makes that Anytime You Are Commitment
So you stop at that commitment.
You stay on top of that commitment. Saturn
It makes commitment serious here and together
Makes it contractual, not casual
Actually, you can do anything.
You won't take it casually. That's one for you.
Working as a contract.
Inside this People's and General Relationship
Duty plus fairness plus equality.
According to this, it is not a relationship
Let's see that I have a relationship with me.
You also have to perform your duty inside. Everything to me
If you want to keep fair and you also need equality if
If I respect you, then you
It is also a religion that you give me respect. These
Exolted Venus Key of Ejected Saturn
There is a sign.
Saturn comes here and gives you authority.
The work gives authority. Silent One Strength
gives. Gives long-term planning.
That's why there is no Saturn here.
Slowly grows a little. Why?
Because here there is a person of everything.
Per slightly slow-working
It happens. He has strength inside him.
But he would work slowly and quietly
is. It takes a very long time of planning
is. But that's what's special about the Exalted Saturn.
The thing is that when the ejected Saturn gives you
If you get it, you are unbeatable. Like you
No one can beat that because you
The design was not reached overnight.
You slowly step by step on top of you.
If you are gone, then Saturn is called here
Saturn becomes unbeatable. photo negative
On the side, this is the Saturn's axle
Inside the exolation. Saturn Feel a Fear
Intimacy like that delay in a relationship
He's coming. A calculative behavior
It happens. It is over-judgmental. I'm here.
But let me say one thing: Venus is in Pisis.
Is like a love without boundaries. End
Saturn in Libriz Love With
Responsibilities.
There is a big difference between the two. He is the boundary
Crosses and it crosses boundaries
Knowing how to express something while staying
is. Therefore, when Saturn is exalted, is it not?
Inside the horoscope, the native can control his feelings.
Can't express quickly.
We definitely get to see this thing here
is. Saturn is afraid that
Rejection, failure,  isolation here.
But there is a fear. But when Libra's
Partnerships come under this theme,
Social validation,  equality, Saturn here
But I have to fight my biggest fear.
is. Because Saturn is a solitary dweller
It's a planet. And whatever is the Libra sign, that
Teach you how to deal with all these things
is. So when Saturn comes here and fights
He has to deal with everything here.
Moving out of the comfort zone and into the mastery zone
goes. Because suppose you
Sitting in the comfort zone as long as for you
If there is no opposite situation, you will fight.
How? When that opposite situation Saturn
You don't find it inside this Libra sign.
He gets it. Such a person then you
We'll see everything with the Saturn Exalted one.
He has learned. In his deeds you
Emotions will appear. The karma he will do
He will do it by staying with his emotions. Without
Emotions do not do any deeds
Can. Ever Saturn is exalted in the
Libra Sign. At a very young age, such
One of the human beings we say is that
Responsibility comes. Like Early Age.
Inside Social Rejection,  Responsibilities Mill
Go see trust issues inside Early Age.
To meet you. When you are in Libra
When Saturn happens, then all these things are to be seen.
See you. But overall here on the human side.
He fights everything. And that Saturn
Makes it in very good condition
A person should go on learning everything.
Rador Dean has been giving that he has someone in one night.
Wanting to get the thing. Then we see
That's when the sun is ejected. Now
They were in the west, now they go to the east.
Like the sun exalted in the east direction
It happens. Like Aries Inside Sign
Exalted. Here's the sun.
It is his nature to turn on his light.
Wants to scatter inside every form. that
I want all of that through my light.
Whether people are attracted to me or like me?
One thing I say is that if the Sun signs Leo
If there is a king inside it, then it is inside the aries.
Becomes a warrior. I mean, such a person.
You can't tolerate justice. He
Will fight. He will fight there. At any rate
The feeling that is coming in will become your ego factor
That fight or that emotion will be the factor in you.
That designation that you have authority on
Will try to go through K. Then here
But you see, such a man is the Byborne King.
It happens. De Kant Compromise with
Anything. There is a message here, human being.
On the inner side of the
In general, such a person would not have shown himself like this.
That's who I am. What about the Sun?
The recognition that he shows that I am an atheist
I do. You all revolve around me. at that time
Where you're having a sun ejected in
D1 D9 D10 So at the price you are
You are getting ejected by that feeling, aren't you?
Trying to always show yourself by connecting
Will you say that I exit here?
Actually in
The Sun has a nature that This is Not
An Ego This Is the Center Point of the
Existence Now you say that the sun is here.
Ego is giving. He's not giving away ego. He
Actually, you have a sense of being yourself.
Signification is showing that I'm here.
Hmm. If he's telling himself that I'm
Hmm. It doesn't mean that he is an ego.
Showing. He showed his presence
Look at that, I am. In the solar system
All the planets revolve around the Sun.
That is, the sun does not say that you are mine.
Walk around. Just Because of Their
Attraction. Just Because of Their
Sub-planet due to gravitational force
Let's revolve around them. So ever you're
Having a Sun Sun Exalted It Means
Your aura is such that people are around you.
Let's try to come. And how to sum up.
Such a person gets used to that behavior
There are always people around me. at that time
That's a little bit when you outshine your presence.
Sometimes people try to do that.
They consider that to be ego.
The sun needs to be flurry here.
That he is his
Leadership Qualities Dismissed by Shine
Express.
Like he brought a leadership quality
is. Sun, you have a little risk here.
Gives taking capability. Such a person
It also takes a risk. But
Self-doubt would have been a little less in him
is. Usually, if the Sun goes inside another zodiac sign
So there should be a little bit of like in Libra.
Or if it's in the pis, a little bit of it inside it.
Doubt comes. But when he was inside the Aries.
If so, he has the ability to doubt on himself.
Eliminates it. That's why Les Doubt gives
Isn't that too much doubt? Here
But the sun also shows your father. It
Shows That Your Father Will Also Like A at the
Authoritative post. Somewhere in their
The design should be such that  it is an authoritative post.
But you work. Or inside your life.
We will act as an authority.
Here we will see that the leadership of the natives
Quality has been brought. But as a natural
The soul factor here is a spirit some initiative.
I have come to do it. If you like the sun
Ejected has not been found in D-One, D9 orD10.
Inside any chart, it means the price that
Inside the exaltation, you feel that
We will definitely do something about it.
Because the soul was born on this earth in that zodiac sign
Inside the place where the sun is ejected
Gaya. That is, the sun is here without anything.
It cannot be done without initiation. It Means
You're Born for Something Initiative
Initiative.
Therefore
If the Sun is King in Leo, then in Aries.
It's a warrior. I don't use it shows.
Hmm. I actually do the initiative here.
on. It's not like it's one of those
The one who is a muck is sitting in the cave. Here
The sun is such that they will land in the battlefield.
Dharma knows how to protect me.
How to protect religion? When the Sun
Exhaust is the one who stands for the
Truth Actually. End Justice is not tolerated.
do. Leadership is actually this natural.
Let's take it. That is why the sun is called that it
Natural leadership is of quality.
Because they do anything.
to. Then we see if the moon exalted.
If there is a moon ejected your torus sign.
Inside Taurus is inside. Now here
But one of the very good things to see is that.
Where is the moon exalted?
is. Where the sacraments are added.
Taurus Sign is the Sign of the Sacrament. That you
They are cultured human beings. Who's the love here?
Connected? From your upbringing? From the family,
from wealth. So when the moon exalted
It  doesn't change your emotions quickly
I can. Remember when the moon
Exotic is good here.
Values are given to human beings. Here's him.
Cannot be shaken emotionally quickly.
If we could shake the week moon emotionally
If you are to the Exalted Moon, then you will be as emotionally charged as you are.
Can't shake. Their minds are always
I know that he lives in a steady position.
Yes, what do I have to do? De Need Actually.
Good Food, Pleasure Environment & Stable
Income. Beyond these three things, humans are more.
He doesn't think. If the moon is ejected.
In the price in D10, you will be exalted.
They must act in the form of that emotion
There will be. Because you know that my
Income will be generated from the price because my
The house is very strong because the moon
He is sitting there ejected. Ever
Any planet will see hostility to the moon.
It doesn't. When to sign an Emmy-friendly
If you read, there is no enemy from the moon.
Taxes don't make hostility because of the moon.
If you have made an enemy, then understand that he
So inside your entire solar system
Disturbed your whole life.
The moon is the factor of the mind. What is the state of mind?
Going inside and exalting it?
Inside the stable sign. That is, one of the minds.
Stability is available. Whether it's family
Be it by or  by food,
Whether it's through the environment, or whether it's
Be through finance. That is, the mind is one
Stability comes in. If he
If it is not coming under stability there.
It remains to be seen what the affliction of that moon is.
Is it coming from the house or which planet is it coming from?
Afflict. That house to you or
You have to fix the affliction of that planet.
Will be.
Such a person is not very deeply caring.
It happens. They Show Their Emotions Through Action
Like Cooking Curly. Some of these things
Provided to the person in front of you
Building a Security. It's like that you
A security inside an environment
You are building for the person who wants to do that.
A person should have a protection feeling. He
If you feel protection, then it will affect your emotions.
He will understand. This is your nature when
The moon is exalted. The Rest.
Sudden Changes. This will make any kind of change
I try to resist that I do this.
I won't change. I want this change
I am not. Actually in
There's Ready to Adopt Anything But Very
In the Slow Way that it makes everything slow.
Let's try to adapt a little bit.
Very slow to adopt but reliable once
Settled up. We will adopt very quickly.
When they feel that the settlement has now been done
So it's the moon working well there.
takes. What to see attachment to them?
What you get is the comfort of the attachment.
Connected. And they have a fear of
As well as I don't want someone to be comfortable with.
Don't lose things. One loss remains
In the exoplaneted Venus. There is a fear of loss
Inside the mind. Too much emotional memory
It is strong. It's on the Mercury side
There is no photogenic memory. Their emotions
Remember when and which emotions are awakened.
It happened. I remember. Those emotions are very much in the way
He will wake up when he sees something like that.
will happen. Therefore, a lot of emotional memory
Gives good. This sign is about stability.
So here, the native is not comfortable and family.
Tries to keep it stable in every way
is. And when Venus gives you your Moon
If it is exalted, then this is the throat.
Isn't it quite your heavy look?
is. Quite a bit of a thick end means pin points.
It is seen in the form. Coffee Moon
Throat in exoltion gives you a lot of throat
The one who speaks is that it gets sharp.
We get to see all these things. Then
We see that if your Mars
Exalted. Mars is exalted.
Inside the Capricorn sign. Now here's a lot.
The good thing is that you get to see that like Mars.
He goes there and exalts himself
The enemy is the zodiac sign. By the way, even the enemy's
There is such a zodiac sign that both Saturn and Mars are different.
is. Absolutely.
It should be understood here that a
Such a person has a discipline force. one
Controlled Fire and Strategic Aggression
Such a person has that Mars has a
It's action, it's debt. And Capricorn's
It has a structure, a discipline. DE
Don't Waste Energy.
These people deploy their energy.
Where I work and how to work
Have to be done. There are long-term ambitions.
For him, it's the long-term use of his energy.
Trying to deploy inside the goal
are. They get the success through the competitiveness
Fields is done. A Strong Survival
It is instinct for such a person that
I want to win boys by any means.
Exotic Mars means south direction.
I have Mars. There is a sacrifice. In South Direction
The Capricorn sign comes and
Capricorn means that you have to
You have to stay in discipline. When he disciplined.
When a person learns to live in his own
Enhances Survival That Makes Me Any
You have to fight in the condition. He fights, but he is wrong.
Doesn't fight in place. He uses his energy.
Deploy does a good place. The Only Fight
When Nessery. The Mars that is here
You can't entertain yourself. He
Give things like entertainment at that time.
He doesn't get it because he sees himself all the time.
Engaged in preparation. De Kant
Entertain as much. Ever You Have Mars
Exalted don't wax your moon.
needs to be done. Because if your
He has the heart and the action, but he has the courage to do it.
The moon gives direction. Now
You have Mars exalted there, but the moon.
If it's a week, you won't even know that.
I want my heart or my heart or my own
What direction do you want to put your affect?
It has to be put in. So looking at the moon
It's very important. When your Mars
Exalted. Mars Is Like a
Kinetic Energy Force & Joe
Capricorn isn't that crystalline time.
is. It shows that impulse becomes strategy.
The decision you have to take, you are not there.
Through strategy. Mars here
It won't work like it's impulsive.
Work in the form. He makes a strategy
Inside this sign is how I want to work.
is. That's how I have to work. That
Through strategy, you can get that power of yours.
Let's find it. Power Without Discipline is Like
A self-destruction.
Together's Create Authority.
If there is discipline in any power, then it is
It destroys anything. But
If any force becomes a discipline
If he goes, he reaches an authority
is. That is why such a person is always in the authority
Trying to get one or he
Works by staying on an authoritative post.
If Mars is ejected, you are 100 percent.
You will go into a profession where
You have authority. IAS, IPS, Police,
Army, Doctor, Sir Means Surgery Providers
Let's try to get inside that field
Where I can get an authority. A yogi
He  wakes up at 4:00 a.m. daily. He is also a
It's an ejected Mars. A leader here too
It works for all kinds of pressure.
Absorbs. He's also an exotic.
Planet Mars is what everyone knows.
How do I handle pressure?
The one who knows how to handle pressure, isn't he?
That's an ejected Mars. Mars is
Experienced Means You Have to Align Yourself
Energy in the Right Direction. Others Wise Up
They are spoiling their direction. Your
They are spoiling the energy of Mars. Wrong
By putting it in the direction. Mars when ejected
Yes, I want to make sure one thing that you are your own.
How much time do you give to things like entertainment?
are. You want the person in front of you.
How much time are you giving to them? Mars Jab
If you are exalted, then you should know that
What is your goal and what is your strategy?
It's made for him. Now let's understand as
Jupiter when ejected Jupiter
Exolted your cancer would have been inside the sign.
Is in the sign of the Moon.
Now here's what Jupiter is about to exalt.
It means that this is the highest form of
Jupiter. That is the place where the human being is giving.
The emotion came.
It is as if there is a guru inside a person. The Guru's
When there is a sense of selfless giving,
He becomes a supreme guru. That is, which
The Moon's zodiac sign is the amount of giving. and
This is why gurus come here and are elevated
That is, there is so much love in a human being.
It increases more inside that motherhood
Wisdom begins to look like a human being.
Likes
A mother who gives you a path to spirituality
You can also show that your mother
Showing the way to spirituality is your moral
Ethics can always be kept on the right track.
Jupiter's exodus inside this zodiac sign
To be and to be Saturn inside Pushya Nakshatra
There is a constellation in this nakshatra
Being exotic means you are having
That kind of wisdom that is in giving wisdom
You will never be forbidden. You never
I will think that I am not doing any good to anyone. It
It is a shelter house that allows everyone to
The shelter tries to give. Jupiter
Ejector means you many people like this
We'll see if Jupiter will be ejected
Be in D1 or be inside DD10
That whenever this person goes somewhere, this effort
Will do that I can actually give. I take it
Nope. It happens that people come to them
They heal very quickly. It's a
It shows them. Why would this be happening?
Right? Because of Jupiter here by Joe Wisdom.
The factor is, he went and sat in that zodiac sign that
Where the nurturing nature that shows that
Nurturing nature means a lot if I go deep
If I don't speak, then understand that this is the one
The pure form is where the intuition is
The native becomes such that those who are ethical
What is divisive is divisive and personality.
It gives rise to a natural teacher energy
is.
Like that this person knows that for me.
What's wrong,  what's right for me. in front
What's wrong with a person, what's right
is. That's why these people don't act as advisors.
They do a great job. Don't let such people
You'll see that you like solitude or
Researching, reading, facts
I love to talk. Why?
Because here Wisdom gets a Wo Ora
That's where he wants me to be.
If I want to tell you something,
What is the fact behind it? That fact
This is where Jupiter reveals. We see
There is no form of protection here.
It works in. Like Jupiter of this zodiac sign
The inside is exalted. So whenever you are on
Will there ever be a crisis?
You will find that someone's protection is on me.
There is protection that is protecting me.
It's here. These people expand
Bow your heart to anyone. Like that
I don't like you doing this for me.
are. You do something like that for me. But then
I would have opened all the doors of my heart
I wish I could give you all this. Such as
I said earlier that as a shelter house
Let's work. This is their faith, isn't it?
It would have been more of a caring action.
is. And they're over believers of the spirituality
As well as the religious activities. Ink in
Spirituality increases towards things
is. Increasing spirituality means that it
People try to find the facts.
Jupiter shows here that
They can't have a faith collapse here.
quickly. Regardless of the substance that
No matter what the situation is. Jupiter here
He never lets their faith fall. She Faith
Always remains. Then he wants Faith to do this.
Whether you  are above your mentor or your mentor
Above, or above the father, or the mother
Whether  it's on top of their own moral ethics
Above, even if that faith is above a spirituality.
Yes,  on top of a religion, he never faiths.
Does not break. Regardless of how big
Why shouldn't there be a crisis? Jupiter
Exotic It gives a personality to the native.
to. The R D
Give it a natural behavior or less.
Here I will safe guard you. Jupiter's work
What happens? Safeguarding everyone.
Therefore, it is their nature that
He's getting closer, I can safeguard him.
Somehow. Healing happens by going there
It goes. When this person sits somewhere
The atmosphere starts to heal.
Because, who will come and sit inside that environment now?
Gone?  The exoplaneted Jupiter came and sat down.
Whose gravitational force is such that
He would draw negative energy towards him
is. Hence exolted in Venus
One thing you need to see in Jupiter
will be found. The negativity of all human beings is in itself
It reconciles but sometimes too much
It gets more upset. That's for everybody.
There will be a lot to do, but on his own.
He sits badly. Sometimes if it
Go and sit in the wrong ways.
The feeling of giving inside a person when
Selflessness is born in the sense of selflessness.
Understand that it was born with an ejected Jupiter
It has happened. I mean that person to that Jupiter.
It has brought that when a human being has such a
Nature has originated that I
It doesn't matter if I give it to him.
Whether it is happening or not, but
It is my duty to give it to you if you give it to me.
It becomes something of it means you're having
Exodus Jupiter and here if
Exalted Jupiter if yourD10 chart
If you get a short shot like this
Man will always be a giver in deeds
There will never be a catcher for him.
A nourishment will appear in the deeds. one
Nurturing nature will be visible. These people always
Somewhere you will find that they have respect.
You get more from your elders than from your own. These
These people respect the elders.
Along with this, they get a lot of respect
is. No matter how many people older than you are,
Be it their guru, their parents, whoever
They get a lot of respect from them
is. When the Wisdom Expands in the Purest
Form It Gives Intuition.
When a person's wisdom expands in the first form
It becomes a subconscious to give it a
Gives his mind subconscious power
The mind is aware of when
What will happen? This is where Jupiter is
Protection is said to be that you are under the
Jupiter protection.
This is the special feature of the ejected Jupiter
That he always tries to keep you safe-guarded.
does. You just need to know that he
Is it functional malafic or is it functional malafic?
For me. You must know this.
In Exalted Jupiter, you always have one thing.
You will see that when such a person leaves something,
If something is abandoned, then life changes.
is. When You're Having Ejected
Jupiter. Okay? Whether it's domestic life or home
In a little relationship with the mother
There may be malice. But even how are such people?
Blazed. He was too blessed.
It's human. If Jupiter in the Seventh House
Exalted. It Means After the Marriage
After getting into a relationship, in life
The change will happen after the arrival of the Spice.
D10 is in  the 10th  house inside the chart. Mac
Sure that when you are doing karma, your
Your state of mind while performing karma is exactly a
It must have been different. When you're doing karma
are. Inside a Bhav Inside the Life Chart
If so, look at that feeling. Do I have this feeling?
I feel detached by joining
Or I'd try to give it to you
Hmm. It Means My Jupiter That Exalted
I have aligned with my life.
is. That's where we talk about Mercury
Exalted. Mercury excluded means I
I say this, the human conscience has been awakened.
is. Mercury is called wisdom. Examination of right and wrong
Wisdom tells. And Mercury when ejected
If it happens, it means it is in is on.
Laboratory where to perform this surgery
Ready. Mercury's job is like that, isn't it?
So he likes that I am conflicted.
Can I resolve or should I be in such a situation?
Where I met by working with my own conscience
And by discerning right and wrong.
Sure. Therefore, Mercury exalted in Virgo.
It happens and from here on the seventh aspect
Pisis looks at the sign. Humans in their own
Fulfillment of illusion through conscience
By the awakening of his conscience, he
He chooses the path of spirituality. Where
Going to every kind of human season,
He controls it. When Mercury Exalted
Yes, this is what you will find inside your chart.
That your one intellect is always a
Lives inside the waking state. It Gives
Your Sharp Skills Clear Speech Analytical
Gives depth. This is practical intelligence.
It gives it to you. Mercury is a part of this state.
The point is said. It's Like That Mind Happens
Clean. The level of intelligence is absolutely
It's clean. Decisions made by intellect
That hundred percent will be fine with you.
Will be. Just a malefic on top of that mercury.
The aspect of the planet is not coming. It Means
Your Mercury in the Good State in theD10 Chart
If Mercury in the
Vargo Sign It Means You in Your Work Area
But when you are doing a karma, your karma
Your intellect always does right and wrong.
You will go through the test and your conscience will always be
Will be awake when you are doing karma. D9
Mercury inside the chart if it is exalted
Means You may do something wrong
But in destiny, if you are Mercury
They have brought you destiny
Any wrongdoing done by your discretion
Action, your destiny is right by changing it.
The result will bring the result and the same result
Your conscience will be awakened after the outcome comes
Maybe I could have done it that way.
I have a time to do this.
It has been found that this work should be done anyway.
Can be done when mercury is exalted
is. Dee N fights Drip inside the chart.
A man would have opened his way to salvation.
is. And one thing I would like to say is that when Mercury
If you are exalted, you should always pay attention to this.
You should keep how well you serve
You can do it with your intellects. How much do you
Well, your analytical mindset is that you
Solve anything with a device
Let's take it. If Mercury is good, then Math is very good.
It's good for a human being.
And such a person is much more than an animal.
There is love. If Mercury is good
Because conscience says that they have no
It is not. We have to see them. It
Wisdom will surely tell them this. When the Mercury
It's excluded. It means whenever there is a planet.
If it is getting exhausted, then you should understand it.
Will be. Why is he exalted?
If I speak as an overall summary if
If the sun is exalted, then it will be its own.
Trying to show the presence. Mercury if
If it is getting ejected, then he wants to serve.
It has been. He wants to show service. He
Wanting to show your conscience what's wrong
What's right. If Jupiter is exalted
If you want to show your wisdom, then you want to show your wisdom
are. You can tell people through your wisdom
I want to explain what's wrong, what's wrong.
That's right. The moon is ejected. It means you are
A stable mind. The emotions you have
They are stable. So, what are you doing through that stable?
Look at the House where they can work.
Because where the moon exalted the emotion
You will always be sitting inside in that house.
It will remain as a form of stability. the planet mar
If you are exhausted, then you have to lose your energy.
You have to bring it to the discipline. That
I am sitting in the emotion by connecting with that emotion.
I can do a lot of good things. Saturn
If you are excluded, then you have to get a judgmental one.
Behavior has to be kept in place of what is wrong, what is wrong
Right, it will always be you have to measure and this
You align your karma in the same way as you measure it.
We will get it done.
Hence understanding planetary exoltion
It's just as important as you need to
Let's  see the D1  chart inside the chart. You D9
Let's look at the chart.  Let's see the D10 chart. every
Inside the chart Exit Planet separately
Functions. The way work in D1
That's what you're doing. Her
What will be the outcome results? That D9 will tell.
The D9 also does not have Eggolton. In D10
What will you see if you go? I am working
Hmm. I want his results to suit me.
Will come. Because of the emotion of karma, that is, of karma
Inside the horoscope, you can see that planet of yours.
Brought it inside the exalted state. So
Try to understand your exclusion
Planet that he actually told me in that sense.
What is he trying to say by joining?