Jai Shri Ram Jai Shri Krishna Welcome to Our
YouTube Channel Refined Vedic Astrology
[Music]
See, today's session is our Mars.
To understand the planet that Mars is actually
When we see in Kalpurush's horoscope
Mars is placed in the tenth house i.e. Capricorn.
It was said to be high inside the sign i.e. there
But Mars gets exhausted.
Meaning Mars gets the strength of direction on the tenth house
is. That is, from any house, if Mars is in the tenth house.
If he goes, he sacrifices that feeling.
Now let me try to explain that
How it will work and how to check you
is. First of all, inside your D1 chart.
You will check. Check inside the D-One chart
You will. D9 inside the chart if you check
If you do, then you will know that my
What is destiny? Where in the Mars D9 chart
Your destiny will also be connected from there.
(a) Calculate the value of i.e
According to the end moon chart, you know.
It will work whether your mind is at where or in what house.
Your mind is stronger if you
You will work with your senses. Your mind has that feeling.
If you feel it, then Mars will be there for you.
It will give auspicious results.
So first of all, let's understand what it is.
What's the topic today? What is our session?
Actually, see Mars which is from the Lagna when the tenth
If you go into it, it strengthens your passion. so
When Mars is tenth in any house, it is in that house.
It strengthens the emotion.
This is how this formula is being decoded. For
Exemplar: If Mars is sitting in the ascendant, then
Which emotion will be strengthened? 4th House
Strong will do. Why? Because from the fourth house
When you calculate from the 4th house, Mars
You will see it in the tenth. That's why today's
The session is that in your horoscope you
How can I know my life?
Where should the efforts be put inside?
Where is the power of my horoscope or mine?
In the Ascendant Chart, in my D Chart,
Where is the power of Mars in my Moon chart?
That Mars will strengthen that feeling of mine.
If I work with that feeling, then
at that time
As an example for someone, if Mars is someone's
If you are in the 11th house, then from which house is it 10th?
It went from the second house to the tenth house
That is, if such a person does his work in finance.
If you do, Mars will give it auspicious results there.
If this person does the work of speech, then Mars
It will give auspicious results. If this person belongs to the family
If you do business together, then Mars will be from there.
It will give auspicious results. If this person went into singing
Or if this person also of Venus
Influence comes over that Mars. the planet Venus
If it is in the conjunction, then it goes into the fashion field.
Such a person somewhere aligns his Mars
Accords with your horoscope
Because Mars is very much for the second house.
Strong factor. The Reason Is From Another House
Mars falls in the tenth. That's why we are today.
Talking about the effect of Mars on all of you.
For everyone to have
Mars will be in the horoscope. Rough
In some sense, it must be in the tenth. But today
We will decode the same thing that every expression.
What fruit does Mars give for you? A little short
Videos will be kept due to lack of time.
We will try to do that within fewer words.
Get a little more results. at that time
First of all, when we look at Mars.
Assume your
Let's start in the 11th house or from the ascendant.
Let's start diligently. If in the tenth
If Mars is there, then it is for the native for himself.
It is good that such a person is going to make efforts.
It will be. This person will be so strong that it will never
He will not be afraid of anyone because there is debt. the planet mar
Gives you debt. Mars gives you energy
It's where you can put energy.
In the house from which Mars will go in the tenth house
You will get the energy of Mars.
That is, this person will be a big daring.
It will be crazius. This native sports field
Can go inside. This native is mechanical
Field, Electro Electrical Field,
The engineering line can go inside this line.
is. Where Mars will give it strength.
What else happens to such a person? like this
The person who loves himself the most
It happens. That is, he wants me to be the most.
Take care of yourself first. The Reason Is Mars Ki
The fourth sight comes on the ascendant. When Mars Tenth
Comes in. So such a person should try.
Either he should take the government exam.
Prepare. Someone connected to the government
Perform the task. If Mars is in the tenth then you
You can try to get physical.
Stay in the activities always. The Reason Is Mars
Which is the energy generated inside your body?
He is doing it and he is falling with dedication. at that time
That is, you are yourself.
You will have to make so many efforts that you will be able to reach Mars.
Let's align the energy.
And when Mars is in the tenth and you are diligent.
If you look at it, you will also find that nowhere
Somewhere such a person can be like running
Be very good at things. Sports-like
Be very good in the field. Be such a person
Might be very good at mantra sadhana
Yes. The reason is Mangal somewhere yours
Mantras show spiritual practice. Scorpio Sign
When Kaal is in the eighth house in the horoscope of a man
When he comes, he shows the Mangal Mantra of sadhana.
(a) Yes, Sir. So if such a person does mantra sadhana.
It is inside your actions because the tenth house
That which is there shows karma and from the ascendant
If there is Mars in the tenth, then the karma of such a person
Somewhere connected to mantra sadhana
It should be. Now let's see if Mars is 11th.
If you come to the house, then this tenth from the second house
Moved into Mars. So for such a person
His speech matters a lot. If Mars
If you are not suffering then such a person
The speech will be very bold, very royal.
It will be authoritative. Speak of such a person
They are different in colloquialism. this
The native tries somewhere in his
You can create sources of your wealth through speech.
And this thing shows that such a person can be
Do any business by joining the family or
Join the family business. Finance-like
It's great to go out in the field.
Such a person of the native tries to get me home.
Can I sit down and work or will it try?
That I invest in things like property.
Or in things like investing.
I can invest because Mars from here
The fourth sight that is placed on the second house
are. Aldo Eighth Drishti on the 6th House
Let's put it. So it shows that such a person
There are very few enemies. So the one who gives strength
Mars is giving strength to the second house.
So here the native should keep this in mind
That I should never know my family lineage.
Don't give up. The Reason Is Mars Here
That's why it's strong  in the 11th house.
The native does not leave his family lineage.
He follows the traditional rituals of his family.
He is very loving. Secondly,
Such a person should never be allowed to enter his speech.
Abusive language should not be used.
If the effect of Rahu comes here, it is
If you are in 11th or in the second house?
Somewhere the activities of the native are
Or the habits of the native become like this.
are. There is a little abusive language.
I became fond of cigarettes at a very young age.
is. So you should try not to give the person
Pay great attention to your language
should.
Now see Mars  in the 11th house by the way.
In a way, it gets stronger because
There is force there, but to whom should it be given?
Has been? To the Second House. Second House Is The
House of Your Rites That you can use your
They depend so much on sanskars. You have to
Where to get it? It's as human as your
He will continue to live on the sanskars, somewhere or not.
Somewhere its wealth of sources would have been different.
They will be gone.
Now see if Mars  is in the 12th house, then somewhere?
Nor is it trying to strengthen the third house.
does. So such a person tries to
I can travel as much as I can. like this
The native tries to do commission work.
I can. I go into a job where
Either the work of writing or such a person
Try a little physical activity
I can stay. Gymming, doing yoga,
Meditate. Fourth sight of Mars Third
If it comes to the house, then such a person would have liked it.
I want to appreciate my hard work.
But the most difficult task for such a person
It happens that their hard work is admired.
Not done quickly. On the 3rd House
Mars' fourth sight and the third
Giving Mars.  He sat in the 12th house. at that time
Most for a person who is fruitful
The results come out by making changes.
Because the third house is not the fourth house.
It's the 12th . So this shows that such a person
Change of place, change of habits, all this
You get to see. It also shows that like this.
As much as the native lives in travel or foreign
Does it get settled or in some other state?
If it settles down somewhere, somewhere in life.
The energy of its Mars is aligned.
It begins.
The third house is that of your relatives. third
The feeling is of your neighbors somewhere that you
How do you relate to them? self
How do you treat them? all of it
Somewhere these are the efforts that make us
Shows that Mars is yours when 3rd to 10th.
Went to the 12th house. Are you in the 3rd house?
Able to align the causative elements so well
Mars is the 12th in life.
He is sitting in the house which gives strength to the third house
Is it aligning my energy?
The Reason Is Third Through Your Efforts
The house shows your efforts.
Such a person can be a person who shows valor
You are very strong, you can say that we should do gymming.
Exercising Running Inside Sports
It is possible for them to do yoga.
Whether it is in childhood time, they did this.
All you have done. If the third house is Mars, then your
Fear somewhere in communication skills
Maybe. If Rahu is confused or Ketu
Confluence comes over this Mars. Aldo
These people are very communicative. It's very
There must be more talkers somewhere.
Talk all the time. The most popular online shopping
Spending too much time. So, where is the power for them?
Will you get it? They will receive strength. Doing Karma of Fruit
Don't wish to. If the third house is of might, then
Such a person just has to do might. alone
You have to make effort. The Result Will Handle the
Mars. That's why people don't think too much.
should. When Mars is sitting in the 12th  house
Because the Mars that is giving you the fruit
In a way, the third house is giving results.
Because he is strengthening the third house.
is. From there, he sat down in the tenth. When Mars
If it is in the ascendant, it strengthens the fourth house.
is. That is, the trades of the mother are very high.
You will get to see Strong. Nowhere
Somewhere the mother who is a little aggressive to you
Will see the official post somewhere.
Na kahin it show ki aisi nativ ki jo mother
He will be a bold nature.
Somewhere else it shows that they have said
Neither is the struggle of your whole life.
Nor would they have taken them on themselves. this
Shows when Mars is inside the Ascendant
You should be connected to the fourth house completely.
Nicely. How will you join it? Now either
You get involved in things like real estate or
Then you get involved with nurturing nature. fourth
The emotion shows your nurturing nature. so
The more nurturing nature the native will be.
He can mean everything to give to all of us.
It will be. So here is its Mars 10th house.
It is getting stronger in the ascendant. Nowhere
Somewhere. The fourth house is also of your vehicles.
The fourth house is your real business. fourth
The sentiment is of your route where we are engaged in agriculture.
Farming that you can be
Are you involved in the chemical industry?
You make things of farming. And It Also
Shows that such a person can also happen in Vastu
is. Such a person should always be blessed with his mother.
You have to do it. If it's your mother
Doesn't behave well with or
This is somewhere where such a person sells his property.
If he gets out, then somewhere he will get his
Weaken the Mars which is sitting in the ascendant.
It has been. Mars is here in your fourth house.
Sitting in the tenth from there.
K. So, from the causative element of the fourth house, your
Combine the whole life. 4th House and
What is it? 4th House Your Childhood Memories
is. 4th House of Your Mother and Mother
There are rituals. The fourth house of those things of yours
The assets that are kept at your home. fourth
The sentiment is of construction. 4th House Yours
It's the trains. Meaning thus these things
By connecting with such a person Mars in his life.
Align. Now let's see if Mars
If you come in the second house, that is, here
Mars, which is the strength of your fifth house.
doing. A person who is very much
There is love or infatuation. From his first child
There is a lot and a lot from your education.
It happens. Maybe The Native Will Be
Sometime Egoistic or such a person has his pride
Yes. These people can go into fields like fashion.
are. An Artistic
You can go to the company or do your art.
Can increase too much. Acting,
Fashion, modeling, all these things go into these things
They like it. Fifth House, Another Thing
It is also of . The fifth house is of mantra sadhana.
Which gave me a very good placement of Mars.
It seems. She seems to be in the second house. bus
Mars should not be debilitated here. Or don't set.
Yes.
So when Mars is here, it is not in the second house.
In the native's no, the inclination that occurs
Nor would she turn to his mantra sadhana
is. Yes in No Doubt Child Conceiving
Gives problem. There may have been a miscarriage
First of all, but a lot of mantra sadhana.
It's nice to have a good time here. The Voice of Such a Native
Whatever will happen, it will be very rich to speak. Yes,
It can be an abusive language. No Doubt
Because Mars came in the second house. this
Mars does not have a domain. The second house is
That is the domain of Venus or Mercury. But when
If a planet like Mars comes, then believe it or not.
The slightly malefic planet is Mars. because
There is a forward aggression, the benefit that is in Mars.
It is a planet, it is timeless. Mafic Planet
They are a little aggressive. When the second house
If it comes in then the person is a little abusive.
He becomes a user of the language.
A little bit of grudges with your family
See it. But this Mars is yours.
So much for Mantra Sadhana and your education
Good. So try to educate yourself.
You try things like music.
To join. Listen to the music, chant the mantra
(a) Calculate the value of So it may happen to such a person that
The native is interested in his stock market such as mutual.
The fund would go and invest there
Yes. And the Most Thing for This Native Is
That such a person should never be with his child.
You should not misbehave. Over here
Mars will be less powerful for such a person if
He misbehaved with his child.
is. Because remember the fourth sight of Mars
Whichever house the fourth vision goes to, that house
He doesn't have such love or attachment to her.
It adds that emotion in some way.
He doesn't want to lose that feeling.
Mars starts tying up. Mars when that house
If you start tying the person in front of you.
I think it's doing it wrong to me. this
Keeping me in bounds. So such a person
Even if you are in a love relationship, then somewhere
Don't let your partner do it.
Let's try. Where they have their own
Conflicts with the partner
are. Such a person has many love relationships
You can be those who are broken in the beginning.
So try to do one thing mantra sadhana. The One
And only remedy for that people are there
Possessing the Mars in the Second House. to you
Mantra Sadhana in the Causal Element of the Fifth House
It's very important. Now Mars if third
If it is in the house, it moves from the sixth house to the tenth house
goes. Only service for such a person. so
One thing I can say to the native is that it
The native is so strong. It's from anyone.
Will clash. He enjoys fighting.
is. We can say that. The Reason Is Mars Ki
The fourth aspect is coming in the sixth house and the sixth house
He is also giving strength to the emotion while sitting in the tenth
K. So such a person
It is very strong. Why was it called Mars?
The factor occurs. The factor in the 3rd house was said to be
is. The reason is because it is from the 6th house to the 10th house.
It goes. This sixth house is so strong.
Such a person makes his enemies
It defeats you. And One More Thing Is That
Such a person should do service. Not such a person
He is the one who serves. Maybe The Ah
Native will be those who are not crippled. Physical
There are disabled people to help those people.
Be it. Such a person can be dogs and so on
Feeds to. If Saturn's Aspect
If Rahu is sitting in the 6th house, then it is like this.
Native Dogs or Dog Shelter Cat Shelter like this
Go to the place and get it fed. 6th House Your Diseases
It is a loan. So such a person does not have a little bit of them.
Stays surrounded. Somewhere in the job.
Conflicts are seen. So that's it.
The person tries to go to the job itself.
The reason is that these people are the police army.
It is their dream to become an advocate. judge
It is a dream to become one. Somewhere if
Third House Sixth House Load If in Eighth
If they go away, they can be such people. IAS,
You prepare for IPS because it
Competitive exam very well
You can prepare. Mars them here
Somewhere or the other there is a strong force.
Does that you can do you. You've had the
Capability. The sixth house is your competition.
So not everything is competition for such a person.
Isn't he getting ahead of me?
Isn't it going beyond me? this
They treat everything as a competition.
So try to look at Mars this way.
The sixth house is also that of service. Sixth House Your Mama
It is also of . If there is a Malefic Planet Horoscope
Functional Malefic Planet If Aspect
Not giving to the sixth house to uncle's
They have great love with them. Uncle Inko
a lot
Can we say to help in the profession?
They are. But the sixth house which I am first
I say it from the beginning. This is the feeling if a human being
Take this feeling with you. service
How will you serve? With hands. Because Mars
Sitting in the 3rd house and showing hands
It goes to the Third House. Such a person as much as his
He will serve his mother with his hands.
(a) Calculate the value of Serve your father. as much a
We will serve them and go out as much as we can.
Helping people with physical disabilities
Will always be good for you.
It will be beneficial.
Now let's see if Mars comes in the fourth house.
It strengthens the seventh house. therefore
People used to say that this is the Manglik Dosha.
Generates. Hence what was called.
Because it is strengthening the seventh house.
is. Watch Now
For example, there is a man and his wife.
If she fights with him a lot, she won't be able to stay.
Somewhere or the other if the person in front of you
If Mars is weak, it will stay. if
If it is not weak, then there will be a divorce somewhere.
Things like that are seen. The Reason Is
Why was Mars in the 4th house said that it
Creates conflicts within marriage
is. Because it is very much the seventh house.
Strong is doing. It is in the seventh house.
It is making you so strong that your
The partner who will be there to fight all the time
Will be ready. From things like that
It will be surrounded. Maybe that's too much.
Be strong that he gives you such an overpossessive nature.
Yes, hers. He starts tying you down and you
That restriction starts stinging somewhere.
Therefore, Mars in the fourth house is said to be
This Family, This Domestic Piece A Little
It finishes. And here in the fourth house.
Shown somewhere anyway
Inside the 4th house in the horoscope of Kaal Purush
Mars becomes debilitated inside Cancer
is. So here's one of the forces on Mars.
The force then decreases that the force of the direction
Mars doesn't get it here. So when Mars
If you don't get the force of direction, then Mars here.
Becomes weak or goes into anxiety
Tue. Here, it is all the things of the seventh house.
It makes you want to destroy it.
Destroy somewhere in the native business
Tries to go. Still in business
Sometimes he eats the loss. But if he is the fourth
Doing business by connecting with the factor of emotion
If you take the seventh house somewhere.
It becomes strong. Here the native has to
You should try to help your partner.
They can't get along with you. Most of it
Good region, can I say this or the most?
Good remedy I can say that such people
Don't travel with your partner.
should. Get in the car. And going over there.
About your conflicts
Talk. One thing is for sure that when it ever
You will also go in the car with your partner.
They will never fight. If there is a fight
It will always be at home. So end that thing.
They don't have to travel
should. End
Try that if you want to take the property
If so, take it in your mother's name. so
If the person has property in his mother's name
If you take it somewhere in the seventh house, then you take it somewhere in the seventh house.
Which is strengthening Mars seventh house
That mother will make the fourth house strong
Somewhere in the fourth house, which is Mars pain.
There's a force on there somewhere.
Now let's see if you are in the fourth house
If Mars is placed in the 5th house, it is placed in the 8th house.
It gives strength to the emotion. Such a person somewhere
Nor will you find much in mantra sadhana.
Passes. They mean it, don't they?
A person is such a wonderful person that he
Somewhere the native Mars from the fourth aspect which
Looking at the eighth house which is of the fifth house
Such a person is happy with the happiness of his children.
It is very dear. Such a person
Such a person is very fond of doing mantra sadhana.
It happens. You will find such a person somewhere
Their transformation within education
is. So, this person is as much as he is inside his life.
Such a person does not have a transformation anywhere.
Somewhere in your life, you will do sinful deeds.
The accounts keep coming out somewhere.
That is, his virtuous deeds should be awakened.
Let's do. The eighth house of your transfection
is. The eighth house is of your inlaws. eighth 8th
Emotion is the inheritance for which you have
You haven't made any effort. So the mind of such a person
It happens that he feels like taking shortcuts.
Should I make a little money through or
Such a person may be very good
A person who composes music and
It can come in the stock market. Mutule
Moving to the Fund Investment Financial
Becoming an advisor in things like research
Can work very well. Astrology Lots
Can you understand well or astrology very much?
He can teach well. What is the fifth house?
It's about your education. Your Fifth House
It is a consultation. The fifth house of yours
You have to give the education that you give
Childhood takes in time. So the fifth house
When Mars is in the eighth house, it is strong in the eighth house.
One of the best effects of doing this is contemplation.
(a) Calculate the value of The more research you will do to yourself.
The more research you do by isolating
May your intellect be as strong as Mangalay.
keep. Because the fifth house is also of the intellect
It happens. Now let's see if Mars is in the 6th house.
If you come to the point where the factor is called, then it
Provides strength to the Ninth House. i.e
Father who must be a little daring
There will be. The father will be so robbed that perhaps the one who
The native's horoscope will be from the father even today
You are afraid. It means that today there is a sense of saying that father
The native is very valuable.
He would have given great respect to his father
is. Of a person who lives first and foremost
That he tries to do that inside the Society
Nothing must go wrong. Her Morale
Ethics is so awake that he is moral.
Ethics lead to quarrels anywhere.
For such a person, it should be kept in mind that
Which his father and guru advised him
Never leave that advice.
should. That is, the person in front of you.
You also have to avoid the efforts,
You have to motivate. Your father and your mentor
You also have to always keep your advice on your head. Sixth
When Mars comes in the house, then from the fourth point of view
Looks at the ninth house. It shows that
The native is very much from his father and from his guru.
He will be loving. He will be His devotee.
Such a person runs towards higher education.
It happens. They have to travel long
Sounds great. The most important of such a person is
What I can say is the main important thing.
That this person never
You don't have to do that work for yourself.
I'll regret it later. See which is the sixth house
Nor did Mars sit there and go to the Ninth House.
If you look at it visually, then try such a person.
He should always follow his father's guru.
Serve and do as much as you can in your morals.
Stick to ethics. Yes, there will come a time
That your moral ethics are somewhere or the other.
I will try to give you very good results.
Try to connect with the 6th house so much
Go to Your Ninth House Blessings Too
Do the work. They are blissful people. Such natives
Above the blessings of the Gurus and the Father always
remains. Ninth House Your Blessings
What you did in your previous life?
were. In your past life, you have somewhere or the other.
You must have served so much that Mars will give you the sixth house.
I found it here in your ninth house.
Blessings are strengthening the emotion. at that time
Always stick to your moral ethics.
Never give up on your respect for what you do.
Respect elders
Their respect should never be abandoned.
When Mars comes in the seventh house to such a person
So, it strengthens the tenth house. It Shows
That the husband of such a person will have a mind
It will be bigger. You can say that
Will there be overpassivity or whatever you feel like?
That would be too much overpassiveness for you.
Regarding the spouse partner. S to Jataka K
One of the best results for the native is that
If you want to strengthen the tenth house, then
What is the tenth house? It's your father's money,
It's your father's family, your government job.
What is it,  it belongs to your Government, it is under the Government?
There is no work. Get involved with the things that
Represents the government somewhere.
Yes. So this Mars will become strong here.
The people who will come to you like woodworkers work
He works as a carpenter, as a mechanical.
Work, electrical work done,
They have their own shops, they take contracts. as
Electrical work is done, carpenter's work is done
Gone, has a shop of its own, an electrical shop
It's done, it's an electronics shop.
Someone should take a contract by joining the government sector.
I took all of this stuff. So this person does that work.
You can do very well. From there, their
It is the field of karma that will become strong here.
On.
But they should take care of their speech
Because Mars is second in the eighth aspect.
If you look at the emotion, then somewhere like this.
Spend money on the person in front of you
The doer gets too much. now
When Mars comes in the eighth house, nowhere
Somewhere it gives you too much strength in the 11th  house.
provides. Because  from the 11th house, you
You will find that Mars has gone in the tenth. Such a person
Those who are older siblings are very
This is how we take strong influence
Above the native. Such a person has an appetite
That can be said to go into anxiety.
If he were to use things like an electronic.
Don't be surrounded. Gaming, Social Activities
Be persistent. They have a lot of social friends.
are. Not a lot of different types here.
There will be friends. Friends are all for such a person
There are some. Active on social sites
Stay. These people are the ones who sit alone
are. You may be sitting alone at home, but
When you go outside, you will have all kinds of
Let's make friends. Mars for such a person
It will be such that this person will not be strengthened.
If the engineering goes in line or it
The native is somewhere like astrology,
It's research,  it's the work of the occult,  it's like mining.
The work is done. If you want to find the eighth house, then
Mining is like a computer.
Decoding done, gaming platform
Gone, PlayStation done. Because Mars
He is happy to be here because he has to
I don't enjoy doing this thing there.
Like what happens when we play games
My blood pressure is very fast.
The end goes down when we're in gaming
If Mars likes it, then when the eighth
If there is Mars in the house, then the person should try.
Either go abroad and settle down.
Because the eighth house is also of your foreign
Shows or incorporates these electronics to the native
One should do some work by joining the equipment
Or computer decoding engineering.
The ring should go in line.  In the 12th House
You see when Mars is in the Ninth House
So  the 12th house provides strength. so
One thing to keep in mind for the native
should. Charitable Nature Is Most For
Dec. Ninth House One is already your moral.
And there are ethics. Okay? And  the 12th house which
It's about the thing you should ever catch up.
No. Such a person may be a foreigner
I want to go very much. He tried
Performs your morals and ethics according to time
To change. In such a person, you will find it
You're going to be a great traveler.
It will be. He will be a very good charity.
Or should you do a very good charity?
to. This person works with many NGOs.
will. He can be a very good yoga guru.
A field like a hospital teaching meditation
(a) Calculate the value of the product. You are a very good surgeon
You can. It's like Mars in the Sixth House.
So there are very good surgeons. Such Ninth
Be it Mars in the house or in the third house?
If you have Mars, you become very good surgeons. this
The native may go to a foreign land and go to a lot of lands.
Do a good job. Or this person somewhere or the other.
Someone can work by joining foreign land.
We have to do the work of import and export. Which
For this, they have to travel a lot
Yes. That is, the strength that gives strength to the 12th  house.
It is happening to you sitting from the ninth house.
Keep in mind that  the 12th house is not that
The root factor has become for this Mars i.e.
The fruit that Mars is giving to Mars at this time
You should prominently find that inside the horoscope.
He will give it in the 12th  house because he
It is making the 12th house very strong.
Moved from 12th  to 10th of the ninth house
Within  the 12th house and also the 12th house of these things
The feeling of loss is of such a person whenever something
If he turns around, then he has a lot more in return.
I will always get what I understand.
Such a person should try to make sure that he is a part of his life.
Transformation should continue inside.
It should be abandoned. Until it leaves
Until then, it won't get anything new. So much as
You will get as much as you leave. And try it
Always a reverence with your father and mentors
Maintain a disposition of respect. 12th
You also have a sense of one more thing. 12th House
Your mother's morals and ethics that
It can make changes in your life.
Because it falls from fourth to ninth. therefore
Try your strong 12th  house
Let's go let nature be yours.
One should live like a yogi and a fakir.
When the 12th house comes, it is that of the yogi and the fakir.
You should be like that. Don't think that your
What the subconscious mind is thinking. What
Are you imagining? Don't think about that. Tue when 11th
If you are in the ninth house, then from the fourth point of view 12th
When you look at the emotion, there is a lot of imagination.
It becomes the doer. The native to go abroad
He is tempted to do so. Tries the native
That I either go into the medical field.
By joining a field like Hospital NGO Inn
I can work.
So try to make your Mars all like this.
To understand in 12 houses who is Mars
Giving a lot of strength to the sentiment
is. Very short video that everyone made
You can understand it in two minutes. I have many points.
Maybe I haven't been able to tell how to decode.
Because there is a shortage of time somewhere today.
I have. Next which Nakshatra Series I start
I'm going to do it. Work is going on on that too.
is. We'll try to talk about it all.
You can explain. But you can read this video like this.
Look. Mars is in whichever house it is in the tenth house.
Grab hold of the emotion. Complete surgery of that emotion
Do what comes in this house. this
What fruit will I get from the house? Just Ascendant
Let's do the surgery. If Mars comes in Dasha
It has been in your life that you have this feeling.
What is the thing that you can do here?
You can add on to the routine of life and
That Mars of yours will become strong there. and
Always remember the mantra for Mars
Always do. The third house is Parikrama
Do spiritual practice by doing it. The fourth house is at home
Sit down and meditate. If it is the fifth house, then
Cultivate through music. 6th House
If you are going to serve somewhere, then that
The mantra is sadhana. So, by worshipping such a Mars.
Add to the form. Ahead on to another session
We'll talk. Until then, thank you. conquest
Shri Krishna. Jai Shri Ram.