Jai Shri Ram Jai Shri Krishna Welcome to Our
YouTube Channel Refined Vedic Astrology
[Music]
Today's session is our Day Nine.
To understand the 10th Lord of the Chart. by this
Earlier also we made a video of the 10th  Lord
is. In which it is stated that the 10th Lord if
Sitting inside a house or the joke he is
What will be the consequences of being inside the sign?
If you haven't seen that video, it's the first
You can go and see. This video
You will understand easily.
What we're going to talk about today is our
What is the price of the 10th  lord inside the D9 chart?
Sitting inside is in the D9 chart itself. So today Joe
We'll talk about that inside the Day Nine chart.
In which we also call the Navmash chart.
Where is the 10th Lord sitting?
Example if you are a torus ascendant
Passion is your torus ascendant and yours
The Navmash that has been made somewhere if
If the Psisis sign is made of then what do you here?
Let's see the 10th inside the Pisis sign.
Lord is Jupiter Navmash
Inside the Navmash, you have done 10th 10th.
Lord means Jupiter according to this horoscope
Look at where it is sitting in the Navmash chart.
So this is how you got your 10th Lord
Look inside the De Nine chart. now
What does the Navmash chart actually do?
The Navmash chart is our destiny.
Actually, what do you have to do?
Will you get it? That is destiny. That Means Marriage
According to the chart, you choose a profession.
You can do it or you can do something. self
They perform actions. What is 10th  House? Our
It shows karma. If we dig it a little deeper.
See De Nine inside the Naumash chart
When we go to the chart, we  are 10th there.
Let's look at the Lord. In what sense is that?
De Nine is sitting inside the chart. From there
We realize that this is our destiny.
is. If we join this work or we can do this.
If we join the house, then we can say from there.
It is that the life of the native is somewhere or the other.
She will align with her deeds. that
It will be connected with your actions. So D9
Understanding the 10th  Lord of the Chart Too Much
It is important when we are aware of someone's actions.
Let's understand about it. That's that destiny
Your that if the native is most of the successful.
Person somewhere he charts his De Nine
The 10th  lord inside and the one who
In the house or inside the joke sign
same
From the causative element of the emotion and the same zodiac sign
By joining, he chooses his profession
And from there he is able to become successful.
So now I would like to say that you can do your day.
Look at the 10th  Lord of the Nine Chart  that he
What are the prices within the Day Nine chart?
It's sitting inside. So what we will all talk about
We will talk about the 12 houses. therefore
This topic is going to be very important.
If the native manages his karma somewhere
Na Kahin S Par The Nomash Chart Toh Us Jataka
Obstacles are lost in life.
are. That is, the obscures will come. This is no
Doubt that it should be said that there are no obscures
Come. But those obstacles will come to you.
Opportunities will also be given together. go to sleep
The prayer chart shows your opportunities.
shows. Aldo which is a Nomash chart by the way.
Which works properly which I think
After the 25 years of age, the prominent form
Starts working or after marriage
We can say that we are the 10th Lord of the Navmash Chart.
When all  are in the 12 houses, what fruit do you give?
Are they?
Now look at the 10th Lord Day Nine chart
If you go inside the first house,
It is in the Navmash chart itself, so see it from here.
The person who gets this karma
It will be a karma for the native.
They will be loved by all. That is, it is called
That this person will be work oriented. It's your
Karma is always up there somewhere.
Will try to keep the level where this
The person can get fame name recognition.
It shows that inside this native.
It is the ability to perform any action.
Maybe. That is, we can call it that it
The native somewhere chooses that profession
Will try to find the one in which it is mastered.
Done. What will happen otherwise? If it's someone
He also chooses the profession and that
Inside the profession of this native, he is well versed in the profession.
If not, then it is inside that profession.
Starts to see a downfall. We are here
You can say The Native Will Be Very Hard
Worker and such a person
He is such a hard worker that he spends a lot of time.
Don't enjoy your domestic grind well
Finds because it went into the fourth from its
(a) Yes, Sir. When we do this is a theory. When we
Let's look at someone's chart, if we
The emotion of any emotion has to be analyzed,
So, we make it a passion. So from there
It is known that this person is from this house.
What kind of linkage will happen? If you're looking for your D Nine
If you make the chart ascendant. this
According to the methodology, what you will see is that 10th
The Lord came to the Fourth House.
That is, from there you will see the Ascendant Lord
Came to the Forth. When you ascend the 10th  Lord
Let's make it. So inside the life of this person
What could happen? Either this person from home
Will it work for the house or will it work for the house?
It will do. It shows us that this
The 10th Lord is somewhere in the center.
And whenever there is no Planet Center
When he goes in, he becomes a sacrificer. that
We can say that by coming to the center, that person
The one or that planet gets strength and that
Equates Native gets so much strength
Will be over confidence. Because when someone
The planet moves to the fourth house from itself
So the house he is the master of, that is, his
Linkage is very high on your psyche, your mind.
It gets too much. Your profession at all times
Keep thinking about it. If your Malefic
It is inside the aspect is with Rahu. Saturn
If the aspect is coming, then a little delay in the
Profession will be found within success. If Rahu
What will you see if it is in?
Somewhere Moving an Overthinking
A fear of the profession
Sa Rahna Unknown Fear Rahna Agar Nauvash Chart
With the 10th Lord in If in your Ascendant
If Rahu is sitting, then it shows that this person
very much
It can be powerful. Like, why so? Added to impart the meaning of ‘giver’ as  giver of water
Reason Is 10th House Shows Our Status
is. It shows our society. Such natives
To chase status in society
There are also many things that are done
That our society is not honored.
are. That is, he can also choose such a profession.
What we can say
It can also be for the welfare of the people.
You can also see your benefit from well-being.
Mother's advice is always very much for this person.
It will be fruitful. Now if it is inside the Ascendant
10th Lord the Native in the Namaz Chart
Can Have the Work in the Medical Field Also
Where with the brain we can say
He can add his likes to the profession
Psychology is done if the sixth together
Lord is also the Navamash or the Eighth Lord is also the Ascendant.
If you are sitting inside, then can you be very good?
You can say that there can be a surgeon who is in the mind.
Functions related to the brain
You do this, these people are very good healers.
Let's heal someone very quickly.
to. Aldo, this is the placement, this profession
Because there is a very good placement for
The 10th Lord has sat inside the Lagna
In the chart itself. So here the native should always
It should be kept in mind that the more he is in front of him.
He will think of the good of the person because when
If the planet goes to the fourth by itself, then
It shows that he went for the masses
is. You do as much good as you can about the society.
Do you think of your profession somewhere?
Opportunities will continue to be available inside. 10th
Lord has come into the ascendant. One more thing
Be careful. It shows that your father
Is a very artistic personality. End
The father's source of wealth will also be somewhere.
Nowhere is it connected to something where
But things like production units were installed
are. Or Your Father Can Be in the Stock
Market. For the reason is 10th , what is yours
Showing father's wealth and father's family
is. And where did it go? Ninth to fifth i.e.
The Ascendant has come in. So Father Is Very
Good in the Singing. If Venus or Mercury
It's okay if you have a planet like Mars. Mars
If so, say a little bit about the nature of the father.
We can be angry and
Father Can Be at the Authoritative Post the Reason
If it is Mars, then it is the eighth house of the father.
(a) The following is the case with the Registrar of That is, from the ninth to the eighth.
It is the fourth house and if Mars is the ascendant.
If I am  the 10th Lord, then this father is a
It also shows up on the authoritative post. So now
Let's talk when the ninth ah when the 10th Lord
Inside the second house, inside the Namas chart
So it shows that it's a triangle from its
Went in. That is, it is inside the same element.
The element of which is the 10th Lord. because
Whatever planets were inside the triangle
There are zodiac signs inside the triangle,
They are of the same element. If then it
If there is the element of fire, that is,  the 10th Lord.
If the fire element belongs to the zodiac, then it is the fire element.
It's been in. He is the master of the water element.
So that water element has gone inside the zodiac sign.
In the Second House. If the air is of the element, then the air is
It must have gone inside the element.
So here's what we should keep in mind when
A planet goes into a triangle by itself
So he doesn't have the whole triangle anywhere.
Somewhere it gives strength. Even in his trine
Trying to give strength to the planets that will come
does. Native Can Choose the Work in Which
Speech is play a variant role. Education is
Also Pledge A Variant Role Important
Roll. The reason is he is inside his fifth
(a) Yes, Sir. Reason for going inside Pancham from yourself
The native also made those hobbies his profession.
Maybe. Like who is inside the fifth house.
Things come, acting, dancing
Gone, singing, modeling done, or
The fifth house represents a production. if
You see in the horoscope of Kaal Purush.
The fifth house is production because there is
It is shown to the child that the child
The origin is shown. So such a person
It may be a production unit of its own.
It can be installed. Setting up a small production unit
It can be the work of toys on it. Toys
You are created. And It Shows One Thing Also
That After the First Child Will Have the Native
An upliftment in their profession. First
After a child, a person in the profession
Upliftment is seen. In Pancham
Gone is one thing that shows another thing.
Fathers may be involved in the job
If the planet is combust or the planet is retro
So there is malice in the relationship with the father
shows. Now look at a crux here.
That the lord of the father's wealth house is the Navamash chart
Sit inside your house of wealth.
Gone. That is, it may be that you
Financially support can be your father and
It is also that the father is someone
You are surrounded by such a habit because of which
Your relationship with your father has deteriorated. thereof
The reason is that the second emotion is that of the father.
For the 10th Lord, he came into your wealth house.
And for the father goes from the ninth to the sixth.
is. The sixth house which is our Shad Ripu.
shows. A little bit with the sleeping father
You can see. If the planet is combust or
If it is retro, then you will see this fruit. this
Another thing shows that such a person is nowhere to be found.
Do this somewhere by connecting with your fifth house.
Maybe. The reason I have done the fifth house
He said because  the 10th Lord was in the fifth of himself.
Gone and went inside the Second House. in the first instance
Someone by joining their family first
Business can do it. Aldo the Native Will Do
Binance Only. Because inside the fifth house
When the planet goes away with its own emotion
Independence shows nature that you can be a part of someone.
You can't work under. You try
They will do some of their own work. Yes, you can
B in the Field of Finance Also
Investments can be in things like.
But you will try to choose the business.
You can choose.
It shows one thing that you belong to the teaching profession.
They can be inside. Inside Analytical Work
Maybe. If it's like Planet Mercury
is. The factors of the entire 5th house
The elements are that when  the 10th House Lord Second
It sits inside the Namas chart so the whole
The Factors of the Entire 5th House of
Get activated. You can also see
There is no businessman in the family.
Or maybe somewhere in the family.
Will try to choose that business
Where the family can help you.
Father what I can tell you can be very
Good Singer. They can be very good singers.
Yes. They Very Well Known About the Art End
Music and Father Is Kind Hearted. if
It's not Planet Retro Combs then.
So now let's talk about the 10th House Slot
When sitting inside the third house of Namaz Chart
It shows in the prayer chart itself that it
The planet has now moved to the sixth by itself. every time
A planet goes to the sixth by itself.
He goes into the sixth with that feeling. at that time
Somewhere it shows that the native
Struggling with your profession
It will be. There is a problem with the slightest stability.
Came and went to the sixth from his
But in which house did it go in the third house?
Shows that The Native Will Be Service
The nature of the person oriented person will be service
The person who does it can be such a person
Sales are within the work of marketing.
He will try to be in the job.
If you don't even have a job, if you don't do business.
Even if he is, he will choose such a business.
Where he gives a service of any goods
Doesn't transact. He's just one on his side.
Provides a service. In his abs, his
Creates wealth. Like We Are Counselling. at that time
What are we doing? We are providing service.
are. We do counselling. You are not ...
He gives advice. I would have taken money for advice.
are. Let's take it as a commission. So he
The commission money is also from the third house.
That's what comes. And if he went to the sixth by himself, then
When you give advice, counseling
are. The wealth that is being received in the commission is
To your entire third and sixth
Aligns it. It Shows One Thing The
Communication is the Man King in There
Profession. They are rich in things. if
It is a planet like Mercury. Like if Saturn
Even if it is a planet, it is rich in things.
There will be. They have a very good communication.
If there is Mars, then Samites They Will Have A
Fight and arguments on their profession.
Because if Mars goes to the sixth from itself, then
There's a little bit of a bit of a bully there. Tue.
According to Bhavat Bhava, which is the third house,
There is a second to the second. So which other houses
All of them are the causative elements of all the thirds.
They come inside the house. One thing
See when the planet moves to the sixth from its
The native should always take care
If the profession is to be corrected  like the 10th Lord
What's in the third? You have to be in the service
Emotion for the Animals. As long as you are a
They won't serve. Because what is the sixth house?
Is it? It is of service. Who has he gone to? Sixth.
It has been removed from the tenth. And whose tenth house?
Is it love? Whose love is that? 6th House
There is love. If inside your Numas chart
You will see that the tenth from the sixth is the fifth.
It does. That is, the native should be able to eat his animals.
Pet Animals Gone, Street Animals
Serve them with a loving spirit
It will be. So he is his 10th Lord who is also from himself.
He has gone to the sixth and will be able to align him. a lot
Deep comes. Understand and see. Astrology
Not as easy as it sounds. a little bit
You have to go deep down and understand that every emotion
What it shows. It shows one thing as well
Such a person who will go into whatever profession he will
Only through their own efforts.
There may be uplift within the profession. Added to impart the meaning of ‘giver’ as  giver of water
Reason Is Third House Shows Your Efforts
is. The horoscope has a trishaya house. 10th Lord
Gone is also the third house of the sixth house.
It's in. So the native just has to deal with the struggle.
Efforts have to be put in. So this person
Uplift within your profession
is. What would happen to such a person? Whenever
You will do this work, there is no problem of wealth.
The day the work stopped, wealth down means don't give
Get the Blessings Actually. Meaning for
This is what God has said. You Karma
Keep doing it, don't desire the fruit. The day
When karma stops, the fruit will also stop on that day. at that time
They should keep this in mind that karma
It is your original duty to do. We are such a person.
You can say that maternal uncle is uncle
They can play a very important role in
Their Profession. Now you will wonder where Mama
Came from?
Now look at the third house that went to the sixth from you.
The sixth house inside shows Mama anyway
But it is also tenth from the sixth if Namas.
Inside the chart, count from sixth to third.
House becomes 10th i.e. Mama's karma
The area and your 10th Lord is gone.
In the sixth, it is of maternal uncle and karmakshatra.
Linkage shows a lot that your maternal
Uncle Will Always Be Very Helpful If This
Planet is not retro or combust if if
If it gets electrocombust, then not a little.
Negative results are seen. Added to impart the meaning of ‘giver’ as  giver of water
The reason is because inside the first third house
So he was in the same agony. Yes, if
If you can say that if it is not in a good amount, then
It's retro so let's go. So the native here
Those who will be neighbors will also be there somewhere.
Will be on the official post. If this Saturn
Like Kalpurush's horoscope as planet is
What we see in the Aries Ascendant Chart
And  the 10th Lord becomes your Saturn.
And he sat inside the Geminiae sign
are. So  the 10th Lord moved to the sixth from his
Gone. Your neighbours will be someone.
Authorities may be on the post. And it
You will find that any of your neighbors will be there.
Neither can anyone be physically disabled. if
It's like Planet Saturn. If like Mars
If it is so, then there is a grudge against your neighbors.
Will go. Keep that in mind. It Also
Shows One Thing 10th Lord When In Sixth From Himself
You just need to go inside the third house.
Be in the Travel Most of the Time When You
If you stay inside the journey, then you will be able to take care of your
You will be protected from the dangers of the profession
Because the 10th  lord of the profession who is his
Because of going from sixth to sixth, he was a Shad Ripu.
I'm stuck. You do your karma.
Through the region itself, all those drips
They will be trapped. Lust, anger, greed, attachment,
Arrogance. When You're on Your Profession,
You are in the profession, you are all your
All
You will remain surrounded by vices. When you don't work
If you are doing this, you will also be away from these vices.
Somewhere you must have found that when you
If you are in the profession, you just have these disorders.
They are surrounded by them. Try to use service
Emotion in your karma. Now that in Navmash 10th
Sitting inside Lord Fourth House Namash
Inside the chart itself. This is the axis of one to the other.
goes. Here, we see that when
The master of any emotion also looks at his own emotion.
If you take it, it is a very auspicious fruit.
That is, he emphasizes that feeling. I am using my
When I look at the house, I see my house.
I won't let it happen. So Native Will Have a Very
Secure Profession. And for such a person, one
The point can be said
That wherever the mind of this person feels, that profession
It's best to go in. The Reason It
Gone to the seventh from himself and in the horoscope
i.e. the Fourth House in the Numas Chart
Gone inside is what shows the mind. so
Profession things are always on the mind of the native.
Keep moving. Continue to move forward with your profession.
If Rahu is sitting together, like Saturn
The planet is sitting together, so somewhere
There will be an insecurity in the profession.
There will be a fear in the profession. Unknown Fear.
Aldo The Native Will Have a Very Secure
Profession. This shows that this is the sentiment of the people.
is. 4th House and in front of the public i.e. if
We look at perseverance. Passionately who is the seventh
It happens that he is the person in front of him. at that time
Which  is the axis of 4 in front of the public.
The master of the house to take over the people
It has already sat down. It shows that such
The natives have many of The Masses of People.
He motivates you. And the People Will
Attract Towards Them. Very quickly
They get attracted to this person
To. Inside the profession for this person
These things will be seen. That Profession
Related to the Land to the Cars. Mother Will
Play a very important role in there
Profession. First of all, for such a person, this
It is important that he grinds his domestic
Maintain. Whenever Domestic Grinding This Native
As long as it is fine, the profession will be fine.
Whenever the domestic piece is bad, nowhere else.
Somewhere he is the owner of the profession 10th house.
Lord who sits in the Fourth Namas Chart
He's in agony. Therefore, this native
To your mind and your domestic grind
Always keep a safe guard somewhere.
It is needed. You can say a lot of such a person.
We are fond of being a political leader.
He can become one and get into politics. this
It is important to see that the master of the center house
He is sitting in the center. How 10th House
It belongs to the center. The Fourth House is also a center.
It shows the same. If there is a mafic plan
If you look at the planet, then it is a bit of a profession.
Creating Struggles and Obstacles Inside
Trys. End Functional Malefic
Planet that accords to your Namas chart
It is formed. That's also important to see. Is he
Is it conjunct with the planet or sitting together?
is. The native wants to choose that profession.
Tries where comfort is given
Or do you go or stay in your comfort?
He wants to run the profession. It Shows The
Hotel Work Construction Work.
The work related to nursing means who is a nurse
The  Nurse Will Have the Work of
Nurturing nature. So that's the fourth house.
Nurturing shows nature. So such a person
You can also choose that profession. give
Can also be in the medical field. If it
Nurturing is still associated with that nature
By nature.
When  the 10th Lord sits down in the Forth. one
Always keep in mind that you are a member of the society.
What kind of deeds do they do inside that the public
Influences you or hates you.
is. If he's going to love you.
That is, the person in front of you is your person.
Let's get along well. It Means
Your 10th House Lord in the Fourth Is Very
Well placed. If the person in front of you
We are deceiving and we can say that
He is using you again and again.
Repeatedly upset about the thing somewhere
It is happening. Going to the Estate that
The person in front did this to me. my
Spoiled the profession. Thinking of something like this
are. It Means Your 10th House Lord in the
Fourthly, somewhere, he is the mafic aspect.
It's in. Or he can say we are that planet.
What is the conjunction with that planet?
Which is the functional malofic in the Naumash chart.
Planet is. Just Inside So Fourth House
Remember one thing that comes to mind.
Choose. Whenever you listen to your mind, sometimes work or
Obscures will not come under the profession.
Always the result will be fruitful. When in front
You will listen to the person and do some work,
Somewhere to spoil your profession
You will get it. Now let's talk about the 10th house
Lord Fifth is inside the house. It happens
That now the planet has gone into the eighth from itself
is. Whenever the master of any emotion is from his
Goes into the eighth. He's inside that feeling.
Transformations show. You can say that
Profession will not have the stability. that
Somewhere inside the profession
Transformations will be seen
It will be found. And that's one thing it shows.
Such a person is in that profession or in his deeds.
Choosing a field like research somewhere
Maybe. Can choose a field like Occult
And the native is an artistic personality.
Who keeps his art hidden. He is ...
Don't let that art be exposed.
In deeds. Such people have very good music.
Can be composers. And they can have the
Production Unit. The Kyunki Lag Numas
This is the fifth house of the chart. Which is toys or
Do any work related to this? Annie
Kind of Production Any Kind of Assets
Production That Come Under the Fifth House. when
The lord of your tenth house, the fifth of Navmash
Went in. Gone into your system.
Friends, you people feel like I am someone.
I set up a production unit. I'm not too big.
I set up an industry. I feel like it. Jataka A
It can also be on an authoritative post.
Because if the eighth house is the lord of the house
If you have gone to the eighth from yourself, then one
Can show the authoritative post. You Can
B. A. The Principal. You're a professor very much.
They can be good. Principals can be
Because the fifth house also shows education.
is. You teach a lot of kids something.
They can be. You are a very good one.
You can be a music teacher. You'll Be The
Very Good Stock Market Influencer. self
You are the one who gives guidance to the stock market
You can. Very good counsellors
Maybe. One thing is always for such a person.
Care should be taken. Their Partner Their Love
Partner Must Most of the Time Under the
Depth means they are buried under debt. Added to impart the meaning of ‘giver’ as  giver of water
Reese of that house of Navmash within the fifth house
The Swami came and sat down, which is the sixth.
The sixth from the fifth falls the tenth.
Who will be your love partner or your first one?
There will be a child somewhere or in a job.
Or they may have a lot of debt.
is. Aldo, we can say a little health issues.
You can also see it. If they have
If there is no sense of service. Education Will Plays
A very important role for this native.
Just reading is very important. Individual
Read types of books. Just try it.
That you can do research. Try to Research on
That field where that planet is sitting,
What type of planet is Mars, Mercury
There is Saturn, there is Rahu, there is Ketu. Whichever
Nature's planet, its causative element
Add it to your research field.
There can be many such people. stock
Go to the market. Betting, Lottery in
The person can also get involved in things like. Added to impart the meaning of ‘giver’ as  giver of water
Native will have to remember one thing. spell
Sadhana should be in the routine of your life.
As long as she stays in the routine. Mantra Sadhana You
They will continue to do it. Why Mantra Sadhana? Fifth House
For example, a mantra shows spiritual practice. It's our
Exposes the deeds of past lives.
So when the planet is sitting in the eighth from itself
10th Lord Either of you who had a previous life.
Karma is either keeping you worried or
Will you keep it in contemplation or make it like a pyre?
They will give. It is better to contemplate than to be like a funeral pyre.
(a) Calculate the value of How will you reflect? When in Samadhi
You will sit and do mantra sadhana. In your deeds
Keep cultivating the mantra. That is, a little mantra
What is spiritual practice? Like I did before.
I made a video. You can see that.
Each type of mantra practice can be different.
The lord of your karma is eighth from yourself.
He is sitting in the fifth place. You Have to Be in That
Routine. The routine in which you have to meet the children of the society
Look at it this way, yes, somewhere.
We see people like that in our lives.
There are still archeological objects that are still there.
It is taken care of. i.e
You may have seen a lot of things today.
In the era we are getting lost. What we sit down to do
They used to recite prayers. Mantra Sadhana
They used to do it. Somewhere we are all losing it.
There are times. Your personality is the responsibility of the society.
Children need to understand that yes there
There is something in our culture in our tradition.
So when this personality is in your life,
Your routine will be in your 10th house.
Lord Is Very Well Placed in the Fifth
House. What will you see otherwise? Professions
Things like transformation inside every time
You will get to see. Increased Karma from Time to Time
Keep changing, don't have that happiness inside the status
Not being able to get it, that status, that recognition
Finding an unstability in the profession
Stay. So,  to fix these things
Your personality needs a lot of
A little change. By the way, the 10th Lord in the
Good inside the Fifth House Prayer Chart
There is placement but of spiritualism
Very good in terms of spiritualism
There is placement. Now let's talk  about the 10th Lord
When inside the Sixth House.
10th Lord in the Six, look at it from yourself.
Moved to the Ninth and Inside the Navamash Chart
According to the Navmash horoscope, this is the sixth
The house has gone. So here's what to look out for.
When you get a plan by yourself.
If the triangle goes into the ninth and that too then it will
There is a very good placement. This is what we do
I wouldn't say anything bad.
But according to that whole chart, overall.
In the chart, it went inside the Sixth House.
is. So it shows The Native Can Choose The
Service of Civil Service Police Navy
Towards the line like Advocate, the native is a
Inclination will be seen. De Can
Prepare the exam for the judge.
What is the Sixth House of? Sixth House
It is about competition. What is the karma of such a person?
That's a competition in itself. As long as it
Until it enters the competition, it will not enter the competition.
One of the professions in the life of the native
Stability will not be seen. More Over
The Time If
The condition of this lord is going on in the marriage of Jat.
Inside and what you will find that this native is
I could get a very good job in that time.
Go to the native. We won't even say that
Health will deteriorate. It would be said that such people
There are chances of getting a job at that time and
You can get a very good job. If this
With Planet if not the Fifth House Lord
Why is he sitting? Because the 6th to the 12th
It is the fifth house. So Namash Chart
See this in 10th House Lord Joe VI
Are you sitting in the fifth house with the Lord?
I didn't sit down.
It also shows one thing that such a person has that
Most of the time in Dasha or Antardasha
The native must have given too many exams
If you are  around 25 to 30 years old, then this is how
The native is most likely to be in this Dasha Antardasha.
Many competitive exams of Planet
Let's make preparations. This is the feeling, isn't it?
There is a sense of shad ripu. So it shows that
Somewhere around these Shad Ripus.
Don't try to choose your profession somewhere
will. Native Will Be in the Medical Field
It can be in a department like Also Loan.
is. It can be in fields like finance.
If the Eighth Lord sits next to the 10th Lord
So went to the Sixth and together if Ath
The Lord also sat inside the Sixth House.
The native will be on an authoritative post.
He will be the one who does the job. And they can also be
In the Field of Insurance Company Excise
Department
Go abroad and work in an embassy.
Or can someone go to a foreign country?
Can work on an authoritative post
Police Army in such positions
This is the sixth house, which is the horoscope.
Shows the insult of Namash in the chart which
The sixth house is that it shows your humiliation.
The Planet Is Not Well Placed There Somewhere
You don't have a lot of problems in your profession.
You will have to take a sip of insult again and again.
Somewhere in the shadow of humiliation, one of your
Builds personality in which
The patience level goes on. This Patience
The level is so much that the native is aware of his future.
Able to set goals. The 6th house is therefore
Competition has also been shown that the native
You have to fight. What is Competition? Thousands
The children give the paper. Someone is selected
(a) Calculate the value of the product. So he has come forward by fighting. that
They have come forward by fighting against circumstances. a lot
There are still many villages where
There used to be electricity or not. All of these that
The facilities are available to us. But he
For the facility that was not provided by the facility
They don't cry. Whose 10th Lord Sixth
He must be sitting in his opposite of him.
Makes way for. So when the 10th Lord
You are the one sitting in the sixth.
Fighting against time and making a profession for yourself
You can make it very good. Suppose if
The 10th Lord is Mars or the Sun. If the sun is there
So, he will become elevated when he comes here.
If Mars and Sun are there and that is the Sixth House
Sitting inside and somewhere in your sixth.
If the House Lord is also sitting there
Inside the Sixth House, Then Native Will Be
Very Good Surgeon and He is in the medical field.
It could be inside. Maybe you have a bone.
Related to Borns which are bones
Whether it is in the medical field related to it or
You can be a very good surgeon. You Can
B. The Surgeon of Tooth Associated with Joe Surgery
Don't you do that thing related to the teeth?
It may be in the medical field related to
You are.
The Most Thing 10th Is Your 10th House
Lord is your karma and sixth is all yours
Disorders. So, such a person should be able to control his vices.
You have to know how to control. This is the sixth house
It is of vices. If Rahu sits in it
With the 10th Lord, the deeds of such a person
The vices in them increase so much that they
Stuck in these dumps. Lust
It will be too much. Desires Too Much
There will be. Can be greedy. Greedy of all kinds
The vice of anger will be all vice. in it
Can you say a little irritated, can't you say irritated?
Nature that happens when Rahu if 10th Lord
Sit down with Try Two in the Sixth House
Be in the State of Let It Be the Reason Is If
If Rahu is in the sixth house, then Ketu is somewhere
Ketu will be in the 12th  house from there
Apply activate otherwise which
Rahu is in the sixth house lord, by the way.
The enemy produces Hanta Yoga that you
You will always win over your enemy, but he
In your karma because your 10th Lord
Inside the Sixth House, he sat with Rahu.
So he is somewhere in your deeds.
You can say that you are like Malafic, can you not?
Things will be seen in your actions.
He does not allow karma to remain so sattvik. End
One More Thing When 10th Lord Ninth Than Himself
Stability in your profession then
You will get very good when you long.
Travel. And in the profession too, you have a lot of
You have to travel a long time.
Travel. And one more thing it shows is that it
He is tenth from the father. Inside the Numas Chart
The ninth to the 10th is the sixth house.
Somewhere you want to choose the same profession.
You can try that includes your father, too.
Have you ever been a father or a father in your profession?
You can be of great help. Try to Always
Respect your father profession. Your father
Of the deeds of you always have one somewhere.
Try to give them attention. Their
Respect. Now understand the 10th Lord
When inside the Seventh House.
See the lord of the center house again
I have come and sat down. And now look at it here.
Is this planet of any mafic aspect?
It's not inside. If Rahu Saturn is his
Aspect is coming if you are sitting with Ketu
Somewhere within the profession and
You can see the obscurant. The Bhawat on S
The lord of the tenth house is in the tenth house from himself.
Gone. Meaning this is a very deep thing to understand.
It's over here.
Your Life Partner Will Place a Very
An important role in your profession. And you can do this
You will also see that after marriage is your profession.
A Stability Inside You Have to See
Met. And most of all for such a person
Well, we can say that it can be a remedy.
You Have to Be in the Polite Nature While You
Are Engaging with the Other People and Also.
With Your Life Partner. If the ego comes here.
It goes because it has gone to the tenth by itself.
So somewhere it will show self-respect
That you have your self with the person in front of you.
They won't let down their self-respect. here
But this is a very important ego
The ego goes here. So you have to reduce ego.
It will be. What is otherwise? Your Joe 10th Lord
Nauvash is sitting in the 10th  inside the chart,
He is sitting in the seventh. So it's your profession.
It will start disturbing a lot from there.
It becomes very important for such a person
How he was dealing with the person in front of him.
Talking. If you are bent then the profession
Standing. If you are struggling, then nowhere
Somewhere the profession is leaning. So Just Be
In the Polite Nature. And keep this in mind
That such a person always has an interest
I can go into business. And these people are those people.
There are those who understand how to go into politics.
Let's just say that they think that maybe we
A Fame and Recognition Inside Politics
It can be found. Aldo, one thing here is very much
If that is then the Earth needs to be seen.
Inside the element is like Taurus Vargo and
If Capricorn is in the sign, then the native can be
I want to go into an industry like automobiles.
Try it. If this Geminiae sign, Libra
The sign and the aquarius sign are inside which
Shows the Aries sign. 10th Lord Agar
If it is inside these signs inside the Seventh House, then
The natural inclination of the native will be the most
Probably here that the army
Interested in becoming a pilot somewhere in the heart
I can go into the profession with things like this.
is. If the fire sign is in Aries Leo End
Sagittarius is in sign. 10th House Lord
In the Seventh House. So the native is an authoritarian.
Post, Government Job, Railway Field
Where there may be electricity and a
You have the authority. The electricity that I
It is said to be in the railways. Government Jobs
Also shows an authoritative post.
Also shows. So you belong to a profession like this.
You can also come in. What are we here now?
They will say that  the 10th lot has gone to the seventh.
So, where did the job come from? The reason is that he
It has gone from 10th to 10th which shows to the government.
is. So somewhere you are under the government.
Will try to do some work.
Like if people do construction work too.
are. Under the Government No Contract
Let's do it. So the Government Will Place a
Very important role in your profession.
He can be your life partner.
Have been a business partner before. Then You Become
A Life Partner. And it may also be that
Someone you're currently in partnership with,
He will become your life partner later.
Always keep in mind when  the 10th Lord in the Seventh
Yes, just check where your Seventh House Lord
Sitting. If he is inside the Mafic aspect.
Yes, he is sitting in a bad place. Likes 6 8
He is sitting in 12 houses. So, it shows
Is it your who you are doing business with?
In partnership, try to be in the
Alert State All the Time. What will happen otherwise?
Your business partner touches you
(a) Yes, Sir. Always keep one thing in mind that your
Spouses will be there, your life partners will be there
Will be very ambitious. The Reason Is For Them
The Lord of His Fourth House came in the Ascendant.
It's seated. Which shows that such
Along with the native being possessive, the spouse is ambivalent.
Somewhere in life, the status and
Giving too much importance to recognition
There will be ones. Your profession has only one
The thing can shake. That's Your Ego and Over
Confidence. When you're very good in the
Interacting with the People. You are very good.
They interact with people.
But keep the equanimous ego very carefully
You will. Too much in foreign countries
You can get good success. We can say
are. Or the state in which you were born.
From there, you have to go somewhere far away and have your own one.
The profession has to be stable. 10th Lord
When it goes to the seventh. The Best Remedy
It's only one thing. Just slide down
Yourself in the Front of Other Peoples. Say
It may seem strange, but it's the truth.
Always remember that there is a society behind them.
People who bow down and talk to the other person
Don't listen to your own answer with arrogance.
They continue to give. If you need a recognition
You have to bring stability within the profession.
is. The person in front of you is saying something.
You have to listen once. Then you can use his
You can argue the above. If Mars
Like a planet and if a planet like Mercury
He is the 10th House Lord and he sits in the Seventh.
So keep one thing in mind that is the center.
Treapati is also blamed. So sleep
Try to see that planet of the center
When the lord of the center house sits in the center
If in the aspect of the Malefic Planet
If the contagion of Malefic Planet is together
He is prone to a flaw. The defects that
Shows that what is a white cloth
There is also a small black stain on top.
That center is not the center overlord, the fault is nowhere
It's somewhere similar. You're very good in the
Profession but there must be an error
Will it be a profession or your behavior?
Inside which is your fame recognition state
She can hurt him. Now let's understand when
The 10th  Lord of Namash in Your Eighth House
Namash is inside the chart. Watch Now
The 10th  Lord moved from his 11th to the 11th
But it went to the eighth house inside the chart
is. It Shows One Thing When A Planet Comes By Itself
Goes into the 11th. The Native Will Be
Very ambitious towards their profession and
Towards their work. It can be such a person
Try to get into this profession where
But he does not interact with the people in front of him.
It does more. Through the Calls, Through the Wee
He interacts with people digitally from the can.
You take it because you have gone inside the eighth house.
So the causal elements of the eighth house are completely
You will be awakened. This shows that such a person
There is a lot of transformation within the profession
There are more. There are different types of changes.
Live. Either this person is in that profession
Will try to go inside which the research
Be it work, occult work, engineering
The line is done, it should work like a coding language.
Gone. If the Sixth Lord or the Sun together
If so, this person may be a UPSC student.
You can prepare for the exam. Just like we
IAS, IPS Preparation for these exams
If you are trying to get into that field, then the person is trying to go into that field.
Where they have the authority. eighth 8th
There are other things too. If here
Planet becomes malefic i.e. mafic
The aspect comes on this planet.
Such a person would have been attracted to wrong deeds
is. The deeds that we can say like today's
In time we might call it robbery smuggling.
It is possible to get into a bad habit.
Get engaged. So, the deeds of the native are
It is determined on this matter
Those who are in the 10th Lord of the 8th House.
What kind of strength does that planet get inside
It has been. That is, others who are mafic or functional.
Is there a faulty planet on top of this planet?
They are giving respect. One thing to keep in mind
It should be kept that the person should try here.
He should either be from his state or from his state.
Going to the state and setting up your profession
Or should he go to a foreign land and settle down?
From where the Karaka element of the eighth house
Trying to uplift her profession
will. It shows also one thing that such a person
Lottery, betting and these things can also come
There are things that are done secretively, which we
That is, there is no work in front of the society.
Let's do. Such a person can have a father.
The Journey a Lot They Can Be in the Healing
Profession. Because for the Father His wealth
The lord of the house  is sitting in the 12th from him.
That is, the second from the ninth is the 10th .
is. And the one who is sitting in the 12th  from the ninth
The master of the second house is sitting with his father.
For. The father will either be away for a long time
Or will he be in the profession where
They have to travel a lot.
You live in another state. Healing
You are in the profession. Like We Can Say Ah Like
The nature of the Father can be very charitable.
If this planet is sitting well here. and
If the aspect of Benfic planet is coming
Father Will Be Very Above This Planet
Charitable in the Nature Investment Manager
It can be because the 12th house
It also shows investment for the father
Can work inside a field like a hospital
are. One More Thing's the feeling that it is for you.
Shows that if we assume here that
Leo is the Ascendant. Venus is  the 10th Lord
is. What is made up of you inside the Navmash chart
Navmash is made up of Leo ascendant. So Venus
Those who are  there are 10th lords and those who are there are
You would come to the house and get excited here.
are. So this thing shows that after your
Partner Your Family After Your Partner Your
Profession will be stable. It may be yours.
Partner's family members of your profession
Try to help a lot inside. End
Your partner family will be much higher richer
Then Your Family.
So pay too much attention.
It is also needed according to the ascendant. as
The gym is the Gemininai ascendant. Gemininai Marriage
The Pisis sign comes inside the 10th  house
And it becomes debilitated at the eighth house.
Inside because Capriccorn in the Eighth House
The sign arrives. So now all the results here
Will change. What do we see here?
Aldo, just this planet should not be retro here.
So, the planet would have become the Raja Yoga factor here.
Because the planet is already in the eighth house.
If he is degraded, he becomes worthy of giving Raja Yoga
That is, inside the life of such a person.
Struggles will come, but somewhere it will be its own.
Will settle the profession in one place
Changing from your place to a place and settling
If this planet becomes retro then it will be very
The most we can say is that the results are opposite.
All will go because if the retro planet
Despicable and if retro then he
Dissolvates Raja Yoga and in the Eighth
Sitting dissolves in the same way. Either he
You don't have retro or it's from that planet.
Don't sit next to a functional maloptic planet.
It is formed. According to that passion, it shows overall.
That for such a person inside his profession
It is very important to make changes. And him
Never Reveal Your Profession's Secrets
The person in front of you should not be revealed
with. When They Reveal Their Profession
Secrets Somewhere Inside the Profession
Obscurantism or struggle is seen.
Now let's talk about when  the 10th in the T9 chart
Lord is sitting inside your ninth house.
There is a very good placement. If Ninth
The Lord should also  sit in the 10th. Ninth Lord
If you are sitting in the ninth grade, then this action
It is called Adhipati Yoga. Or both of them.
Let there be an exchange among themselves. So this karma
The overlord produces yoga that it
Whatever work the native does, he will do very well.
In such a situation, it has been written in the tenth of Jataka Saravali
It is written in that chapter that the House is written that
Such a person will be a virtuous person. Like Joe
I call it They Are the Pure Soul. Added to impart the meaning of ‘giver’ as  giver of water
The reason is because it is not moral of the native.
Ethics will always awaken that I
Do not do any wrong within the society.
is. I have to make my status high in the
Society. Now how will that status be high when?
I will do good deeds. This is how moral ethics are:
The native is always awake. Nowhere
Somewhere you will come who  is the 10th Lord by himself.
He is sitting in the 12th. The Native Will Be Very
Charitable in the Nature. Yes, it could be a father.
There may be some grudges in the relationship
Because  he is sitting in the 12th from himself. So we
It can be said that such a person with his father
Relations will not be good. Maybe from the father.
You've been away for a long time. Aldo Agar Ninth
Lord is also sitting in the 10th  and somewhere
Relationship with father is good. now
Here's one thing.
It is the ninth house, it is the fifth house.
So when from the fifth house which is the factor of the fifth house
There are elements, they are causative elements, they are all nowhere
Somewhere to see you in the Ninth House.
See you. Profession is like this for such a person
Like travel means travel so much.
There is more involvement in the profession
Inside that he was in his travels all the time.
Lives in the profession. It Shows One Thing
The native will be a very good we can say
If there is a planet like Jupiter, then it is very good.
The person will have education. Quite ahh
The person must have knowledge of the subjects. infant
Can Be in the Field of Professor, Teacher Us
You can go in line. And if it's the planet
Moon or Venus is like Moon or Venus
The 10th Lord and sitting inside the Ninth House
So it shows The Net Will Have The Profession
In the music and in the dance as well. one
Always remember the 10th Lord, your prayers.
Inside Cha whenever inside the Ninth House
Sit you have to be respecting yours
The guru gives you this much knowledge, does it not?
Just understand that it has given me the way.
I always say a line a lot.
There is a good line, it has been said if the native will.
Have a very spiritualism in nature.
These people will be able to understand that Guru Gobind is the one who gave the go-to guru.
Khade Kake La Gopal Balihari Guru Aapki
Tell Govind Dio
It's a very good line.
In this line, it is such that the native should be like this.
I want you to tell me this much too.
Nor is that too much for me. The Reason Is That
When the guru's grace is being bestowed upon you, isn't it?
He is sitting in the 10th  Lord Ninth
Can take the profession to a place where
You never thought about it. So when the 10th Lord
Someone is sitting in the ninth with even this much knowledge.
Give that knowledge a lot of your understanding of it.
Make way. Your mind will say that yes this
Person wants to think of my good somewhere.
It has been. Then leave it on the planet that
Yes ok if you want me to do so
I do it and I feel fine too.
Somewhere your intuition power is too much.
Strongly will tell you because karma bhava
The lord is  sitting in the 12th from himself.
That is, the intuition power in your actions.
Linkage. So you'll know that person
That he has done me a lot of good as a guru.
It will be done. Inside it, we are
Let's see that education can educate itself.
(a) Calculate the value of You need to understand spiritualism
It will be. And you have to travel long
It will be. If you want your profession
Travelling inside. Out of your state
You have to go. You will have to travel abroad.
That's why you get into your profession.
You can get upliftment. You are such a person
Can give very good counseling
Yes, because the Ninth House is counseling.
And the fifth house is a consultation.
Of. So  when the 10th Lord sat in the ninth.
In the 9th chart itself, the net will have a
Very good counselling skills. If this mercury
If you have a plan, then talk very well.
It comes to the native. Even if it's more education
He doesn't have it, there's not much we can say.
Schooling may not have been good, but the native will
No How to Talk with the People. And to talk
The tone of such a person is very good.
If it's like I mentioned before, if Venus,
Mercury or Moon-like planet is 10th Lord
Yours. And he's sitting in the Ninth House,
Native will be very good looking. Enough Ah
You can say it is attractive. Attractive Face
It will be such a person. No society to such a person
You have to sacrifice inside. The Region
He is the lord of his karma 12th from himself.
Sitting. When a planet sits 12th  by itself
If so, he asks for sacrifice. society
Maybe some people meet like this
That whatever you use but you will no one.
Thing. As much as people are using you,
You're always getting more than that.
Somewhere you'll fall again, stand up.
Will go. The 10th Lord is in the ninth. go to sleep
Sacrifice
Sacrifice should be in your nature.
Okay? I have to. I have to do it.
For everyone. When this will be the nature of the Ninth House
Blessings will always be with you. so
You can also choose a profession in which
You have been his father. First or with Father
Someone can work together. The native has his
Can stabilize the profession in that place
Where it is a foreign land. Of Healing
Be a profession. End
This is what we call the High Era of Philosophy.
They say that philosophy is very good.
He can also go inside that field. Aldo
It's great to sit in the 10th  Lord IX.
Placement takes place. If you have to give inside
There is emotion. Karma that is in the 12th  from oneself
Gone. Have a sense of giving. As many as
10th Lord is sitting in the Ninth House,
He will be able to connect with me. That
You have to give. The more you give, the more
You will get it. There is never any heat in the profession
It will come. As long as there is a sense of giving. Let It Be
It doesn't matter what everyone did. When it
There will always be a feeling in the mind inside life
You will get to see the upliftment. now
You understand that when  the 10th Lord sits in the 10th
Be inside the Mass Chart. Now see 10th
When Lord sat down in the 10th,  it was very
There is a good placement. Understand this first.
What are the factors of the 10th  house? Saturn,
Mars, Sun, Mercury Somewhere you get this
Shows that what is the Malefic Planet
They do good work in the 10th  house, not
It is a benign planet. Benefic planets such as
Jupiter is done, Venus, Moon.
We will tell them that this is a benign planet.
They don't have that much work here. Okay?
It will give you upliftment within the profession
They will give. But he is not able to give happiness
Who would have given this Malefic Planet by struggling
are. So if you have the Saturn, son,
Mars, Mercury in That Sign It Shows Life
There will be a struggle inside the profession
But the upliftment will definitely be available for sure.
It is said that the lord of the center
He is sitting in the center. Now for one thing.
Keep in mind for the Gemininai Ascendant,
Virgo Assent, Sagittarius & Pis
Assentent. If  the 10th House Lord is in the 10th
Sitting talking about Namash Chart
I have been. This is not the case with the ascendants of Namash.
The center makes a origin of the overlord defect
That this planet is so benign, so clean. if
Above this comes the aspect of Malefic Planet.
What if the faulty planet is conjunct?
He gets to blame. Because which
The center is very gentle and clear.
They have said neat expressions. Meaning is a white cloth
There is not so much worm on top of it.
When he sits down, he can see it from a distance. that
Stains appear. So here's the center of the Atipati.
Defects arise. Shows Sleep
That in spite of everything, somewhere.
Happiness will not be there in the profession.
There will be no happiness. If the center is overright to blame
If you don't have it inside the numas chart, you will find it.
There will always be blessings in the profession.
Whatever actions you perform, you will definitely receive the fruit.
It shows one thing that such a person is in his career.
Inside you stand from the opposite situation.
Stands up to the profession. 10th House
It shows the fame in our society.
That's how much fame you'll have. Planet if
It is well placed here, so we can
There will be a very good fame in the society. society
People would love to get your opinion. It
Shows that such a person is going to run after fame
It will be. They Need Recognition in There
Profession. And such a person is recognized and famed.
He also takes it. 10th House Ours
It shows the government. The native is trying.
Can it be a government job or a government job?
To go to the side. Native Will Have the Very
Bold personality. An Authoritative Authoritative
The personality of the person is that he likes it.
It is about placing an order. And this order is equal
Personality of giving with the person in front
It makes you feel hatred. Always Remember
One Thing The Native Will Be Very Work
Oriented and Very Ambitious Towards Them
Profession. He is very proud of his profession.
It is more ambitious that I just work.
It has to be done. It is work for such a person all the time.
The work will go on. Whatever is the nature of the native
She becomes an independent nature.
is. If the sun is here, the sun means you.
Scorpio is ascendant. Namash Scorpio
If it is made of the ascendant, then the fifth 10th lord is
That Leo sign arrives. The sun is sitting there
So it gives overconfidence sometimes. when
The ruler of the house is sitting in the same house
So he definitely gives overconfidence. but
One thing this reminds me of the story. A frog
They put it in the teapot with water.
Filled it up and turned on the gas downstairs. That water
It's warming up and the frog is sitting comfortably.
So what does one see? Near the frog
He has the ability to jump out
Maybe. But he doesn't leave. He sat down
It lives under water. What to see
Get it? He feels something difficult.
It's not for me. I get out when I want
I can. Water temperature warms up slowly
It begins to happen. He doesn't come out.
It's too late, it doesn't come out. When watering
The whole starts boiling and then he tries
He can't get out even if he wants to.
Because all his energy was to be borne at that time.
But she goes out and she overs it.
Confidence kills him when I
I will leave. So 10th Lord when 10th
Namaz takes place inside the house.
Over Confidence and Ego Only Down Your
Profession and someone to shake your profession
I can't do it except you and your karma.
Therefore there is always an inclination in your deeds
It should be kept. Yes, okay. What you are saying
That's okay. It shouldn't be that I
I know more than you. When it's the ego and it
There will be overconfidence. Aldo, you know
Be about him but you still have to lean on
You have to show that you have to bend and bow down.
A little bit. Ok no problem profession
It will be fine. When you are on top of the profession
The point will come. Therefore, the native should have his
Losing through potential overconfidence
I don't want to. You Have the Ability to Do
Annie Work. Just understand that planet. Saturn
So you can indge in the steel iron work.
Like we can say that you are also in travel.
You can. If there is a moon, if there is Venus, then which
Painting, music, all this in the profession
Maybe. If dancing is mercury then
You would like to do business. In the Teaching Line
You can go. Jupiter is from  the 10th house by the way.
Inside, Jupiter does not produce good fruit. but
You can still be a teacher. Give counselling
You can. Very good. It's the sun, it's the sun,
If it's Mars, you'll try someone.
To go to the authorized post. You like
It will happen that you are in a job on such a post.
Wherever you want, you have a small authority.
Yes, but it should be. Factors of Sleeping Planet
Understanding the Element 10th Lord When in 10th
Understand that he is sitting. Now let's talk about when
10th Lord 11th House Inside Namas Chart
It happens inside. Now the plan is from itself
The second has gone. Any planet when
It is better if one goes from one to another.
It bears fruit. Most Probably, This
Shows that every deed is happening to you somewhere.
It will be positively rewarded. Because when
The planet went from itself to another, that is, it
The bank balance has gone in. By yourself
You will reap the fruits of your actions in others.
We will meet you. Netty Will Have a
Very Good Status in the Society and Social
Inside the gathering there is a good namesake
Of such a person. But understand one thing.
It is the 11th house, it is six to six.
There is a sixth to a sixth. Tries to do that
There are a lot of servants around such a person.
(a) Calculate the value of the product. In whatever profession it will be
There will be servants there with them or at home.
But there are many servants. Such a person
Pass. The Native is Very Good in the Speech.
Communication skills are very good.
Through Late Speech Native Will Make More
Resources for Their Wealth. Different Types
Let's make resources. if
It's a planet like Mercury. So, you are such a person.
You can be socially through your speech accomplishment.
To become a center of the point in gathering
He tries and can say that we are such a person.
He is the one who makes jugaad
Neither does he run his profession one thing.
Keep in mind if this planet is here.
Combust to come within the malefic aspect
Now you must be thinking that Nauvash is retro.
How can a chart be combust or retro?
Which planet is inside your passion chart?
Combust is retro, that's somewhere in your
Even inside the Navmas chart, you will find that position.
(a) Calculate the value of the product. So try it.
To understand. If it's a moon-like planet, then
Such a person can go into the work of drinks.
Like where liquidity is seen.
It can also go inside the stock market.
You can also go inside a field like finance.
is. Where there is a lot of liquidity and speech.
There is more work. Jupiter-like Planet
So he tries. Jataka Education Field
I  want to go into the field of finance.
If you have mercury, then you have to go into analytical work.
Trys. If like is Jupiter then it is
If you sign the segregated  in the 10th house
Comes and he is debilitated in the 11th  house.
goes. Now take a look here.
One thing that is seen for the native
not
A lot matters at that time that his
The 10th Lord  gets debilitated in the 11th.
This shows that such a person has to try.
He should always help the other person.
Because now you are socially your karma lord.
The one who is the master of karma  is the 10th lord
It has been debilitated inside the House. So You
Just have to be in the spirit of service and so
There is a lot of need to go into the field of education.
Nice tries. Shows Struggle
But still, the results are good somewhere.
Takes it out. Because Trishadaya is the bhava.
Whenever there is a planet in the Trishadaya house.
He is despicable, he is somewhere in Raja Yoga.
The factor becomes the planet. Native Will Have The
Gains in the Financial Terms But Peace
Don't get a wish very quickly.
The second desire is awakened.
Because you see that one action is one
The horizon of the center house is the tenth and a desire
The horizon of the triangle house is the horizon of the craving house
If there is a horizon, then it is inside the deeds of the native.
The desire never ends. He is ...
He is a chase of desires.
Try to just say that we are our
Bind the desires. When you
Desires will be tied inside the profession
A stability will be seen. otherwise
Struggle within some profession
You will get to see the obstacles.
See you. Because the master of the center house who
He is sitting, sitting  inside the 11th House.
Who  is the 10th Lord. Jataka Samatias
Greedy gets done. Greedy in the Nature. So,
You should try to understand this nature.
That when  the 10th Lord is in the 11th, you have to
Not too much greedy. In your profession
Whatever profession you are in, try
Understand the causal element of that planet.
of. Now let's talk  about the 10th Lord when your
Are you sitting in the 12th  inside the D Nine chart?
So it shows that the person who
Initially, you need to learn obscures within the profession.
You will get to see. The Reason Is 10th Lord
Third from yourself to yourself in the trishadaya bhava
Went in. You Have Too Struggle A Lot In
The Profession. The native is very fond of his profession.
He changes the bar and changes his profession.
Inside you will find that communication
You have to maintain very good skills.
Travel is very much and this
Within the profession, the native should have his birthplace.
You have to leave. Why? Because it's the third.
He is sitting in the house. The third house is not to change.
Also shows. The 3rd House is Your Self
Shows the efforts. The native is doing his own deeds
It will never be attached. He's going to do that.
That would be okay, I've done it. it's alright
I will get the fruit that has to be there. Such a Nature
It becomes the native's. Alad the Native Will Be
Very Good Teacher of Yoga Meditation NGOs
Working Together Charitable in the Nature
It will be because the lord of the house of karma  is the 12th.
The house has gone. Intuition of such a person
Power is very strong
Because  the 12th house is of no imagination.
Such a person has so much about his work.
He thinks he wants his job.
But sometimes it can't do it.
When he sits down to work, just obscals or
Somewhere to see obstacles in work
Meets. But still he keeps those obstacles
Crossing one in his profession
Brings stability. Medical-like line,
Go inside the hospital-like line in the field
The person can also set his profession.
Alad Native Can Set Their Profession in the
Foreign Land Foreign Land Also. The Reason Is
The 12th house also shows your foreign land.
is.  The 12th house is of change and the house of karma
The master sat there. So in deeds
There are frequent changes. It shows
That for such a person if that Rahu sits there.
So don't do it this way.
Gives that the person does wrong deeds even if he does not want to.
It sits. If Rahu is sitting next to him
9th  in 12th  House with 10th Lord.
Native can also indus der in the
Investment work. oh great
Such people can be investment managers
Or you can say investment advisory.
The giver can be from where he is commissioned.
You earn it. If you have gone to the third by yourself, then
The role of commission is very much played that
He would take commission from some work or the other
Live. Healing Counseling It All
Profession of yours in this 10th Lord when in 12th
When he sits, he comes. The Reason Is From There
Sees the 6th house that you are in front of you.
How quickly can you heal a person?
Relish the conflicts of many people
These people can also be doers. Morant
The Thing Is They People Have A Very Strong
Intuition power.
Through this intuition power, it is able to achieve its karma.
You can make the area look great. when
Sitting in the 12th, so meditation is the key
To Stable Their Profession. You need to meditate.
I have to join. Rooting You in Spirituality
Gotta join. You need to know spiritualism.
We need to understand what these changes are
Why are these changes happening to me? It
What is the main logic behind it? Then you can ...
Catch the causative element of the planet that it
Is there a planet, can I connect to that planet?
Am I working? Like in the house before
Told what factors of the planet
There are elements.  Inside the 12th house if your
It would be great if Lord Saturn is the 10th.
It will give growth within your profession somewhere.
Nowhere else. Yes, he will give Saturn's work
It is giving. If it's Mars, you'll need to put in your efforts.
There is a lot of love. If Mercury
If so, such a person tries immediately.
I can go and settle down. Venus is so good
In the position because  in the 12th house when Venus
When He comes, He is the One who gives very auspicious results.
It happens. Such a native fashion modeling
Music Art Trying to Visit These Places
does. It also goes into the medical field.
If the Sun is with Venus on  the 10th.
If Lord  is sitting in the 12th. So 10th Lord
The native has to understand this by sitting in the 12th
Variations. The Secret Behind the Change and My Joe
Imagination is the power of your actions.
Can I use that power of imagination to help my
Can I do it or not? Deeds
You have to do sadhana because  the 12th house is also one.
It shows spiritual practice. Correct your actions.
If you are wrong
Are you inside an ab or a wrong society?
If I am inside friends, then change it.
It will be. What else is it? The 12th house is also of jail
It happens. Such a person will act in such a way that he will be jailed.
You have to go.  He is sitting in the 10th and 12th.
The 12th house is also of foreign land. The native has his
It will go out through actions. NGOs
There is also charity. By connecting with these things
Will it work or is charitable in nature?
It will be. So 10th Lord, when you are just in 12th.
Mark the One Thing: Change is the law of life.
For you. So what we talked about today is that
What in the 12  houses of the 10th  Lord of Navmash?
There is fruit. It's a good topic. But it
Understand that a lot of people say that De Nine
Planet Retro or Combust Inside the Chart
They don't. Actually, they would have been
are. If Inside the Planet Ascendant Chart
It's retro as well as inside the diane chart.
Will go inside the retro position itself. And if
No very close to the Sun inside the D9  chart
The planet is sitting. No conjunctions with the sun
If I am there, it has been combusted somewhere.
You have to accept this. The Principle
The same D9 applies to the Ascendant Chart.
Will also apply to the chart. So where ...
There is talk of combust or retro
It has to be understood that if the passion inside the chart
It's retro as well as inside the diane chart.
It will be retro. Again on to another session.
We'll talk. If you have any questions, you can ask.
are. I'm trying to answer. then
Take care of yourself for the time being. Jai Shree
Krishna. Jai Shri Ram.