Jai Shri Ram Jai Shri Krishna Welcome to Hour
YouTube Channel Refined Vedic Astrology
[Music]
Today's session is our Rahu
To understand that when Rahu's different planets
If there is a conjunction with the Internet, then what is the benefit for us?
We get to see it. You can try it.
You will also see that the fifth and ninth from Rahu
Which planet is inside the house? That too to you.
It will bear fruit only in the form of conjunction.
You can see it in all of these charts.
Maybe. This will let you know that which
Planet Rahu is Rahu and Mercury
One thing is said for the generali that it
Whichever planet you sit with or who
The planet is ahead of them.
Inside the house, it is the causative elements of that planet.
They do it all on their own.
That is, they act in the same way as him or
This act is like that of whomsoever it is.
Let's try. So generali today.
This is the age of Kaliyug. So here we are.
Let's see that Rahu is very much.
Probinently, you see it working
It will go. You're looking at me this way. who
You can see this reflection of me, this one
Rahu is in itself. So, this is the role of Rahu
It becomes very important in the era.
So, we see that Rahu when all
Let's sit with the planet, what to bear fruit
Let's try it? The mother of Rahu
The causal element is not the illusion. That's one of them.
Illusion is what creates confusion and that
You believe the illusion. It's out
Off the box thinking is a planet.
I mean, you understand a story about it. one
Humans got gin. The Jin said to him,
If you keep me working continuously, then
I will tell you
Will keep you happy. I'll keep you alive.
Otherwise, I'll kill you.
Rahu is in such a way that by putting him to work.
Keep it and he's happy. Where he sits
Comfortably, you are not giving him any work.
The planet he is with in the house he is in.
So you suffer from that feeling and that planet.
It starts to come because it is all over him.
Somewhere as we see the sun,
Rahu also gives an eclipse. The Sun and
Rahu eclipses the moon. So by the way
He began to eclipse that planet.
gives. The whole factor of his whole
It's like a black hole. She's her
The gravitational force is so high that
He absorbs everything. So, such a
This is Rahu. His gravitational force is this.
The way that works is on the other planet.
Completely eats up the causative element of
And he binds them in this way.
Analogous to the factors of that planet
They just can't do the right thing. That is why he is a
Illusion is created. Here we have
Rahu should see us as a desire.
Shows. Rahu shows a hungryness
is. He's a hungry one. It means he needs knowledge.
Or he needs a fame in the society.
I mean, we will talk about that when the planet
If you are with him, what does Rahu ask for there?
on. Think of it as Rahu in this way.
It's going to work that never ends.
Will be.
If the work is over, then the causative element of Rahu
Over. Rahu is why we say that
It shows that it shows the foreign. Foreign
Shows the land that is far away from here
is. You have to travel. Out of the
You have to think about the box to get out.
You have to work hard outside.
To go. You usually do a little bit of work.
You can't get out of here. You have to be out of the
You have to think about the box to go out. this
One shows the security. Whatever
It will be with the planet, with which Trine
It will be,  in the trine of whichever planet,
You are insecure about that relationship there.
They will always be there. It's too big
It shows the industry. of Rahu
When the influence is on a person, it
Like the entire film industry.
The whole is afflicted with Rahu. We see that
Rahu's role is so much in this era that
It is spread everywhere. So we have a lot of it.
It is more important to understand that when Rahu
With the planet or in the trine of each planet
If so, what fruits do you get to see?
First of all, we start Rahu Jab If
What's the first thing to do with the sun?
Shows? The Sun Natural is a father factor
And the sun is the first for a father.
There are children. The first child. So here you are.
Think of it as long as the Sun and Rahu are with you.
Or is Rahu in the Sun's sign or Rahu's?
The Tyne has the sun. So until the father and the first
Children will live together, not with each other.
It becomes. Conflicts remain. Opinion
There is a mismatch. Even if something is going well.
If it happens, then something will pop up after a while.
Goes that he spoils the relationship
is. Therefore, when there is such a congestion, the father and
Son or daughter to stay away somewhere
should. As long as it's not far from each other
Until then, there will be no separation that is called or
The attachment that we say will not be made.
Otherwise, again and again, this sun of Rahu
Relationship is deteriorating due to conjunction
is. Pitta and son and daughter are the ones who give you till
You will get to see The End Life. of the native
I wish he could settle down immediately.
Because the Sun is the natural love soul factor
is. We'll see. The native will feel that
Should I go abroad and settle down or that?
Settle down immediately and do yourself very well.
Professionally, you will be able to uplift. Sun Fame
What is the factor? The native may have it very often
You have to be humiliated. Sun such as
It shows your respect, your fame.
It shows,  it shows the status. of Rahu
There's a conjunction with him that
It's putting a stain on him. So where is the stain?
Will it be? It will be on top of your status. He
It will depend on your personality. Therefore, this
For the native, it is not from his own state.
Go to another state or a foreign country
Go to the country and settle yourself. at that time
This person aligns himself somewhere.
takes. Then both the Sun and Rahu here.
They align their places.
We also see that the native his first
So much attachment to the child
He starts tying her. and
When he ties her up, somewhere
The first child is much more than her opposite
It starts to stand up. Due to which then
Again we see that the reason for the Sun Rahu
From the relationship between the father or the children
Dispute was seen. Such a person has a
There is an appetite for authority. Recognition
There is hunger. No doubt this is an immens to the native.
It gives wealth. If the native is away from his father
Trying to set up a profession
does. Too much fame and then too much
You get to see more wealth.
In this, the sun is seen in our eyes.
Shows. So, here is the next week.
Maybe.
You will see the problem in Eyes.
The Sun We Talked About Natural Spirit Factor
And Rahu is an illusion that is fear, then the native
Somewhere, there is always an unknown fear.
It goes on its whole life. Now here we are.
You understand when Rahu is in the company of the Moon.
So the person who is the moon, who is the mind, now the mind
The influence of Rahu above is such that it is very
He is overthinking. What is the mind?
What is our state of mind? Of our mind
How are the emotions going? Above that
So much of Rahu, one Rahu has so much for him.
The state of mind is such that it is held
That would be too much of a thinker. No
Doubt is so much fear inside the native.
He wants to tell that fear to someone.
I don't know. So that's an unknown fear in his mind.
But it always is. But with this conjunction or
When Rahu is in Trine, this is the Moon's lot.
There are good resources. Because of thinking
If you are used to it, you can think out of the box.
are. This research can do so well
Perhaps no one can do better research than them. this
A very good process of Lunar Rahu
is. And in this, if you align Rahu
If you want the Moon in conjunction with Rahu
You should not go around the circle.
The more you circumambulate, the more you do it.
The mind is going on in the circle and when you
When you physically orbit, your mind
I am getting negative thoughts, I am not saying anything.
Does his energy flow out or
This person will travel as much as he can
Travel will settle in its profession
Life will be a professional upliftment.
There will be a domestic grind and a mind that will be a
I'm afraid he's going to get out somewhere.
Mother's life is somewhere you struggle.
The moon will look full and natural.
Mata Karaka is called. Illusion
To see the ambitions that are there
Get that his desire is something. Some of that
Wants to get. But he's in a dilemma
Will he find her? That's a lot to get
I want something, but it's an illusion.
Somewhere. It's impossible to get it physically. like this
The native thinks. Be too emotional
He wants to control his emotions.
It starts to do. Mentally, you understand.
You will get to see this in the mind of the person
There is no peace somewhere. if
You have to align here, don't you?
Work on the Artistic
Works. That you don't work with any art.
Do. Work within an art.
Because the Moon is not in Rahu, the state of mind
It remains like this. He remains a thinker.
Imagination is very strong. that
Put imagination out in your art. when
If you take it out in art, then here.
Moon Rahu aligns. Or
You don't do anything except travel
Because there's such a thing as travel, it's everybody.
Humans can. Always out of the native.
One should try to think of a box. as long as
He will think in a limit, he will not align it.
You will get this energy. And here we see
When the Moon is Rahu, it is not Chin
A little bit of what you'll see slimmer and
Forehead is that little bit to see you wide.
Get it. Now when Rahu's conjunction or
With Mars in Rahu Trine
When there is a concussion, it is normal.
We've all heard it, we've all heard it.
An Angaraka originates Yoga.
That is, Mars which is Agni and Rahu is that
The wind is there that ignites the fire. So when
If there is a conjunction of Rahu and Mars, then this person
It's very annoying.
But this person can also be a bodybuilder
is. Will bring a muscular body. to this
Gymming will feel great. Running it
It would be great to do. So much inside the body
The excitement arises that you will be able to
Acne means seeing pimples on the body
See you. Will there be any birth mark?
Inside the body.
It shows the impulsive nature that the native
Tries to make a second decision
And later on that decision, he was very much there.
He lives in more pain. To this person
You should think before doing any work
Mars before or before making any decision
And Rahu also shows that the native thinks
He doesn't think anything before speaking. her
There will be a special interest in the speech. be
It may be that when this person talks
Extremely abusive
Use the language. This is very much for the native.
Gives a good kind of vine through the land
Through the Foreign Land. Now if this person
If someone does property related work.
Fruit in the city where it is born
It won't. You have to go out of town.
When this person goes there and works, doesn't he?
So this person gets very good results
to. Conflict with older siblings
You will get to see and the native will get to try it.
You need a little bit of it on your tongue.
You have to control it.
if
You're not running. You are physical.
If you are not working out, then somewhere
You have the energy of Mars Rahu.
You have spoiled your body. That body
Creating a lot of anxiety inside
is. You will be overthinking because now
When the energy is not draining, where is it?
Will you? From that it will go to the mind, to the mind
It will go. That's why physical workouts are huge.
Remedy is for Mars Rahu. Actually
People get over-driven too much.
Here and it's a very good placement.
People who play games like army, police or athlete
I want to go to a lot for them.
It's a good placement because there's a lot of placement there.
Mars does its job. Mars Rahuwala
It can also be a very good protector.
Mars Rahu is a very good destroyer.
It can also happen. So the understanding is that which
This is the conjunction or trine of Mars Rahu.
In what amount is it happening? If the amount is good
If it is, it will start working positively.
If the effect of the zodiac is more negative.
On top of both the planets, the result here
You will get to see that one is a destroyer.
You will get to see it as such. Court case
Things like Land Related Litigation
Mars will be seen in Rahu. or
You will get to see the house changing again and again.
Not being able to stay in one house,  out of the house.
Leave.
If Mars Rahu is one's third or sixth
If you are in the house, it shows you that the native.
There will be a lot of daring. It will be so daring that he
Establish more than one relationship
takes. So what causes your marital
Ah aware what causes marriage
There was a conflict. That's why Mars and Rahu conjunction
If in the seventh and sixth houses and in the 12th  house
Be in the third house. Mars in the 12th  house
If Rahu is there, then we call it a thief or
Bandit
Placement will happen because it is the 12th  house.
They show what is the secret and the expense is
is. The sixth house of the front is for him
It's theft. So Mars Rahu in the 12th house
If not, the native should be on top of his greed.
I should control that I am more greedy.
I don't. We see that if it is three 7 11
If you are inside the house, then the person is very much
Becomes possessive. Your relationship
Taking it in which he starts tying it
To your partner. Zero Level Satisfaction
Mars resides inside Rahu that you can do any
You won't be able to satisfy the situation.
Neither to myself nor to the other person. Then understand
Rahu is with Jupiter. Usually we
Have you read that this would have been Guru Chandal Yoga?
is.
Now it matters that the master is ahead of the degree
I or Rahu came in degrees. Meaning Guru
Whether Rahu is Rahu or Rahu is Guru, this matter is very important.
Does inside this placement. It's very
He will be a person who has exclusive devotion.
This native's attitude towards spiritualism
There will be a separate delusion. We see this knowledge
There will be a lot of hunger for it. i.e
This native personality like desire.
Desirable Personality for the Knowledge of the
Knowledge Higher Knowledge.
No doubt that such a person should not be able to get his higher education.
I want to see too many problems inside it.
You must have found it. Obscures were seen
There will be. Change of place to see again and again
You must have got it. A person with Jupiter Rahu is an exclusive person.
He can also be a devotee and the other is his devotee.
And also be an insulter to your father
Maybe. If Rahu's influence is too much.
Is it more than Jupiter or is it a good zodiac sign?
It is not.
Religion and Religion Spiritualism Moral
Ethics is a different philosophy
There is a kind of thinking. Time per time
Moral ethics can change. Time per time
They can also defame religion. Religion
There may also be a lot of believers.
Depends on the influence of Rahu here.
Is it more of Jupiter or Jupiter's of Rahu?
It's up. You just have to understand which ones it is.
The joke is happening inside the sign. Academic Hire
To see the blockages towards education
They meet. Guru called a living factor planet.
Gone is it. So as a living factor that your
Personality will be seen by people, it will be like this.
Why will it appear? People will say that you have too much.
Those who pretend to have any knowledge or
Of any devotion. Actually, it would have been like this
No, because Rahu shows that thing.
Rahu shows the reflection of what I said earlier
Your age as a living factor.
What the reflection will be is what matters.
Unconventional
Shows the path as a creature
This native to fulfill his ambition
One can choose the wrong path. where
But its moral ethics have been eclipsed.
That's how we see it. Confusion in one state
The native keeps the traditional values
Believe it or I accept my modern values.
Sure. This person will feel that one
The traditions that are coming from behind are ours.
We have a culture that we should follow.
But when modern values are modern times,
If you see there, there is a confusion one by one.
The duel goes on for the moral of this native.
Ethics is what I should do.
I believe in whom, I don't. This situation is very
It's good. If it is the center or triangle
If it is in and within a good amount
This in itself becomes the Raja Yoga factor.
If this conjunction of Jupiter Rahu gives you
Inside the good sign in the center triangle
Yes. I'm saying it again, Jardiak Sign.
There should be a lot. In which both these planets
To be able to work well. Like usually Sagittarius
Rahu was not said to be good in the zodiac.
But there Jupiter becomes stronger.
Therefore, the conjunction of Jupiter Rahu in Trine
Or if you are inside this zodiac sign in the center, then a lot
Good results are seen.
He is an extremely knowledgeable person. this
The placement shows that Rahu is not to the native.
Jupiter forces you to know
Have to take. You have all kinds of knowledge
You have to learn. You have all kinds of knowledge.
should. That must be required. That is, your
I would blame it on wisdom and ethics
Again and again. Therefore, the person does not know himself
It should be made. To understand his religion
It is popular and necessary. As long as this native
They won't understand knowledge. Don't understand religion
It has been. Your Moral Ethics is always
Damado will remain in position. And until it
The person is the personality of another human being or the other person.
A human character or another human being
Somewhere the knowledge is to blame.
What do we usually see? General I Joe
I see if someone has posted a video.
A lot of people comment on it.
As it would have been known from the comment of the person
What is the position of that planetary? what
Is this Jupiter sitting on Rahu? A Jupyter
Rahu will be so absorbed in his devotion
To the Guru, that is, to bow down to the Guru.
It will be. He has bowed his head
At their feet. And one of the gurus is Rahu.
The person who is proud of his knowledge
He will be so much about to say that he is his guru.
He will not be able to understand only the one who understands him.
He will use abusive language. both
Guru is Rahu. The only difference is that a human being
By reducing your ego to the living factor who
Planet Jupiter is the wisdom of the one who is not arrogant.
Understanding that he put down his knowledge that
There are probably more knowledgeable people than me. and
I'm the only person with Jupiter Rahu.
Hmm. I am the real knowable of knowledge.
I am a person. He blames his moral.
to ethics.
Therefore, the native is not misguided.
Because Rahu's instinct is not
Jupiter misguides Jupiter
Blames it. Now stay here
If you are with Saturn, then the natives are not in their own way.
Thinks about making the work bigger
Because what Saturn is is your karma.
The native increases his karma until
He won't think he'll live with a small idea.
That's okay, I've got so much work going on. I
I'm happy. Here Rahu is telling him that
You have to think big, do something big
Will be. Otherwise I will be in your profession
I'll give blockages. The profession of such a person
It is set there by going to a foreign land or
From the state in which it is born
Leaving and going to another state. The native himself
Not in a single insecurity within the profession
I wonder when my profession will be set.
But Saturn is not the same person as Rahu.
More than I've seen after 35 to 40
After that, the profession starts to set. Added to impart the meaning of ‘giver’ as  giver of water
The reason is there, he understands that I
You have to think about increasing your work.
As long as I think about the work on a small level,
My work will not increase.
Now here you understand in this way as we
Talked first.
The planet with which Rahu sits.
Captures the entire factor element of the planet
is. So there are two Saturn and two Rahu too.
Saturn is a kind of delay for you.
What is the factor? So, delay and Rahu are yours
Showing a flaw. Rahu is the one for you
Keeping inside the confusion state. at that time
Here is the success inside the profession of the native.
Will you see delay or success?
Because Saturn's job is to give.
He. Rahu who appeared a little obscure
It's  been a little bit misleading you,
He'll lift you up there for a while.
After when you are able to do your tasks
Very well worth understanding. This is the person
Don't pretend to be in your workplace
It falls. Because Rahu is an illusion
A pretentious planet that makes me like this
It has to be shown. So as long as this native does his work
One on the field, one of his own personalities.
He won't keep it even if he doesn't have zero work.
But my personality is such that I do a lot of work.
I am very knowledgeable. So even then, this person
Let's stabilize our profession.
There is always confusion related to career.
No doubt that the person is connected to the career
There is never a straight path.
He is always wandering about his career.
Therefore, the native does not get to see the struggle
is. Don't let this person have a self-doubt on himself.
There will always be someone who does one thing.
If he does karma, he checks it again and again.
is. Suppose I have swiveled mine.
I went back to the door. I'll come back and check.
I will. Did I stop or not? So this is a
Self-doubt that I did that
is. Whether it has been done properly or not. that
Rechecking shows the inside of the karma over and over again.
Eyes at work. Saturn is the karma of Rahu
If we look at what we call the most, then
Probably, the people who will be their
Whenever there is a photo of the work area
The native is also uploading them.
The blue eye that we call Nazar Batu
They must be putting in and we will be able to see this.
It is found that this person is not his own.
You should be so secure about karma.
It seems to happen again and again
Someone has done black magic on top of it.
These people are going to believe in that thing.
There will be. Saturn is usually inside the eighth house.
Rahu gives very good results and Rahu in the eighth house
It's kind of a factor. Now understand here
The native should not be very good in research.
should. As long as he's inside his work.
I won't do research. Anxiety in the eighth house,
It is of contemplation and contemplation. That is, you have to contemplate.
It has to be done. Reflections inside your profession
As long as you don't do it, you are in the profession.
Stability is not seen. Your
You don't have to understand the values of humanity.
You have to understand. Saturn is the one who is humanity
Reflect. Rahu is right there in the cruelty
Shows. If this person does not love humanity
If you understand, then spoil your karma.
It has been. It's ruining your profession
is. Therefore, the native should not engage in his karma
It should stay. Keeping Up with Humanity
should. Humanity is seen in the deeds of the native.
should. Gradually, the natives come at a time.
It becomes successful. Then we see
When Rahu is with Mercury. This is a
Extreme manpulation shows that
The native has a lot of power. that
Can manpulate anyone. This is a
Shows the mental restless personality
That Mercury is the significator of intellect. On Wed
It has also been said that the planet
The fruit will sit together in the same form as it is.
We will try to give. So when Mercury and Rahu
If they happen together, then this is too much.
Humans tend to think and over.
It becomes communicative. Very much so.
He is more talkative than he is.
Drains out of energy.
Sharps are intellectual. Mercury that is
He shows our academic education.
So, this person is not behind academic education.
There will be an escape and in the same you will
Blockages will also be seen. and Rahu
It shows the technology. Digitally
Shows marketing. So this person is in these
Receive education within both things as well.
Maybe. Whether you do coding digitally
You're at work in marketing. Where
Your communication plays too much role.
Let's do it. In general, this person is smart
There is an effort on the side and not hard work.
Side. It becomes an unconventional speech.
I think that the communications that you have are not
They get something out of their mouth that they
Conflicts arise. If that's what
Conventions inside your 10th or 3rd house
If so, it shows that the uncles who are there
They will have Emmanus Wealth. Mama's
The profession will be very good in such a way because
Mercury, which is there, also shows it to your uncle.
As far as the study will do, going abroad.
will. Study where you were born
It can't be. Academic Education
It will not be complete. Study abroad
Will you study or stay far away from home?
will. The native's neighbor will be the same.
NRI or any other religion or we can say
You will get to see it from another religion.
This person is not a general person who is interested in education.
A hunger personality will be seen that
He needs all kinds of knowledge. Just as long as
I will not take all kinds of knowledge
I won't find peace. Mercury, Moon, Rahu
Suppose if this is a conjunction then no
Centennial
Such a person is definitely a ditch inside a love relationship.
It happens. He would have been cheated on
It's a turn. Mercury is not as much as you are.
Say,
The more you communicate, the more you do it.
You're getting beaten. You need to communicate your
It has to be kept low. The more quiet you are, that is.
Where knowledge is being talked about
I am silent. This is very important.
Do you understand why this is so? Where of knowledge
I am silent there. There I
Shut up. Why is that? It has to be understood
You. Photography is memory. Generali
You may have heard what Mercury is? Memory.
What is Rahu? Photography digitally
Things are not of such natives, but of the natives.
Photography memory would have been much sharper
is. If there is any event, then it comes to mind.
A photo is hidden. So, I think so.
It seems like this has happened to me.
I think it happened to me
That's photography memory. Maybe one of the time.
But you click it and save it inside the memory.
Sometimes you have to stay in your data.
It is seen. And it shows that these people
Education like photography is also very good.
Maybe. General Mercury is the education of
Shows and Rahu who is your smoke
That is, it shows your smoking. be
It is possible that when this person sits down to study,
If you smoke, then his mind will run.
Many people must have tried that when
If we study, we have to apply it once.
is. We have to smoke.
This person is not a film line photography if it is.
Its education takes a very prominent form.
Rahu aligns here. Then we
Let's see that this person who takes online classes
As good as it can understand offline.
I can't understand that well. Because Mercury
It's education. Rahu is your online activities.
Showing. That is, if you want to
If you have Mercury in this, then you are mine.
You will be able to understand the matter very well. Radher
Give it to me if I write it down to you because
Mercury, Rahu, both of you are aligned.
They are also taking education. Rahu also
If you have aligned, then online education is for this person.
It's very good for you. Then we'll see
Rahu and Venus show luxury because
Venus which is luxury Rahu out of the box
Side. Now you have to understand it here.
You have to build yourself a brand. Only then will you
Venus will be able to attract you.
Venus is your female in the mail chart
Shows it to your partner. That is, which
Your partner will be over-ambitious.
She's a lot of luxury chasers.
There will be. And thankfully inside your chart it
Shows you a lot of luxury on your side
There will be attractants. Butt in what way
You have to build yourself a brand. As long as it
The native will not make himself a brand until then
This is not a settlement in the profession of the native.
There will be. This relationship will not be good. this
The native will be a chase of luxury.
What is Rahu? Rahu to your foreign land
Shows. Rahu shows off that pretentiousness
is. That is, you are wearing a watch. A watch
Worn. Not knowing the other person
How much watch do you need to wear? If it is
He saw the pretense and understood whether or not
That's 400.  It's 200. So here
Venus and Rahu blamed Venus.
That is, you  do not even have ₹1  in your bank. but
You should look like you're a millionaire. This Venus
There is a conjunction of Rahu. As long as it's not pretentious.
You will do Venus Rahu, somewhere you will down.
You will get to see. You don't attract
You'll find Venus on your side. Rahu says that
Think out of the box. And Venus says
That I am the factor of indulgence. i.e
I have so much indulgence in me now
That he also made more than one relationship
Can or am I in the same relationship so much?
I get loyal that I'm over with him.
I become ambitious, my partner.
with. What is the nature of the fact that this person is not a person?
You will get to see inside the situation that
It's going somewhere with your partner.
What will happen on the way? No one
There is a fight over something. Just Because
I had to take something off. He couldn't take it or
About something. The general who
There will be conflicts when it comes to each other.
When you are in the market, you will be able to see it.
See you. Venus always gives you big in Rahu.
Natives thinking about the house big car
I'll find that I have a very luxurious life.
should. I want a big car. My wife
That's how my husband should be. Meaning big
I want to go to the Car Foreign Country. me
You have to live the luxury life of a foreign country. Wherever.
Somewhere. This will make you look prominently
Get. Its best remedy just
One is that when the native makes himself a brand
Take it. There is just no other remedy for it. no
So you'll blame your planet. Emmons
Wealth will give. Very large fabric factory
Be the native. You perform very good acting.
The film should be related to the music.
It's that
Go and brand yourself. any
Brand yourself by going into the art of the genre
Take. If there are also inside the finance work
So finance should also have these brands
Look, it doesn't work any better.
When it comes, it seems that a Venus is coming.
It has been. It should seem so. Otherwise on Venus
Rahu will blame you. So try two
Sold a brand. I don't know by looking at you.
How much do you have, what you don't have?
is. Otherwise, Rahu will spoil everything.
So what we understood today, we didn't
I've tried to get a few points.
Due to lack of time, but it is very difficult.
Can be made bigger if you sit down to think.
Try to see each of your planets.
That he is from Rahu
Which constellation is also there? Which zodiac sign
It is also in the United States. Then there is also a lot of constellation in it.
There is a lot of role play that Rahu Kiss
In which constellation is that planet?
With which in the trine then inside it and
Can be deep landed. For now, we have just
This has been understood from above. Then make it even deeper.
Can be seen.
We'll talk about another session later. then
Thanks for that. Jai Shri Krishna. Jai
Mr. Ram.