Jai Shri Ram Jai Shri Krishna Welcome to Our
YouTube Channel Refine Vedic Astrology
Today's session is of our Saturn.
To understand the curvature when the planet Saturn is retrograde
What fruit  do all 12 give?
For the Ascendants. First of all, you understand this
What does retrograde mean?
What does retrogression mean?
Retrogression does not mean that a planet
Moving in backward motion. Curvature
What does it mean that Saturn is from the Sun?
The distance has become so much at this time that he is trying to
Give Your Fruits as Force
Interested. What is Pulective Force? For
Example: Suppose India is a Democratic
There is country. Everyone here has their own set of accounts.
Permission to operate. The one who
There is democracy, it is not available only then
When a planet is more than the Sun.
Goes over the distance. Then he retroged
It's called a planet. That is, the force of effort in it.
Too much is generated. Now the king
is. If the king goes to another country.
The people there or the people there.
Ministers are supposed to do things in their own way.
Try because the king's authority
It doesn't happen in that kingdom at that time. So that's the way
Retroplanets work when the Sun
Very much at a distance and near the planet
At this time, you have to give your full strength to the fruits
For. There will be no obstruction to its fruits.
This is called the force of action. The same
Or called retrograde planet.
are. That at this time this planet is, at this time
No one can give their fruits to this planet.
There will be no interruptions. It will also give it to the fruit
That which man wanted to do before, but do
I couldn't find it for some reason. Now I'm going to take those fruits.
I'm willing to give it too. That Retrograde Planet
explains. So when Saturn is retrograde
So first of all, they align your deeds.
Do that past karma that you have been doing for some time.
If you couldn't do it, then you wanted to do it.
Now the force of action increases in the mind. For
Exemplar if in the seventh house like Saturn
If you are going retrograde, you can
You will find that this is the behavior of your spouse.
Time will change. They Can Be Indulged in the
Spiritualism. They talk to more than one person.
Let's start meeting. That is, the relationship of saying
It is that the seventh house is that of meeting.
The seventh house is that of interaction. So over there
So much Saturn on top of the husband's mind.
The effect of the curvature will be that now he is less ahh
Too many people instead of speakers
You can be going to meet them. or Interaction
They can be with a lot of people. i.e
This is called the force of effort of the native.
Such a planet above the intellect and the mind.
The effect comes that he is afraid of her.
Not for that, he inspires him.
He makes you do this now so that you can do it. at that time
The same curvature for every 12 ascendants
What effect will it give or Saturn?
Retrograde is very good for which ascendant
Is it a little struggle for which ascendant?
Or a little bit on the side of the effort.
We may have to pay more attention.
We'll talk. So are Saturn who is retrograde
From 13 July 2025 to 28 November 2025
Retrograde will remain inside Pisces. Now Speak
What about all the 12 ascendants?
Saturn will have an impact. Planets like Saturn
When retrograde, one thing is for sure
Keep in mind that your actions are ahead of you.
It's a blueprint. Your actions are yours
It's a blueprint for the future. That's always the case.
Remember. Because in this effort the force did
It is the fruit of your actions that you have lost when they are curvated.
When it ends, you will see. Therefore this
In time, you will do some work, maybe someone
They will hide their deeds, but when Saturn's
If the curvature ends, the retrograde time ends.
The result that will be the result of those actions
Then they will not be enjoyable to you, so when Saturn
If the planets are retrograde, then their deeds
Needs a lot of attention
And you'll find a lot of people right now who have nettles.
If Saturn is inside Pisces in the chart, then
You will see that all these people at this time
Professionally very much in life
Changes are being seen in Saturn
There have been returns for these. That is 30  years
After 60 years, Saturn would return to that zodiac sign.
The zodiac sign in which he is in our birth chart
They are inside. i.e. Our Nettle Chart
(a) Calculate the value of the product. So whoever has Pisces
Saturn is in the natal chart for them
So much like a transformation.
Things will be watching. In Life
Some people will be relieved of the responsibility.
Liability will increase on some people. Through the
Job Change, Through the Marriage, Through the Child
Berth that a liability fell on you. one more
Saturn for those who  are 60  years old
The second is the return. They are responsible for it.
You must be liberated at this time.
You had to do it now. Now yours
Your old age is now Lord.
It is on the side of devotion. So you do not have your responsibility.
Having become free, she is now engaged in devotion to God.
So, the return of Saturn is many.
It brings a lot to people. most
It brings about a big change. So let's talk now.
For the natives of Aries Ascendant, that is Aries
For those who are Eris Ascendants of the Ascendant
Saturn transiting in the 12th  house
It's retro over there. Saturn which is
There would have been 10th Lord and 11th  Lord for them.
are. As you can see in the chart.
are. It tells you that first of all, you have your
Those who see the transformation professionally
Look inside things like profession.
You will see in your actions. You will find that
For a long time, if you have been in your job.
Were you trying to change or in the same job?
You wanted to change the field, you didn't do that.
They were finding. But now there is so much strength inside of you.
It has come that you can take this decision.
That is, the natives of Aries Ascendant have the highest number of their
You will see changes within the job or profession
Through their decision-taking power. Their
Ability to make decisions is very high at this time
increases. People who are still reading children
They can go abroad for fathers.
Study. Most of their travel involved
It will be in the profession at this time. because
Saturn will find your Capricorn sign which is their 10th sign
She comes to the house. From there to the third
Traveling and retrograde.
So inside things like a job or a profession
Inside the business, you will find that they have to travel.
It will take too much to do. Most of all now
These people will travel. And the same travel that
There is no more to their spiritualism.
Somewhere I will try to connect them.
Because  the 12th house is of spiritualism.
The 12th house belongs to NGOs. 12th House Charity
Of. Such natives are the most likely to be the natives of Aries ascendant.
More than you need at this time for charities, NGOs,
Spiritualism in organizations like these
You will get to see. It's not too much.
Deep inclusion gives that you don't yourself.
Start isolating. From others
Start separating. It may happen at this time.
is. Your imagination is a
Towards Spiritualism and Meditation
Get infected. The more you go deep inside it.
Start and this is what you need spiritually.
The travel side also shows that you
You can travel a lot more spiritually.
You may take a religious trip
And there you visit a religious place.
Do it because Saturn is sitting here on the 10th.
Let's look at the ninth house visually. Ninth
Emotion is our spiritualism. Nova Quote
Spiritual Travel, Ninth House Higher
Education. So that's why I said that.
Those who go abroad for higher education
If you want, you children can also go at this time.
are. And It Shows That Conflicts Will Be
Seen in the relationship with the spouse. Because of the
You will find that from the seventh house which is the sixth house,
He  is the 12th. That is, with the spouse
Some Conflicts to Watch in a Relationship
Can be found. Or you may find that the spouse
You will get to see health related issues.
At this time. Because the sixth house is the healing of diseases.
And the planet Saturn that is sitting there is also
Somewhere they cause disease. at that time
Planets like Saturn which belong to the natives of Aries Ascendant
They are retro in the 12th  house for
One thing that tells them is that they
If the spouse is inside the job, then there will be
They will get upliftment from but
It can affect health. If Health
If it is good, then their spouse inside the job.
There will be some conflicts. and
Now you'll find one thing in it, like that.
The  tenth house is the tenth house, that is the seventh house.
Fourth. And in which horoscope?
In the 12th. He went into the third of his own.
Went from seventh to sixth. You will find that
Husband's mother has health related issues
You can at this time. Because for them the seventh
The one who is fourth  is the 10th. that
I have gone to the 12th of the horoscope and from myself.
Gone to the third. Who is the mother of the husband
You can travel a lot at this time.
Face Some Health Related Issues. So for them
The best of all is that it is your spouse
You can tell your mother
To donate shade. Those who do it on Saturdays
We see the shade in mustard oil.
Let's do. It was given the name of Shadow
is. This happens by shading somewhere.
Somewhere we would have been a little bit of a charity.
is. A little bit of us at spiritual places.
Let's visit and in a little shade.
We have found that the negative aura of humans
Which is Saturn which is mustard oil when
When we look inside it, it is a negative aura.
Pulled up somewhere. So you can do this
You can do it and you will find it at this time.
At this time in your house in the east direction.
Things like resting iron or garbage
If it has been gathered, then it should be cleaned first of all.
Because when Saturn is retrograde and
Nowhere in the South East direction for you.
If they are transiting somewhere, then South East.
Direction gets its very clean
Need to keep for the Taurus at this time
Ascendant Saturn is transiting in there
11th House Now See Here Not Functional
Malefic and Functional Bull Ki Beneficial Planet
It is a very different role play. For the Taurus
Ascendant Saturn is his ninth and tenth house
They are the masters. And in Libra
For the natives, the 4th house and the 5th house for them
They are the masters of the senses. So here's their
It's not functional, it's functional.
Benfic is the planet. Meaning natural auspicious planet
This is for the ascendant. So never of this ascendant.
Undo not do where you will find it. at that time
The retrograde ones that are happening here at this time
You will generate multiple sources of income.
The 11th house is of income. 11th House Socialize
It is also meant to be. There may be many natives
Instead of socializing at this time, you should find yourself
Isolate. Why? Because of Saturn
The tenth vision that is coming here is
They are coming to their eighth house. and Saturn's
The dispositor is also somewhere in their eighth.
The lord of the house in his second house
Transiting. Jupiter shows this
That such a person does not make himself active socially.
Or don't involve yourself in social groups.
By doing this, he isolates himself.
Even after isolating himself, he has a lot to do with himself.
Does he make sources of wealth or his own?
Increases income. It Also Shows Is
Not your morals and ethics in transit
Most
Checks will be done. When it was Saturn retro
So here is the Lord of the Ninth House.
That is, retro is happening to you. Ninth
When the Lord of the House is retro, you
Find that on your moral and ethics you
How much more adamant it depends on
does. Because the Ninth House is our Moral
Ethics Higher Education belongs to the father. It shows that
Under what circumstances, how much strength do you have?
You have to adapt this situation to your own
Or you can adapt to this situation.
(a) So here are the moral and ethics of the native.
First of all, checks are done. And you can do this
You will find that what is your faith is not your moral
Ethics will grow more when you
You'll find out if what you thought was right or
You were able to do what you wanted. Tenth
The vision that is coming to the eighth house is this.
Shows that such a person can be like this
Do deeds that cannot be shown in society.
You can. It can be good and it can be
Bad. It's dependent on the natal chart that every
The ascendant would have its own planetary position
are. Where is the lord of the eighth house among them?
Inside the nettle chart, he will depend on the Taurus.
For Assent. Overall Saturn's which tenth
Drishti is coming to their eighth house. These
Even within fields such as the Research Occult
Incline can. Inside the Father's Job
You will come. Transfer can happen. and Father
There is a lot of travel involved in the job.
Maybe. Why? Because of the Ninth House.
The master is retro by going to the third of himself
It has been. The third house that is there somewhere.
Shows travel. Transformations
shows. This is because the third house
He sat in the 12th house  from his father on the 10th house.
Looking. That is, the Ninth Lord
is. The father of the father is the lord of the senses. Your
It has gone from third to third. Of your 11th house.
Went in. From there  to which 10th point of view?
Looking at the expression? On the eighth house. eighth
The house is the 12th  house for the father, which is
Shows The Changes in the Father Life
Struggle in the Father's Life and We Can Say the
Father Can Be Traveled Abroad
Are you too spiritually inclined?
Because  the 12th house is the house of spiritualism.
There is also.  The 12th house is also that of charity. 12th
There is also the sentiment of NGOs. In the 12th  House
There is a change of personality that the father
A lot of changes in your personality.
Got to see.
For the mother, you will see the fourth house from the mother.
Saturn in the eighth from which is retro
are. What are you mother about health related issues?
You can give a little. The most for the sleeping mother
A good remedy can be that you are a mother.
Go to a spiritualism place with
If you visit, it will be good for you.
It will be.
Now you see here that the natives of Taurus Ascendant
For Saturn has no more negative results for you.
No, they are giving positive results. That kiss
Kind of giving. Retro in the 11th  House
After this, take you towards isolation.
I'm going to give you more about yourself.
I will explain because the third vision from here
Coming up of the Ascendant. When Saturn's third
If the vision comes above any house, then Saturn
From there, we tell you that you have to
Efforts need to be put in. That is, you
There will be a lot of work on yourself at this time that you
Those who have not been able to work for a long time
This Saturn will be able to do it in retro. Many
People have to read a book. That at this time
You can read books. certain
Spiritualism
You can say that you can visit such a place.
Where to do it connected to spiritualism
It happened to be a relationship. So visit it there.
You can. You can go to a temple.
You can visit the temple. Meaning a long
Travel looks for them. But he long.
Travel brings fruitful results for them.
will come. Otherwise what if it is long?
If you don't travel, then you will see it.
Blockages from the Ninth Houses. To the father
The problem may be health related or
Change in your father's life. With Father
There may be malice in the relationship. Meaning that when
By you align the causative element of the Ninth House
I won't do it with my life till then.
Saturn for Taurus Ascendant here
They will cause mental agony. Because the third sight
From those who are looking at the Ascendant, who are the brain
You are looking at the mental agony there.
It is shown that the person is aggrieved. That anguish
When won't it happen? When you have a spiritualism
Will you go on a journey or hire yourself?
You will incline towards education.
Because the ninth house is also of higher education.
is. Upliftment to them on the field of work
You will get it because the lord of the tenth house is from yourself.
Gone to the second house and the 11th house of the horoscope
(a) Calculate the value of the product. It may be a little too much.
Wealth related to you is very modest.
There is a problem but give it just checking yours.
Moral ethics that I mentioned earlier. Now Speak
Let's talk about Gemine Ascendant.
Saturn is for the natives of Gemini Ascendant.
Transit at their tenth house
That they have the Eighth and Ninth Lords.
First of all, the profession for them.
It's time for a change.
Look at this because one of the eighth lords of the 10th
It is inside and it is also looking  at the 12th house.
Saturn is the first one to you at this time.
There will be a change in profession. otherwise
What will you find value in the profession?
The Loss of Humiliation, the Loss of Respect
Status Dropping If You Won't Change Job
That's why Saturn will inspire you here.
You have to change. If you don't change, humiliation
You will have to take a sip of it.
In many places, it can happen that people have their own
Profession as well as Change of Places
You can also see that they have a place too.
It has to change. Because whenever Saturn
Let's look at the 12th  house from the third point of view
Sitting in the tenth means a change in actions
And the change of place is the first thing to happen
Because  the 12th house is your loss.
shows. The 12th house represents a change
is. Either change your profession or change your
Change the place or change your deeds.
He is the Ninth Lord. Sitting in another of your
Yes, he is sitting in the state. So you're overly
Inclined in the Spiritualism Right Now.
That you are a little bit towards spiritualism.
You will have more attention. False Blame Is
At the time it may take that when Saturn is on the tenth house.
Your retro is happening which is the status
Shows the false blame on you there.
It can take place. When you feel blamed, you
The first thing to know is that your
Who is yours who is standing with you and yours?
Who is the stranger who is standing opposite you? at that time
Somewhere in this blame too, it is you.
The advantage is that you can filter that one ah.
Who is there for you in your life in your bad times?
Who else is standing for you ah the opposite side?
I stand in yours. Who is the mother of the husband
You may have more interference
Inside life, inside relationships. Why?
Because sitting in the tenth house with the tenth vision
Looking at the seventh house which
Shows the relationship with the spouse.
Whose house is the tenth house? Seventh to fourth
Which shows the spouse's mother. It
Can be the mother of your husband at this time.
Did you come home or because of your husband's mother?
Disputes arise within the relationship
For any reason. Now on the seventh house when
If Saturn's 10th aspect is coming, then this
Shows that inside your business at this time
Some changes in business, you are new
You can do a startup that you have been doing for a long time.
They weren't able to do it. It Shows That Spouse
They can start a new business together. Marriage
Proposal to come that if marriage has been done for a long time
If it is not happening then at this time of marriage.
Proposals start coming in. Fr. K
We can say a little bit about financial
Crunches may occur. A little bit of them
Financially
Ah, instability will be seen. speech
Harshness will be seen inside. Father's
You have a little bit of an ah-a in nature.
Irritability will be seen. Because the other
Expressions are retro for them.
The one who is second from the ninth falls the tenth. at that time
A slight change in your father's temperament.
You will get to see what shows that the father
There may be slight differences with it. Overall
Father Can Be Involved in the Spiritualism
Also. Because for them the 12th Lord
The lord is also sitting in the second house. So Father
Maybe Through the Investment Give Earn
Lots of wealth. They Can Get Something From
The Inheritance.
Overall if we look at the Gemininai sign for
Saturn is sitting in the tenth house for them.
Changes and new opportunities somewhere
Showing. For them, some of these people
The face that they used to think of will come out
But they are not actually their own.
Because the 10th aspect of Saturn which is the  seventh
Coming to the price. It's going to give you the front
Shows the real personality of a human being
What kind of personality is the person in front of you?
of. Now let's talk about cancer attendants
Saturn for Cancer Attendant
Transit to the Ninth House and
They have the Seventh Lord and the Eighth Lord.
So for the natives of Cancer Ascendant you will find
First of all, there are a lot of majors for them.
Changes will be seen in life. Father
There may be a slight dispute with
Because for you, the seventh and eighth house
The lord went into your ninth house.
Seventh Lord in the Ninth is fine, but
Eighth Lord in the Ninth It Shows That Some
Disputes will be seen with the Father.
The Father and the Guru are also like that because of the Ninth House.
It is also the guru's. Inclination towards them and
Your sense of spiritualism is high
There should be no hatred towards them. if
So your Ninth House Lord in the horoscope
If you are sitting well, then you are with the father and the guru.
You have a relationship that has become very good.
Maybe. But if somewhere in the ninth
House Lord is not good to you Nettle Chart
Inside then with your father and guru.
There are malices. Otherwise, what do you do?
Will you find? Saturn who is here in the Ninth House.
Retro inside. It gives you
Spiritualism, Philosophical,
On the other hand, your inclination is higher.
What does it do to the Majorly Impact? This is it, isn't it?
It affects your wealth. Why?
Because the lord of the eighth house comes in the second house.
Gone. Now let's see what happens here.
The lord of the eighth house is second to himself.
I got in. And what is the house he is looking at?
Looking at the 11th  house, looking at the 6th house
And from the seventh point of view, the third house
Watching. The third house is also wealth.
(a) What is the value of the product? Therefore, at this time, the native should have his
You have to put in a lot of effort. and
It is written in the classical text that the triangle
Planets retrograde in the U.S. are not considered auspicious.
One is for you in the eighth house.
There are masters. Marquesche is also in the seventh house
Swami who is the factor of Guru in the Ninth House
He sat down in the mood. Planets like Saturn
The native is as much his mentor as his father's mentor.
The more respect he will have in his heart, the more he will respect him.
When Saturn transits the 11th house from the third aspect.
Looking at the source of income from there
Increase. Teach to be social.
How is it socially? Such as those who are Cancer Ascendant
They are not able to be very social.
Because emotions don't have to dominate you.
Giving with others. So be social
They will teach. Such people socialize a lot.
It will be. But it also shows the seventh house
The owner of the retro going to the third
And looking at the sixth house from the tenth point of view.
is. Spouse's efforts are taken care of at this time
It is very important to keep that it is actually
What are you doing? He puts his efforts into it.
Where are inbuilt or outbuilt?
That is, the force of action has come. Spouse Now
The behavior of you will be a little bit
You will see the change that it can be.
Spouse not the person in front of you, whoever
He's trying to hide something from you.
Trying. I want to see you over there.
Needed. It Also Shows That You Can Uncover
The New Site and Approaches That You Missed In
The Direct Transit. You can use those things.
You can also think of something new that you
Haven't been able to do it for a long time or someone.
Because of responsibility, you could not do it.
So, this transit is retro, isn't it?
Transit of Saturn shows you that
Your belief system is not going to increase
Timings. That's because Saturn is the ninth house.
It's retro from here.
Looking at the 11th  house from the point of view which is
It shows that such a person is in his belief system.
But only when he is able to stand as much as he has to do with the sixth.
On the house that Saturn's tenth aspect comes
From there there has to be humiliation and that humiliation.
After he sees how I do for myself
New avenues have to be opened because Saturn's tenth
When the vision comes on the sixth house, it shows
Diseases can be affected by all these people.
is. Disease can occur. It could be Ripu.
That is, in front of someone for a loan.
I had to take money from the person. purpose
Different people who are different are shad ripu
Ninth House related will be seen.
But when will it trade positively? when
You can apply for your father's higher education or his
Your mindset remains positive per one
is. From there, you will again have a strong belief.
Okay I start moving the system
Stick to your moral ethics.
Whatever I did with the person in front of me.
He makes efforts, I helped him with that.
Try it. So, It'll Be Alone
Along with your chart. This is how it is inside the business
The native has to put in a lot of effort.
are. And they don't have travel plans.
Yes, they change dramatically.
Because of the Ninth House of Travel and also Saturn.
There are retros over there. So is there any travel?
If you make a plan, it will change immediately.
Either he will be delayed. Or have you done it before?
I had made a travel plan. He is at this time.
You can complete. But at this time, which ...
Will make a travel plan at this time?
Won't because Saturn when retro
So, he first completes the past karma.
Let's try. Saturn's tenth here.
The vision is coming to the sixth house. It shows
With your business partner or spouse
Legal Matters Legal Matters
You can. Because the 6th house is your legality.
It also shows. 6th House Disease, Ripu, Debt,
Debt, court case also shows these things
is. So if someone like that we could say.
If there is a divorce case going on, then here in it.
But you will find that you have to go again and again
It could be inside the courtroom. Not a date, but a
A few days later, their dates kept coming. at that time
Here the court shows the case. or
It can be with a business partner or with their
With the spouse.
Now let's talk about Lionant.
For Leonenton, let's first look at that.
What is the nature of Saturn? For the Leosendon.
Here the Sun and Saturn have no relationship with each other.
Haven't shown good ah, friendliness. By the way,
Saturn Sun is a son. But still
It has been shown that the Sun and Saturn are nowhere to be found.
There is a grudge somewhere. The sun is a bit ego
There are factors and the one who is Saturn is somewhere
They are discipline oriented. So both of them
There are slight differences. So the sun's
Saturn is the sixth sign for the zodiac sign Leo.
There are Lord and Seventh Lord, who are their
They are transiting in the eighth. Opposites
It shows that there is a Raja Yoga. 6th House
If the Lord goes to the VIII, then this one is his own.
It creates Raja Yoga in you. It Shows
Upliftment in the Eighth House Factor Element.
The eighth house is of your research. Your
Occult's. It is an investment. Personal
It is of growth. Meaning personal of such a person
How much can the growth be? That this eighth house
Because the eighth house is not a pain. that
Suffering is the change in the life of a human being.
You get to see. When he is in pain.
passes. Therefore, that pain is the eighth
When Saturn comes in the house, it removes that pain.
You have to treat a little bit like this.
That's Let It Be. Let it be. Anything
Nope. It had to happen. So get out of that pain.
Do what Saturn is sitting in the eighth house.
Retro is happening, that's your field of work.
But it will change your mental intellect.
Trying to make the most changes in
It will do because Saturn will sit here and do the fifth
They are taking a tenth look at the house. It Also
Shows That Challenge Will Come. Your Field of Work
There will be challenges. A place to be afraid of them
Use them as opportunities.
Because the eighth house is transformation.
Of. Saturn is the 10th from the third point of view.
Seeing the expression. So karma
You will find a lot of different areas on the field.
There will be types of opportunities. May
Some people are trying to harm your status too.
Try it. But the same status is
Your when you look at them as opportunities
Would have taken the same status would have uplifted you.
It will go.
Try that towards financial matters.
You take a long-term goal, not a short one.
You have to take a shortcut to the term. Shortcuts
Don't think about making money through. Here
Let's take a long-term investment.
Such people do not have many mystical things.
They will be involved inside. Like Sadhana,
Tantric Kriya, Astrology, Mantra
Sadhana. Because the tenth sight which is the fifth house
Coming on. The fifth house is that of mantra sadhana
And the eighth house is that of tantric activities.
is. Astrology. Cult's. peacock
Over The People Can Indus If Nettle Mars Here
But there are many sitting in someone's chart.
People moved into software engineering
Will go. In this case, software engineering
The natives should get a job inside.
Here's where your spouse may have to
You generate very good wealth. Here's it.
This is because the lord of the seventh house is his
It is transiting the rate from the second price to the other price.
And there's retro over there. So the spouse's
A little bit in financial matters
Upliftment can be seen which is
They can also help you. Majorly Changes
In the Profession and in the Spouse Family Will
B. Seen. People who are in consultation work
Or you will come into the teaching profession
They will get a very good uplift.
Because the fifth house is of no knowledge and
The eighth house is the eighth house of renunciation and giving.
How much can you ever give?
Because in the eighth house, inheritance will give you
And in the eighth house when the seventh house
The lord of the sixth house and the lord of the sixth house comes
So how much can you give to another person?
Depends on it. So those who consult
Or are you in a profession like teaching?
You can give people such good knowledge.
Depends on your Karaka Element VIII
Saturn is sitting at this time, which is showing Saturn.
Which are retro here. So try to be in
The Positive State and give it according to this sentiment
That I have to give it up. To give my work
is. Transformation Will Be Seen in the
Routine. Routine will not be the same now. as
The sixth house is now in the eighth house and the sixth house
K  is the 12th fifth house. 6th to 12th
There is a fifth house on which Saturn's Dashami
The vision is coming from the eighth house, so the routine
There was still a going on inside that routine.
Change will be seen, that routine is not the same.
And you will have a lot of time with your routine.
If you are bored with it, then change it for a long time.
If you were thinking of a change in routine here.
You will get to see that you talk at this time.
Saturn for Virgo Ascendant of Virgo Ascendant
It is retro inside their seventh house.
Which shows that with Virgo Ascendant
Saturn is the lord of a fifth house
They are the lords of the sixth house
Which is in transit within the seventh house.
Retro is happening. It's not on the show of you.
Workload may be high at home
You have to do a lot of work from home
Or do too much housework. if
Are you in a business like real estate or
You are in a business like vehicle sale purchase
So there's an upliftment to be seen.
(a) Yes, Sir. But above the psyche which is Saturn's
The tenth vision is coming from the seventh house.
Sitting in it shows that the front
Humans don't have too much influence at this time.
It will fall on your mind. You need people like that.
What you will find is spiritualism, spirituality
You can incline it to the other side. Their Mind
This is the retrogate of Saturn
Or a positive return of their force of action.
That which connects you towards the spirit of service.
Will try because the lord of the sixth house
Inside the seventh house other than yourself
It's retro. When you are in front of the people
If you meet them at this time,
Listening is very important to you.
Will try to find out which are your anime or
Your colleagues are somewhere in your status.
Neither can harm anywhere because the seventh house
There is a tenth to a tenth which is your social
Shows the status. You will find that this
Time can be too spiritual for you
Because Saturn's third aspect is
Coming to the Ninth House which
Shows spiritualism. Higher
It shows education. Your Moral Ethics
(a) Calculate the value of the product. So the person in front of you
You will find that your morals and ethics will be fulfilled.
Shock can occur. But it depends on you.
How much do you stick to your moral ethic?
Explore New Opportunities in Business
Can you get another job inside the job?
Promotions can be seen. because
The lord of the 6th house in the 2nd house
Gone. There's retro and even.
Inside the zodiac is retro. i.e. Joe
It also has lords, who are dispositors, that
Transit in your 10th house only.
are. Jupiter that is if they are trying for
A loan, at this time, they don't even have a loan anywhere.
It can be found somewhere very easily. End
Marriage Event Can Also Be Happened In This
Retrogression.
Because retro in the seventh house when Saturn happened
Those who show things like marriage.
are. Marriage is the most important of those natives.
You will get to see more of whose Saturn
Is the condition going on or is the condition of Jupiter going on?
Or the Antardasha is coming from Saturn or Jupiter.
There should be an event like their marriage in it.
You can get to see it. Just Mark One
Thing Focus on Your Business Partner &
Spouse activities. When it is Saturn's
When the retrogation is over, you will get a
The result will be seen in front. So that's why
Your attention to their activities at this time
It is very important to keep. Because Saturn
Retro is happening inside the seventh house.
Trying to Inflict a Stroke on Your Mind
Will do. I remember that trauma for the rest of your life.
Yes, I will have to give the person in front of me.
How to understand? I think about him.
was. What exactly is it? So when Saturn
If there are atros inside the seventh house, then your
Don't see the real face of the person in front of you.
Do you know if he's actually there? go to sleep
Try to See the Activities of the Other Person.
There should be a struggling period for the first child
Because the lord of the fifth house is his
It is retro in the 3rd house. go to sleep
Education will be a struggling period for them
You have to see blockages inside a little
You can find it. Putting in a little more effort
You will have to. At this time with your offspring
Too much time should be spent.
If you have time with your child at this time
If you don't spend it, then the fifth house is the intellect
Neither is it treating you negatively somewhere.
It will start happening. The fifth house is also of the child.
is. The fifth house is also of mantra sadhana. fifth
The feeling is of your entertainment that
Entertainment, you are the person in front of you at this time.
(a) Calculate the value of the product. A little with your baby
Spend your time. Towards Mantra Sadhana
Pay more attention to what you are in front of.
Chant with people or do their
With a Spiritualism
Or a long journey of a spirituality
You can do it. Now let's talk about the
Libra Ascendant. For Libra Ascendant
Saturn is always a Yogakaraka because the Fourth
Lord and Fifth are Lords. And here
But they have come inside the sixth house. So it's
Shows that Mother Can Have Some Health Issues
And a little bit on top of the domestic piece.
Violations will be seen. Because of the fourth house
Swami is retro by going to the third from himself
It has been. Getting retro inside the 6th house
is. This shows that Saturn is the third here.
Looking at the eighth house from the point of view which is
It shows that such a person does many such things.
At this time it will be included that such as
Take money from the person in front of you,
Get insurance at this time. May
It is that you take a loan from someone. At this time he
Unable to repay. Astrological-like
Getting involved in things, like an occult
In things, in things like research,
Inheritance to your spouse
Something can be found. These things to see
See you. As much as you are in a job at this time
You will see your transformation as much as you can.
Transformation you've never seen before
It will be because the sixth house represents the job.
If you are currently in a job, then this time change
Of. It's time for transfers. this time
You may get to see a transfer
Because Saturn is third from the tenth point of view today.
Looking at the house from the fourth
It is 12th. That means you can go away from home.
are. There can be a transfer somewhere. Social
In activities like these, you can do a little bit of media
There may be more indulgences because the third
The feeling is also to be socially active
That's because you have the sense of the desire triangle. 3
7 is 11 . This is the sense of the desire triangle. this
There is a sense of interaction. Seventh House You
Let's meet physically. The 3rd and 11th houses that
Is that somewhere you are in front of you socially?
Let's meet humans. It also shows that you
Some such bad habits or bad companies are called this
You can skip time. What is your karma first?
It was paused. You are suffering from a bad habit.
This is a very good time to get rid of that bad habit.
I want to leave because Saturn is here for you.
At this time, you will make your intellect like this because
The fifth house is ruled and the fourth house is ruled by the fourth house
He also made both the mind and the intellect like this
You'll give a bad habit to a bad company.
You can leave. If there is a litigation case
Or a court case is going on against you very little.
If you have a chance to win, then try to do that.
Compromise externally because
The 12th house is the fifth of the sixth.
And he's transiting to the sixth, seventh.
The fifth is the desire of the person in front of him.
Therefore, his wish will be fulfilled quickly.
Otherwise, not you, so try to ...
Compromise outside if anyone
There is a court case, litigation case is going on.
Overall, if seen, then which is of Libra Ascendant.
The natives are for their spouses who
Is it investment or foreign land abroad?
There is a lot of gains from there. De Can
Be very spiritual at this time that you
You'll find that he's too much spiritualism.
Be it. Because Saturn is here from the seventh.
The 12th house is the sixth house. Sit down from here.
The tenth sight that is being cast on the third house
That's the moral wisdom of your spouse.
Shows spiritualism. So your
Spouses who are too spiritualistic
They may be inclined at this time. That
Will be very good for your health also. that
It will protect your health.
Somewhere. Now let's talk about Scorpio Ascendant
About. For Scorpio Ascendant Natives
Saturn is his third house Lord and Fourth.
The house lord is his fifth house.
They are transiting inside. So most
First of all, it's nothing related to your stomach.
It can show the disease or
Constipation is something like appendicitis.
Know if Rahu planet is also your natal chart
If I am inside the fifth house here, then the stone
It shows the disease. It Also Shows
That travel will be involved in the education.
If you are a student and are still studying,
Travel will be a bit more involved
Inside Education. Professions like teaching
Inside or who is a professor, no extras
Classes give it as a business
If you do it in the case, then uplift them there.
You will get to see. Good Wealth From There
Can generate. Here in the fifth house
If you are getting retro inside, then your intellect
I would not like to study that subject.
You have been thinking of studying the subject for a long time.
were. But I couldn't read. spell
There will be more attention towards spiritual practice because
The Third Lord came in the V, not the Third Lord
The one who has gone into the third of his and
If he comes in the fifth of the horoscope, then such a person
The mantra becomes grasped towards sadhana that
I have to do the efforts of mantra sadhana.
Seems to be the causative elements of the fifth house
In Education Entertainment Speculative
Making money from markets like stocks
Getting involved in things like the market.
The significator of the fifth house, the whole of Saturn.
At this time, you take control of yourself from here.
The tenth sight that is on your second house
Let's put it. It Also Shows That Can It Can.
Be Happened That One Member Will Be Added In The
Your Family. It can be through your marriage. It
Can Be Through the Child Birth. But Childe
There will definitely be a slight delay in the berth. Over here
It will happen, but it will definitely happen. Because Saturn is
Not a dinner. It's a delay. That delay
does. Dinai doesn't. Majorly
Changes to see you in a relationship
See you. You will see that in business
You were in a business and from there you now have to
Something had to be transformed. Moving from there
Got from business. It Also Shows That Your Mother
Can help you financially. Why? because
The lord of the fourth house is called the mother house
It is the feeling of the mother. He is in another than himself.
It is in the fifth house. And sit down from there.
Your money house is looking at the second house. who
That shows Mother Can Help You. Someone you
Purchase the property for sale. From there
You get the money. Sale Purchase of a Car
Do. You get money from there. Meaning fourth
With the factors of emotion, you will be financially benefited.
Gain can be found. It Will Impact Your
Speculative Investment. Don't Take
Risk. You can find yourself inside the speculative market.
There will be indulgences. Because the fifth house is the same.
It's of things. But looking at you here, you
There is a need to invest. Otherwise, it is a loss.
Maybe. Because from the fifth to the 12th
He's transiting to the fifth.
Why? Because the fourth house is from the fifth house.
It is 12th. Fifth House Speculative
It belongs to the market. So when it has Saturn in it.
The planet comes in second and  the 12th.
If the lord of the house comes in the fifth house, then it is
Shows that the native comes inside this market
So is the mutual fund speculative market.
Bitcoin comes in with things like these
But until the loss is eaten up there.
This retrogression of Saturn will end. go to sleep
Don't take the risk where you are.
Invest and you can incur losses.
Saturn's transit for Scorpio Lagan
It's the people in front of them and their
To have a little control over speech
Tell me if you want to read something.
For that, you have to look at the person in front of you.
Don't depend on him to bring you something.
Give. Don't depend on your family
It has to be. You have to help your family.
Isn't it that your family will help you?
So at this time to understand your obligation
Saturn will act in such a way that on their intellect
It can make me understand my responsibility.
There is work to be done. Now let's talk about Sagittarius Ascendant
About. For the Sagittarius Ascendant
Saturn is the lord of their second house and
The lord of the third house is the one who
Transiting in the 4th house of the horoscope
are. And their disposer is the seventh
They are transiting in the house. Saturn's
Dispositors. So, it shows that you have whatever you want.
No, a laziness on top of it, a heaviness.
Go. A mind will be very heavy on the mind.
There may be a little bit of negative thought like the mind
Come in. Because Trishadaya Bhava is third
The lord of emotion is transiting over the mind.
The third house is Trishadaya Bhava and Upacha
There is also emotion. It can be done. Be it
It may be that
Your mother is suffering from health related issues.
A Towards Passing or Mother Spiritualism
Their inclination should increase or they should be one by one.
Can travel from state to state
Because the 12th from the fourth  is the third.
The house which falls in Aquarius is the fourth house.
I am transiting and there
Retro that shows the mother
The lord of the 12th  house for the mother is  the ascendant.
It is transiting inside the mother's
For. So  from the 12th house, all the factors which are
He is the intellect of the mother and the intellect of the mother.
You will start to see in personality. this
Time can grow on you a lot of burden.
Overworkload. Because here ...
They sit and look at the ascendant from the tenth point of view
Saturn and looking at the 6th house from the third point of view
are. Too much workload inside the work
Go. And it also shows that you can have that.
Your spouse will have upliftment in the
Profession. Travel Will Be Seen With The F.
Why? Why? Because of the second house
The lord has come to the third from himself. third
The emotion shows travel. 2nd House
The owner is transiting to the fourth. Saturn
Retro to family with you a long
You can go for travel or short travel.
are. The more you will keep the spirit of service, the more you will keep it.
Health and finance will increase. Because Saturn
From here, sit down and take the third sight of the sixth house.
Watching from . That is, your efforts are like this.
You need to be of service to other people.
You can. Whether you do as a charity, whether you
Do it physically. You should do that. the same
The thing is your finances, wealth and health, your
The health of the help will keep all of them well. Lots of
Efforts will be seen in the job. Because the sixth
There is also a sense of a job. So inside the job, you will get this
Time Saturn will tell you that you need to put in the effort.
There are needs. Want to change within the job
You can change that too. Such a person digitally
Becomes very active. because
The third house is in the fourth house for them.
Transiting. Which is the third house.
Shows things like digitally. Ahhh
Can Be More Active in the Like Meditation,
Inside things like Yoga Content These
We will add more to ourselves that we are in these
We can devote time to things like where we
Learn spiritualism. Meditation,
Learn things like yoga. More Over
The Time Wealth and Family Will Be Surrounded
On Your Psyche. That will remain above your mind.
Family, Wealth, Family, Wealth. Just me
These are the things that have to be handled now because
This is your responsibility to teach Saturn at this time.
Wanting. You Can Put More Efforts in the
Home Decoration. You can use the things in the house or
Lots of home décor items
You can spend more,  you can spend more.
are. So, Saturn for Sagittarius Ascendant Overall
Transit is very good. Just keep this in mind
That is the spirit of service for you, your efforts.
(a) Calculate the value of the product. As much as you spirit service
The more you will keep the disease loan from all this.
They won't get sick quickly or quickly.
Won't come into effect and the tenth vision that
Coming to the Ascendant she is showing you this
Don't desire the fruit of doing that work.
Keep that in mind, now let's talk about Capricorn.
About the Ascendant For the Capricorn
Affendant Saturn is their Lord 10th Ah
Sorry First Lord and Second Lord
Transiting in the Third Lord and over there
Retro is happening. So first of all, it's
Shows that Saturn is not retro here.
Shows what the desire is? If there is a desire
If there is a desire to do any work if charity
Don't desire the fruit of doing what you want to do.
Desiring for the fruit after doing the deed, i.e.
Shows you the way to increase greed. at that time
First of all, for the Capricorn Ascendant
You have to perform actions at this time. He doesn't want to.
I have to do what I will get.
in. Saturn sits here from the third point of view
Let's look at the fifth house to see if there is such a person
Could they more overly involved in the
Entertainment Movies Mantra Sadhana Hobbies Apni
Spending more time with your first child
More in things like love relationships
To be inclined means to be Capricorn here.
Such an effect on the intellect of the natives of the Ascendant
What is the time of your hobbies or your
He was not able to give time to entertainment
Now it will start giving or where it is.
Wanted to make efforts there
If you were not able to do it, then this back there too.
If you go on a date and check that I
Where do I want to give time to my desire?
was. I want to fulfill my wish.
was. We will fulfill that desire because these
Transit Inside the Desire Triangle for These
are doing. Because of the desire triangle
The first house is the third house. You'll Gate
The Gains from the Speculative Market
The Investment. Why? Because Dhanesh who
The lord of the second house is your Saturn.
Sitting in the third house means the house of wealth.
Swami sits in the fifth house of wealth
Shows the speculative market. 12th House
Shows investment. Because Saturn
Look at the 12th  house from the 10th point of view.
There are. So Travel Will Be More In More
Gains from the Involved Speculative Market
Be there. You Can Buy A New Car And New
House Also. Why? Because the fifth
There is a bank balance in the fourth house.
The fourth house has a whole sum that is the fourth house.
Things happen in the house of their bank balance
Addition and subtraction is all the fifth house. So this native
You can buy a car. They Can Buy a House
They Can Buy Anything for Their House. Some houses
But anything like decoration
Can buy. These guys. You don't have to do it at this time.
Keeping Patience Within Your Pay Efforts
Needed. Why? Because what you do is your
I want to complete my wishes. Saturn
Sit there and have retro. In the Third House
Inside the Third House Karma Desire This Place
But it's retro but Saturn's
The basic principle of discipline is that
You have to be discipline-oriented.
To the Efforts.
You can spend a lot of expenses at this time
Inside online activities because the third
There is also the sense of things like online digitalization
And sitting from here looking at the 12th house.
From the tenth point of view that is in your deeds
One of the strengths that will increase will be that
More in online activities
Can I spend or invest the money?
I can do things like that. Because the 12th
The feeling is not of your imagination and
The fifth house is that of the intellect. When these two
Vision comes over the houses like Saturn
If you do the planet, then you start imagining something like this.
Inside the intellect that goes into your desires
I was there before, but now I fulfill my wish.
Couldn't. So when Saturn is retro here
So you are letting go of those old desires of yours.
This time can accomplish what you never accomplish
Wanted to.
Such people do a lot of new things.
They can be inclined towards reading.
Reading new books,  new topics
Reading, learning something new that you spend a lot of time doing
I wanted to learn from it. You Can Also Indulge
In the NGOs, Charity Firms,
Spiritualism,
Doing yoga, meditating. You are in such a place.
You can also visit where these things are
You are taught. But one thing to keep in mind
Keep Saturn here to teach you this
Saturn in the 3rd house which is retro
That paperwork is there whenever you're doing it.
But you have to sign any paper without reading it.
Don't do it. Otherwise, with you over there.
It can be deceiving. The third house that is yours
Also shows the paperwork. Third House
Your Efforts Third House Your Hand
shows. So When You're Signing
Someone and some other documents so try to
Read that document first. You should first find that
The document needs to be read.
Now let's talk about the natives of Saturn Aquarius Ascendant
For those who are transiting their others
Transit in the house and there
Retro is happening. Saturn is here on 12th.
Lord and Lagan are lords who are the other
Going to be retro in spirit. go to sleep
First of all, your speech is very
It should be discipline oriented. somewhat like thi
Don't say that with the person in front of you.
Be it malice or the actions of the person in front of you.
It has a huge impact on the region.
You demotivate someone so much that in front of you.
The person in front of me can't work.
Too much influence on the human mind
Too much influence on the intellect
Read. Why do I say this? because
Saturn sits from here and takes your third view.
Let's look at the fourth house. But the fourth house
Falls from seventh to 10th . That is, in front
The karmic field of the person and Saturn here
Sitting from  the 10th to  the 11th house
Let's see. Which is seventh to fifth.
is. The 11th house means the opposite one.
Your intellect means your voice.
It should be reflected in the sanskars that in front of you.
The person who is motivated by you is not that you are them.
Demotivate. It's the Time to Know Your
Family Lineage. Because the second house
It is of the sacraments. 2nd House Family Lenses
It is also of . So Saturn is here when it was retro.
If you are such a person, then understand your lineage.
Guess what. Visiting Homeland. Where
You can visit the land of your ancestors.
Can. Where you have your elder
Too much for the elderly to know
Excited will be seen above your mind
That you want to know that my elder
How were the elderly?
You Can Put More Efforts for the Gain For
Wealth Making Activities. Be socially active
Go. Don't see you here at this time.
You will have to struggle to lose your money and
How to save routines. Because one is the 12th.
Lord Jahan to your money quote
There are. Retro is happening. The amount itself is
of Saturn. If you are a Capricorn, then how is the money?
To save? How to Orient Your Routine
It has to be made. How to Routinely Orient Yourself
Want to make? Spend a lot of your time there.
It will be. Because the 11th house is the 6th house.
It is sixth and Saturn's 10th here.
The vision is coming that means that you are doing your deeds.
How are you tying it in the routine?
It's very important. By the way, of the Aquarius Ascendant
Natives who are very socially active
There are humans. So at this time Saturn is here.
They will also tell them to be socially active.
And as a charity inside Good Deeds
What a difference it makes to work. You Have
A good amount of wealth. Try to use that
Money Age in the Charity. You are the person in front of you.
Can you help? This good karma is not anywhere.
Somewhere there is a law in your karma
in. You have to pay for foreign or investment.
Profits are being made. So try that.
Profit or investment as charity
You can use it somewhere. Why?
Because the eighth from the seventh is the second.
It does. The pain of the person in front of you
That. If in that pain you are in your 12th house
The profits that you are getting from that
People in front of them use it for pain
For a human being, what is your 12th house?
Somewhere it gets aligned, which you
Shows that you may have to be hospitalized.
Is there any wrong deed that goes to jail?
It protects you from what you have to do.
Therefore, from the 12th house that is coming to you,
Whether it's the imagination you're thinking about. that
Through Thought, you can bring that thought into your actions.
So that the person in front of you
Pain can be reduced. So that's your automatic
Saturn aligns you here that
You also did charity. You need to see something wrong.
Didn't even get it. You are social, you are not wrong.
done. Otherwise, what will happen is that you are doing something socially?
You will do something wrong that will ruin your status.
Can cause harm. People who have
There was no job for the people of Aquarius Ascendant.
So this time it is very good for them for the job.
Retrogression is taking place. That's because
who
Now look at it carefully from the sixth to the
The 11th house is the fourth house. i.e
Job's desire is there, Saturn's third sight
It is coming to the fourth house. From the sixth to the sixth
He  falls 11th. There is Saturn's 10th.
The vision is coming. From the sixth to the ninth, there
But Saturn himself is sitting on the fate of the job. It
Means job opportunities will increase. Job
If you want to make some changes, then
He will be able to change. If there was no job, then the job.
You will get an opportunity. It Will Depend on Yours
Karma that you do socially more yourself
Are you able to keep it active or do you keep your karma law?
Can you understand that this time is my job?
This is the time to do my work. go to sleep
The people who will understand this thing will understand it on their own.
Will you inline in the job or service?
We will incline towards the spirit. because
The sixth house is also the spirit of service. 6th House
It also shows your service. Let's talk now
Saturn is there for the natives of Pisces Ascendant
They are transiting in their ascendant and
That's where it's getting retro. So it's
Shows that the native is not on this time.
The burden of expenses will be very high.
Expenses can be very high. It Also
Show That Native Also Can Have Multiple Sources
Off Income. Multiple sources of income become
to generate. Because 11th and 12th
Both of them become Saturn, which is their
Transiting in the Ascendant and Retro
It is happening. Such a person may have an inclination
That I can go abroad and settle down or.
He went abroad for his wealth.
Create different sources. Because the 12th
There is a sense of that somewhere in a foreign land.
shows. Shows spiritualism.
It shows you a sense of how you feel that you are in that
They can serve the people by connecting with the spirit.
Because it falls from the seventh. secondly
The spirit of service to the people you will find that you
You will find people who want to serve.
They want to serve and they want to serve you.
Taking advice. It also shows that other
People take money from you and go away at this time.
Do not return. Why? Because for those who
The sixth house is from the seventh to the sixth, where
Your Aquarius sign, Saturn in the ascendant
Transiting. Getting retro
There, the person in front of whom is the loan from?
Will take? Will take from you. I took money from you.
Will go and don't give back. Will it happen or will you?
Helping others as a charity yourself
Do it. This transit, this retrogression, you
Age A will give very good results in the form of service.
You need to do any online activities or any
If you want to sign the document digitally nowadays
Also, as we sign, there is a big one.
Needs attention. Otherwise, there ...
There may be a fraud or from there your
Account bank balance can be emptied
is. Why are you saying this? Because today's
In today's era in the field, such as scammers work
Do it through online activities or
You click a link online. there
Money disappears from your bank. at that time
Why might this be? Because Saturn is here.
But looking at the third house from the third point of view
What are the online activities,
Things like document sign in
shows. So try any paper.
Read and sign it. You'll Put
More Efforts. You can use all your
You will try to put in your efforts.
Wealth and your spiritualism or your jo
You have imagination to fulfill it.
You can put in all the efforts. Because the third house
Efforts are there and  the 12th house is yours.
Imagination is what you only think about
They are not able to complete. So at this time Saturn
Give you time to do what you're thinking.
We can fulfill that thought. Otherwise, what
Will it? You may find yourself depressed or anxious.
You incline towards isolation
You will start living alone.
Otherwise, what should you do? At this time, you
Socialize and interact with other people.
By sharing the idea and working on it, you can
A very good name can earn respect. this
time
Health related issues are rarely seen
You can. The best remedy is this.
Because  if the 12th Lord is in the ascendant, then health
A little bit of the
Trying to trade you negatively
is. You go to the hospital. Go there
If a poor man is visible or someone is his
Can't take medicine or anything for it
Give something as a charity from your side
Give medicine. What will happen to that? Your number 12th
The house will be aligned. What makes you suffer from your illness?
You had to spend money on top of that.
Donated as charity and medicines
It was spent on it. So, that's your good.
Karma joined. The 12th House Aligned and
The 11th House also aligned. Because where
Money  came from the 11th house from that 12th
Put inside the house. Your health too
Safe, wealth is also safe. So the best remedy
This is when  the 11th Lord and the 12th Lord in
The Lagan Shani to Remedy in Hospital
Go and do charity as a remedy. one
Keep in mind that your not at this time
There will be a major identity loss. Passion We Ourselves
And there is the lord of the 12th  house.
Individually within the personality
Changes are seen. So who at this time
Will you change?
What will change for you at this time will be yours.
Spiritualism and that gives you the Society's
Inside will give you a different perspective that you like
You weren't what people would call you.
The change in personality that will take place because Saturn
He has a nature that changes it. any
They change the color of the thing. It's iron, isn't it?
You have seen the iron heated to the mold by heating the iron.
You can create anything. Similarly, Saturn
Warming you up from bad times
To change your personality. if
In this retrogression at this time in life
Do you see some truths?
People hate you. to you
If you are cheating
Thank you Shani Dev for that.
You have been taught this in retrogression that
What is the true personality of a human being?
And that's what makes your personality.
It is very helpful to change that
Time will make you bold. Then when someone
When bad times come, you fight through that bad time.
Always stand for.
Your engagement towards spiritualism is very much
It's more important. Joining Charity
Essential. Otherwise, you either go to a foreign country.
Will go. Can you generate something through foreign land?
You can make wealth. Otherwise, you are not going to be able to do so.
Negative, depression,  your attitude towards these things
The thought system will continue. For the Pisis
Ascendant, I would say that at this time your
First of all, your own personality is
Change. By hook by crook whether you are in front of
In return for being cheated by a person or
Understand what he's trying to do
And why do I need to change? As long as I
If I stay like this, then I will get its results.
Trades will be found negatively. Negatively
See you. You will not find it in a positive form.
So what we talked about Saturn Retro all
Very small points for the 12 Ascendants
Just small points that have been decoded
I can say a big thing. So that's why it can be
Listen carefully to this video. This session
The motive was that retrogression meant the previous
You never have to give the fruit of your feelings.
Retrogression means the emotion that
I am sitting in the full fruits of that feeling.
I'll give it to you. They can also be positive,
It can also be negative. It will depend on that.
What is the relation of Saturn with your Ascendant?
Pancham is the lord of the house of the triangle center
So you get better results.
But if N is the lord of 8, 12  house, then
To see a little negative result there.
See you. Like Cancer and Leo Ascendant
Eighth and Seventh House for Natives
He is the lord of the sixth house and the lord of the sixth house
(a) Calculate the value of the product. So here they have negative results.
You get to see a few. So for these
The best remedy is Let It Be. who
I am absolutely sure that what is happening
It would be right. When this thought system of the brain
If you bring it inside, then somewhere in the horoscope
Inside or inside your chart, you don't have Saturn and
You will align Ketu because Shani karma
Hey Ketu let it be I have my work karma
I will do if Saturn Ketu in the chart.
What is happening to you?
Let it be because Saturn and Ketu give you this
We want to teach that according to the times.
How is it changed and this work of Shani Ketu
Don't desire the fruits of doing that work, Saturn.
Ketu renounces desire and works to escape.
are. So if Saturn Ketu in your natal chart
If you are together in any sense, then perform actions
Don't desire the fruit. And if Saturn and Rahu are there, then
Think of increasing karma, not decreasing it.
Think. Because Saturn is karma and Rahu
There is expense. Means Rahu which is Amplified
Let's do it. Think of increasing your actions.
I have to grow up. Don't do anything trivial
Think. So this is the curvature of Saturn.
Planet Saturn is retrograde, that's all in it.
You need to pay attention to that of Saturn.
The 10th vision is falling on the house
My karma is attached to it. Saturn's Third
Where the vision is falling on me, that karma is falling
You have to make these efforts. That's it.
Be careful. This will make you a little easier.
It will help you understand your chart and your
What house is Saturn in the chart?
Will activate at this time. Next on to more sessions
We'll talk. Until then, thank you. conquest
Shri Krishna Jai Shri Ram.