Jai Shri Ram Jai Shri Krishna Welcome to my
YouTube Channel Refine Vedic
Astrology is going to be today's session
This is our Sun within the 12  houses
What fruit remains?
Before the 12 houses, we understand the sun.
Is the Sun in the horoscope or above the native?
What an impact
It is all stated in the classical text.
That the Sun is a self-possessing planet.
The soul is the factor i.e. the soul on your life.
What is the purpose of the Sun in your horoscope?
It tells us about man's life on this earth.
The purpose of the soul of what he has taken birth
what
Sun is also the significator of the father and the factor of the father.
For the first child who is the first male child
The Sun is also the significator of the First Male Child
So the sun is what we can understand at any
The factor of origin of the thing is i.e.
As long as there is sunlight on the earth,
The organism moves towards a origin or can be said
We are here until the light of the sun comes to this earth.
New things are being generated.
Meaning the factor of origin is without the sun
There is no life in the trees of light.
Humans without sunlight
There is no resistance
Sunlight is so important.
That He gives a life in everything
If the Sun has the ability then when the Sun is in the 12  houses
What fruit does it give us?
As an example, like the sun of someone.
Suppose you are in the ascendant, then we will say that
Very bold personality is authoritative
Personality is quick for people to it.
You will be attracted if you are of high and
One of the special things about the Sun is that where the
There is also the sun in the house of a human being.
Values are attached to the feeling of what the soul is.
If the Sun is in the fifth house, then the human being is in the fifth house.
The soul is devoted to education and to himself.
To the child, to the first child.
Will be very much connected
Now some people say that if in the sixth house
It is very good if the sun is exalted
But the point to be understood here is that which
The sixth house is the Trishaya house, that is the Trishadaya
A debilitated planet in the house is a yoga factor, is it not?
That planet of exaltation if it became of high 6
If the Sun is exalted in 8 12
The person has to face a lot of problems.
There are different types of diseases
Your ego is a factor of your fame like the sun.
If there is self-respect then in 6 8 12
If the sun is exalted, then such a person does not have fame
I could find it.
Disrespect comes from everywhere for the father
Hatred becomes the first child
If you become hateful with G 8 12 or
The Sun is debilitated in three houses like 11
It gives better fruit and not higher
There is a feeling of craving, there is a feeling of struggle.
If there is a debilitated planet in the house of struggle, then
He gets that environment to fight.
The same environment means that it is the same.
Suppose we are a goonda, you
If you send him to the company of a saint, then his
There won't be so much effect on the top, not so happy.
It must be because he is forced to live
But that is the color of his company, that is, him.
If you find someone like you, then there
He tries to put in more effort
There his energy will be different and the monk will be different.
If his energy is different with the saints
Whether the sun is high or the friend is regional
That is, the benefit is with your planet.
If you are with friends, then the person should be positive.
Gives results even if the sun is debilitated
But if three are in the same expressions as 11, 6, 8, 12
So there it becomes a planet of yoga.
Because if the Sun is debilitated in the 6th house
If you go, your diseases will end your enemies.
If the Sun is in the 6th house, it will suppress the Sun
If the higher one rises, then your enemies are yours.
They will be anime and they will be top class from you.
The more powerful you will be, the more powerful you will be.
It will be going to happen
Therefore, within these houses, the sun is debilitated.
very good
And the sun was said to be the factor of man's ego
How much of the ego you have in a human being?
How much respect will you give to others?
Understand why the Sun is in the seventh house.
It is said that such a person does not get married.
If it happens, it doesn't happen if it gets married
See, if the sun is in passion, then inside you.
If the Sun is in the seventh then your ego is yours.
There is an ego in front of you, that is, in front of you
The one is so fast that you are in front of him.
Dominating the front will not be able to stand
Nature will be on you if you have Sun in the ascendant.
Marriage goes on but in the seventh house
If there is a sun, then dominate the person again and again.
You have to be in front of your partner or in front of you.
He is disrespectful of the one
It is shown on the talk and on top of that.
If you dominate, then in that domination.
To the native
Repeated humiliation has to be endured if on top of it
If you have the aspect of the guru, you can say that
Marriage happens, marriage goes on, but
If the Sun is alone or in the seventh house
The seventh house is called the west
The direction is the direction of the west coming here.
The Sun becomes weaker with weakening
That is, it is the setting sun in the seventh house
The setting sun means the relationship is going down.
Isn't it the effect that is going on the relationship?
He will come, he will come, not to rise.
The Sun would have been good inside the Lagna
That he drives the marriage he rises the sun
If seen practically, then which
It's sunny, it's early in the morning.
If the Sun comes in the ascendant, then the time is 5.
From 7 or between four to five.
It happens, that is, it is rising, it is rising.
There is more positivity in it and what is falling
There is more negativity in what is drowning.
The Sun in the seventh house is therefore weak.
Lives that sinks the relationship there.
But your partner has so much ego that
You can't bear the ego that is the reason for
You become hateful to each other and
The sun, as I said, is the soul factor.
If the Sun is in the seventh house, then the native's
The soul that is there towards his partner
Too much attachment gets attached to the partner
With and because of that attachment when he sees
That's what I'm doing for and
My front partner as much as I do.
Doesn't give respect to me again and again
Putting me down in front of others
When that thing happens, it is the relationship that happens.
There is a rift inside due to which we
Let's see the relationship gets divorced
If the Sun in the seventh house breaks
If you are sitting with the fifth house, there will be a love marriage.
If it breaks later, then this is how it affects us.
You can see that the sun is your soul.
The emotion in which your soul is sitting
The sun tries to connect with the sun
A king
It is the king's job to do it for the people.
Sun is the factor of the heart inside our body.
have
There is a factor of liver and a factor of lungs and
The sun is the significator of our bone, when our
The immune system is a factor when the sun is good
If it happens, then the immune system of the person is very
It is good if in the horoscope of Kalpurush
See, the Sun comes in our fifth house.
Leo is associated with the fifth house.
Wisdom, man's conscience, man's heart, and
Our stomach is associated with the fifth house
Take the whole stomach from our heart.
All the organs up to the stomach are the sun.
When you control the native's Sun.
When he is strong, we tell him that
The immune system will be very strong.
Having a weak immune system weakens
If the sun is the king of all the planets, then
We call him King on all the planets.
The Reigners and the Sun When Very Good
If there is a sun, then the person is in the fame society.
Status: You get all this if it is a week of sun.
The native runs for the same fame and status
Suppose the Sun is Leo
Libra comes in the third house of the ascendant
If the sun becomes debilitated there, then such a person
Fame will definitely earn Fame will run after Fame
Will get it but after struggling a lot
Because the third house is your struggle
Like we talked about three, 6, 11, or 6, 8
12 This is the feeling of struggle here
Sun is very strong, you have such a fame.
Will give but will get the struggle completed
That's why the sun that fame is about giving you light.
The planet is the work of the sun inside you.
Highlight that people understand your point of view
That's why the sun is called the leader.
We see that inside the ascendant like the Sun
Now let's start about the 12  houses
Suppose the Sun is inside the Ascendant, then the native
It can be too egoistic.
That is his nature towards others.
It is the one who humiliates others.
Is the one to dominate if together
Jupiter is not
So what else will we find in his appearance?
The bone above the chicks is
It will be a little bulging
Hair is brown, eyes are brown.
And there is a little charming personality.
Because the sun is bright, the sun
It will go into the house and give light there.
When it gives light,
That means more intense inside of you.
There is more light that people who are on your side
Get attracted as we see
Not the moths that fly with light.
They are attracted very quickly.
There is also a song 'Mehfil Mein Jal Uthi Kshama Parwane'.
For that is, that which is in you.
The glow that is inside you, the Sun in the Ascendant
People are attracted to him inside him.
And because of that, sometimes he has to
I think people are so attracted to me.
If he has been there, then the ego inside him goes on increasing
I'm something there, but he's a little bit of his own.
The sun starts spoiling your sun
Just as bones are also a factor of bones
factor
Sun is the significator of your eyes.
If the heart is the factor of the heart, then the factor of the heart.
When the Sun is in the ascendant, the native should have one.
Good health gives him very good eyes.
It means we can say in the eyes.
Disease would not have happened if the Sun is a good sign.
Is it with Mallick Planet or if
You are also alone, but you are inside a good amount.
As we can say, Gemini
Virgo Sagittarius is exalted in Aries
the sun
Be a little dominating inside Cancer
It goes because there is an aquatic amount, so a little
The factors of the sun weaken there.
When we go to see the First House.
The personality of the Sun is a human being.
People are very charming towards him.
Leadership quality gets attracted
Gives as we know the Sun King
He is the king of all the planets and one of the kings.
Religion builds on top of it.
A lot of responsibilities come when the Ascendant
If the sun is above the human being, then
The person has a lot of responsibilities.
Doing for your family and others.
He has a lot more to do with his father.
Attachment occurs because the father factor Sun
He came and sat in the ascendant, that is, with his father.
The native is very internally attached if he is with
If Rahu comes with the sun, then we will say.
Can it happen after some time or Rahu trine?
If it is  in the houses in 1 5 9 then if
If Rahu is with the father, then the native is with the father.
Do you have grudges or do you feel like this after some time?
Like we say pop up
That something happened that led to their
There was a hatred among themselves or the Sun Rahu
The native immediately goes with the father
Or gets a little distant from the father and bes.
You should go because otherwise you have to go sometime.
Later, he creates a misunderstanding.
The same planet weakens the Sun
What is the shadow that Rahu does?
The sun eclipses everyone
It can set, but in front of Rahu, it can set
When an eclipse occurs, the weakness of the sun occurs
Rahu means the one who you want to get fame Sun
Fame is a factor that you want to get fame.
Which you have to fulfill your responsibilities
Who blames your personality?
Is that Rahu is misunderstood?
What does Rahu do misunderstanding?
Creates in the mind of the native
If you create such a grudge in the mind of the native.
Gives that the native feels that only I
I am the only one, everything else is less, so the native's
Personality is there, it will depend on the Sun
In which zodiac sign is inside the Ascendant if the Self
Is the zodiac sign Leo or Aries?
So leadership will be a very bold personality.
The person is born with quality in life.
If Jupiter is also with the Sun, then
We can say that this person belongs to his family.
For this, he came with a sense of prosperity.
The native should take prosperity for his father
Came with his family's lineage
The one with the Sun in the Ascendant will run
What does the strong sun do to you here?
The relationship with the Father is very good.
But if the sun is here
So, the relationship with the father is time-by.
Time keeps getting stronger for you
The sun makes you honest here.
Because what is a king, a king is honest.
If the king doesn't work honestly
If that people rebel against him, then you will have to
It's very important to be honest here.
That's as honest as you are here.
As loyal as you are to your family.
Per Kundli if Sun is in the Ascendant
And if Saturn is less strong then we see
Hair loss day by day at the time of the native
Hair loss starts after some time
It starts to happen.
There is a lot of attachment with the Father.
Like we talked about, but one thing is this.
Make sure you don't have as much as your father.
Moral will respect their ethics as much as
Your ninth house will be strong.
Because the Sun is the significator of the father.
The house is worth as much as your father.
The number of morals their experience can be filled with their own.
The more you use your luck in life.
It is very much supported somewhere.
self
If the Sun is in the ascendant, then the native will find
Likes to do business mostly
Because such a person does not work under anyone.
Can someone do us in the job?
You have to listen to someone, you can say that
Orders have to be obeyed, but in the ascendant
If there is a sun, then such a person does not listen to anyone.
He may want to do his own business.
The person who is here is self-centered.
It happens, you can only call it self.
Obsession becomes that there is something other than yourself.
Doesn't show a bit of dominating nature
It happens that he has to dominate the other person.
Tries to become impulsive nature
It may not be his nature, but the sun.
When in the ascendant, above the one in front
The native tries to dominate and be too
The sun goes if it is well placed.
Sun is seen in the seventh house
As we see, sometimes,
The ego comes in the relationship, that ego comes to you.
It comes from your side and not your partner.
Because you are going to dominate your
To the partner or to the person in front of you, here
But if Surya becomes a debit debilitator.
The Sun is of Libra as if we
You will find that there is a lot of above the status of the human being.
It makes a big difference
Man can't find the fame of which he belongs to.
He works day and night for man.
He has to be insulted again and again.
One has to endure if Libra in the ascendant
the sun
And if the Sun is in a good sign in the Ascendant
If it is in the zodiac sign of a friend, then we will say that
Here the native can do any work
Asks for proof as the king's work is done
Give me proof whether this is true or false.
If it is, then the person asks for proof that you give me
Tell me how this thing happened.
Those who have the sun in the ascendant need the sun here.
But if you are with Mars, you will find a body.
Somewhere on top of your burning sensation
There will be marks if the Cancer is like
If the Sun is in the ascendant, then you are 100%
You will see that somewhere above your body.
So there is a burning mark on the hand or face
Sun Mars in Cancer Sign
You have to take care now, that's why you said it here.
The aqueous amount inside the Cancer sign is his
If the planets of the two fire elements come and sit inside, then
When there is a combination of fire in water,
A steam is formed that traces of hot steam body
Will be on top of or repeatedly with hot steam
Afflicting therefore Sun, Mars, Cancer
If you are in the scars of burning sensation, we say
Can be on top of the body
These people don't talk much when the sun
If he is in the ascendant, then a person is going to live in himself.
He is looking at himself.
Looking in the mirror again and again, looking at yourself
To be happy to see yourself, it is your
You're mostly engaged in
Don't talk to anyone, very little talkative.
We can say that these people will come forward.
Fighters don't fight behind their backs
If the Sun comes in the ascendant, then they will have to go behind their backs.
They don't know how to fight when they fight.
Will you talk to someone behind your back?
I can't speak because it's the king's job.
What you have to do on the front, which is the treatment.
Whatever measures have to be given, what is to be punished
I want to give it to you on the front, king anytime back.
No one punishes from behind, the whole assembly sits
When a king pronounces his sentence, we
It can be said that the front of the Sun in the Ascendant
He fights and not behind his back.
So overall, the person with the Sun in the Ascendant
It happens, we can say that it is strong.
The immune system is related to the father.
Good personalities are very good
Other people are attracted to him.
Becomes
The one with the Sun in the ascendant is his father and
Always respect the mentor
The advice given by them should always be taken.
Otherwise, if you don't take the same advice, then your
It will spoil the luck that your ninth house
Sun in the Second House Sun when Second House
If inside the good amount of the
Be it within the zodiac sign or even in the higher zodiac sign
If so, the lifestyle of the person is
We can say big royal.
In such a situation, the person should know his family history.
I am very fond of reciting that my grandfather
His great-grandfather was like this, his family history.
He is very fond of showing off.
Because when the Sun comes in the second house,
To shed full light on the lineage of the family
Tries to make your speech that will be big
What will be elegant is your lifestyle, food.
It will be of the most elegant royal form
So the Sun in the second house is the political of the human being.
There is a big inclination towards career or like this.
The native joined the government sector and started his
Generate finance, generate wealth
Are the natives here to their real identity?
Tries to lose a false identity
You can ask him to show himself here.
By hiding the personality of his family, he
Tries to show personality in front
And here's what the native should do.
Suppose you have to use your own
Those who are elderly have done very well.
If you do the work, then instead of showing them off.
We should just say them in the normal way.
Not that we should have an ego or pride in him.
I want to see what my family has done.
Suppose they did, then that
They have made no contribution to it.
If not, then don't keep that thing in ego.
That's why a lot of people are talking about it.
Debates with or with many people
We get arguments with us that we
Did they do so much for you?
What did that go because of a lot of their people?
There are clashes with egos.
Speaking ability says a little bit
It can be a disaster because the sun
What is the king's way of talking?
But the pitch will be very high.
When you speak, talk with a loud voice.
If the other person gets scared like that.
The sun is good if the sun is debilitated
Here you give a lot of confidence.
Not being able to share views with your family
Unable to share the sun with the people
If it is weak here, then it is like this.
The native is married to his family due to his spouse.
Rebel with or fight them
Sits and separates from the family
If the Sun is debilitated in the second house
Because it's your family.
And the other is for your spouse.
This is the eighth inlaw of your spouse.
The native rebelled because of his own spouse.
He sits with his own family members.
The sun here can call you very good.
We are royal in getting food intake.
It can be said here that the nature of the sun
It happens that the mind of the native is
Towards things like Gold, Copper, Silver Inn
He gets attracted more quickly
Because the second part is also of jewelry.
If a planet like the Sun comes, then it can be like this.
The native is wearing many gold silver rings or his
There will be many such antikey pieces at home
Made of things like copper or brass.
All the loyalists at their house are royal.
There are many servants at their home.
You will find more servants who are there to work.
Many people will find the Sun in the second house.
If the second house is the factor of our eyes, then
What will you get when the sunlight shines in this house?
There is so much inside that they have eyes.
That little bit
Stays dry, stays warm, most of the
Time due to which they have many times on their eyes.
You must have to add water to this eye drop.
You must be using it if the sun is here.
If the person is afflicted, then the person goes into politics.
And by suppressing your money there.
If the sun is good, then it comes back like this.
The native is very quick towards political career.
They get attracted and there they get attracted
Many social contacts are made at a high level
From where he started his political career.
You can have a little bit of education here.
You can say incomplete because when the sun
If you sit in the second house, then it is your lineage.
Showing your lineage to your ego
Don't choose such a school many times.
Find that where you see that my
Are they not equal people or their egos?
Clashes occur in school or colleges
Go and cause some mishandling
Whom they go because of whom they have their own
I had to give up my education.
Either if the Sun is weak, then the native's
With your first child or with a male child
There will be no good relationship with you or you
He doesn't have a good relationship with the inlaws.
When the Sun is in the second house, the father will be there.
Will be able to come either in the government sector
Or any such authoritative post.
But where they have a lot of
Servants are the ones who work
So keep a good relationship with the father.
Because somewhere the father is the only one.
Generating wealth in the second house
The Sun that is sitting is the Father, the creator of that wealth.
You are able to do what you can because of your life.
Able to live in a royal form in the second house
If the Sun is with Mars, then we can say
Such a person is due to his arts or because of his
Due to education, the native has to interact with others.
Gets a clash or misses with others
If the Sun starts behaving on Mars
Be together because two planets are such fire elements.
The planets came and sat in the second house.
There are a few speeches like this.
Did they even talk to someone?
So he feels that the order has been placed in front of him.
Because of such behavior, they
Others get clashed with others
Fighting with other people's money
They inherit the inheritance of others.
If the Sun is in the second house, then it is in the seventh house.
The eighth is the eighth of other people.
Inheritance assets money them very quickly.
These people give their money to them.
It is very easy to get into political parties.
If you're going to learn over there.
You should go and don't understand that you
Everyone has taught you a lot of family lines.
Assumed to have been good but who is in front of you
Someone is going to work towards someone.
Are you going to work for the party or are you?
If you also work in the government sector, then
He has to understand his religion and work.
2nd House Your Wealth or Your Soul
It is purpose, it tells you that the work that you have to do
I have to do it for my family now.
Suppose you are very attached to your family.
If you are who you have to do in this life.
You have to do your family for your family.
Where is the work of generating wealth?
Sun in the Third House has gone to the third house
When the Sun shows courage, the third house
The Sun comes in either the native's siblings
Or the native would have been the eldest brother.
have
Inside your siblings and these over there
Relationships with your younger siblings
Destroys them, not with them
They can either call it an ego clash or
Try to explain it to your siblings.
They think it's up to us.
Trying to get an order
Egos clash and each other.
Ends the relationship
Here the native has a lot of communication skills.
If they are good, then the person is administrative.
Inside the Government or Secretary in the post
Do you try to get into a job or?
The third house is our writing.
There is also the third sense of our courage.
The third house is your communication skills
So when a planet like the Sun comes here,
Communication skills are very high here.
Boosts and makes them very confident
Keeps the confidence level of the person very high
It is like journalism.
Go where it is on top of any news.
The sun's job is to shine light.
Putting it is journalistic journalism
Inside the media of news channels
Inside them can do this work.
Here these people get their enmes very quickly.
Because the sixth to the tenth
It falls on the field of karma of the enmes.
The sun is sitting i.e. when you are working.
You know he's my enemy.
You get to know that it's my undeniable.
I have come here to do something unhelpful to me.
If you did, the sun would save you from it.
Is there any light inside your mind?
You already realize that this is mine.
If the Sun comes here in the third house, then the Sun comes here in the third house.
Helps save the person from his anime
These people always win in debates.
Let's try when the debate is going on.
They can beat anyone inside that debate.
There is no victory from them in terms of debate.
???? ?????? ?? ????????? ????? ???? ????
????? ???? ?? ?? ????? ??? ????????? ??
Because the seventh is the ninth from the other.
Sun moved to the ninth house for people
Which is the seventh house and the third house for you, you
?????? ?? ?? ????????? ????? ??? ?? ???
Let's have good luck in life.
Growing, which is the ninth house, grow
What is luck, what is morality, so when you
If you see the growing life of others, then it
You get satisfaction and you get good
It seems to see the progress of others without
Never ask for the nature of helping others.
Sometimes they get into fights that the other
Other people think it's too much.
Interfering with our lives
And because of that, they have a relationship with other people.
Clashes would have taken place
The Sun in the Third House is a Karzius to you.
Makes Brave Makes Charitable Makes
Because a man is a charity-doer.
It is the job of the Sun to give the third house.
Courage is the third house of the hand, then the human being
The second to the second house is the third house from the house of wealth
According to the Bhavat Bhavan, there is a sense of wealth.
The person is career, he is brave.
But also the soft-hearted charity
It happens that it is kind hearted.
When the person sees the suffering of others,
He took her grief for him.
Gets ready to do a lot of charity
They express the feeling of this thing to themselves.
Do or express any feelings
These people should choose this profession too.
Let's take up publishing work
Editing work should be done due to which it is
Emotions through publishing or any
Convey those feelings through editing at work.
Pull out
These people can do so well in math or science.
They may not be in this field, but these people
Drama or performing arts like we need to
Also performing an art on stage
So it works great in those places.
The place where you can take out your art.
It is the job of the sun to show the sun.
It is your job to provide light, it is your job to give light.
To connect the soul with that emotion is to have a sense of courage.
Very good communication added
Skills to extract any art given to you
Sun for or to work in the theater
It is very important to be good when
Your communication skills or your
People can't take the art out.
If you are not attracted to you, then the third
The native is very good in the house of the Sun.
There may also be those who work in theater
Their intellectual knowledge would have been very good
But because of that knowledge, they have their own
A little bit of a safe guard to Impatience and Pride
It should be done that because of that knowledge, it is more
I don't know that I am impatient.
Listen or because of that knowledge that intellectual
Because they let others down.
Show yourself more proudly in that
this
People think the native thinks that he is the native.
It's always right, he thinks I'm always
I'm right because of that thing for other people.
There is a misunderstanding with which
The reason is that they become hateful to the other people.
You shouldn't always think about that.
I'm right, maybe the other one.
The work of the king is also right somewhere.
You have to see both sides of a coin.
If it happens, then prove yourself right or
You understand that this is right, I am second before that.
It is also important to listen to the human being
Because this is the king's religion.
I am telling someone in front of me something.
Let me first listen and understand what he has to say.
Trying if Sapta-H in the 3rd House
If the Sun is of Aries, then such a person either
Fashion Field Likes to Go to the Line of Modeling
Because Aries is your own.
Personality means that you will dare to do so
Or will you try in a place where your
People look at you by looking at your personality.
Are you attracted or your wealth is generated from there?
And if the Sun is Libra here.
So the native has a sexual desire inside the native.
Love marriage increases a lot
There is a desire but there is a lot of laxity
In interacting with other people, this
Libra's Sun is very much in the third house
Top class is Libra
There is interaction with the person in front of you when here
But the Sun has become debilitated, which is the third house.
If there is a trishadaya feeling, then the native is from the people only.
Learns how to interact with me
It means that he is so friendly with other people.
He has talked about his communication.
They become so high class that they are bye.
The one with the Born Sun didn't bring it here.
If you learn by learning, then the third house
Tell the sun your speech and your own
You can use communication or your knowledge.
You should not be so proud of it.
Let him weaken his sun in the sun
Fourth House When Sun Comes in 4th House
So you can say that there is no light that it
Night time is from 12:00 to 1:2 pm
It's around time when the sun is here.
The behavior of the mother is one
The mother is more like the father.
Mother Will gives guidance to the native
Be Give More Guidance to the Native Father
Does he have a grudge against his father or hatred with him?
Due to excessive hatred, the person is far away
They don't get their father's love.
Someone who yearns for a mother
Manager post is on any authoritative post
Pay within the government sector and who
The father has gone from the ninth to the eighth
Sun could be the father of any government
In the sector, as if it has become a sales tax.
Insurance companies will be inside whose
Inside he is inside the official post.
And because of this attitude of theirs, you will find that
You have a grudge against your father.
Along with this, there is neither the sun nor the sun there.
Gets dull in the sense it's night time
There is no sunlight, that is, light.
It is not in that house inside the horoscope.
To the native who
It can be said that the mother is the happiness of the whole father.
Giving
It is written in the stories of the books.
It is written inside that the Sun in the fourth house
One does not get the happiness of the father completely.
Do they get away from their father or their father?
It is written that if it is written that
The sun is suffering too much there.
So, the native who loves teaching advice.
He gets all the food from his mother.
You can say things to him only through your mother.
It is the mother who nurtures in this way.
Native
Like Mother, we talked about the manager post.
It can be the native from his homeland or his own homeland.
He has a very common attitude towards the house.
It's a big hobby in your home or your homeland.
To show that we have so much.
The land is how big our house is.
Ah, it is a big attachment to show things.
Because it is in the fourth house of a human being.
The soul of the human being is at home.
She is very attached to her house.
A fried cake made of grounded pulse and spice
He is conscious that everything is at my house.
Things are aligned as they are kept
These people should stay in their homes.
Décor also looks a little royal
Yes, as it used to be during the time of kings
Mostly these people show in Amazon Flipkart
You must be engaged in things like these and your
Something like this for home décor
You must have been busy ordering, because of which
Our house which is a little royal
Sun comes in the 10th  house for the spouse
If there is sun in the seventh to the tenth then the spouse
Which is inside the administrative post.
Or be in an officer rank.
If you are inside the female chart, then
If the mail is in the chart, then any administrative
There will be a lot of friends inside the post.
They are supportive all the time.
They stand up to do what the native does.
The native is interested in playing vocals
Instrument music a little bit inside it
It's more because the sun itself
In the fifth house, which is in the horoscope of Kaal Purush.
Leo comes in the fifth house, which is
If music shows any art, then their
On the singing side or on the vocal singing side
Moving towards instrumental music
There is an inclination in the fourth house, which is also of the mind.
The sunlight coming over the mind is now here.
But if the sun is dull, then sometimes if the sun is dull.
If you are suffering, you can call them on the way.
Giving them advice in this way of life.
There is no one
Many times we will find that our lives are bigger.
Full of darkness in which the Lac of Light
No one is going to advise them
The fourth house is not going to give light
If the Sun is in Libra, then this is what will happen.
The native will keep thinking all the time that I wish I
Can anyone give advice?
I have such wounds on my mind in front of me.
This is what people think of me.
But that torments my mind.
Here, if the Sun is negative, then the person should
At first, he would have eliminated the motivation from his mind.
It makes it less direct.
I don't understand the purpose of life.
What have I come to do to understand the soul?
I don't know which path to take.
Here the sun gets dull, exactly to him.
There is no light on which way.
I have to walk, it gets oversensitive.
If anyone says a little kiss, then
They take it upon themselves personally.
As a result, they feel insulated that
I may have been insulted even if they
The person in front of them did not say anything about them
If the sun suffers too much on here
Suppose you are suffering from Rahu from Saturn.
Come here to get hurt.
So the native's heart, lungs, brain, kidney.
Livers have some such disease inside them
Because of which he is very upset.
Is there if the Scorpio sign is with the sun?
If Mars also sits in it, then burning sensation
Can you say on their hands or on their chest?
You can see the scars.
The sun is here as the father's factor.
If he goes from the ninth house to the eighth house, then the father
Are you also very worried about health issues?
There may be some health disease.
If the father is upset because of this, then here
But for the sun, a remedy is that
The native should not offer prayers to the sun every morning.
We must give what we offer water
The Sun must do what it needs to do.
When the sunlight is above him, he
Something in your personality.
Such a person will see a change, there can be a lot
Time cannot bear the sunlight
The person should take sunlight on himself.
The more sunlight comes, the more it
Light will come over his life.
Luck will support when fate supports the sun
The light of the ninth house is supported.
Luck is that the sun is also the factor there and
Jupiter is also the factor there when sunlight
Sunlight falls on your body
If you have a problem somewhere, your mind
This is how the nervous system intellect starts working
She does that for herself in life.
If he makes a way, then he is in the fourth house.
The Sun should think that the one in front of him should also
If something is saying then let him down.
Don't take it upon yourself
Take overthinking as an insult
The rest of them are very attached to their home.
Where should you go to your homeland?
You were born in your father's land.
This is my father's land, we say.
Should go to it, never sell it.
If they sell, then from there.
It hurts because you are sitting there.
Weakened the Sun
Sun in the Fifth
When the Sun is in the fifth house, it
Too much problem with child conceiving
Creates this because you see.
The brightness of the sun is not what it is.
If the water can also dry up, then the fifth house
When she is pregnant inside the stomach
Liquid form will not be able to be made where
But that liquid for the birth of the child
Form is needed and Sun in the fifth house
Sitting and drying that water in the stomach
From where you can conceive a child, then
The first child to come here is the sun.
Creates a problem with conceiving
Which
The soul of the native who walks or
So, will you continue to be concerned about your education?
I couldn't educate myself or he
Too much for your first child.
Inconcientious or we can say fear
Lives he is afraid of his first
If Jupiter becomes a child
If you have respect, then you are afraid because there
If the Sun sits, then the people of the fifth house will be there.
The Sun must remedy one thing
He didn't have Lord Shiva in his life.
Krishna ji is very hard to vote.
If you want it, then it is his devotion sir.
Then the sun is here to Krishna and Shiva.
But you can reduce your brightness of the sun
It will be less here, otherwise what will happen child?
Most in conceiving and education
There is a problem here.
The involvement of the native
He can say instrument player or
Art on the Vocalist side from Singing
There is more of a person here.
But his attention is more towards education.
I can educate myself
As soon as possible and due to the same education.
The same education in front of others.
Shows that he is the center of
Look at how much attraction I can become.
I have knowledge because people look at me.
He got the fame of doing this here.
Let's try to give fame to a person
So increase the art in him, his education.
But if the sun suffers
That's not even the art in him.
Let it grow and stop its education as well.
They are big in tantra mantra sadhana.
There is a hobby because it is also a sense of hobbies.
If the third to the third is the fifth then the person
The hobbies that are of tantra mantra sadhana
On the other hand, his inclination is more human.
Devotion is mostly towards religion.
He has more devotion and the more he does.
He knows religion as much as he knows himself.
The more he goes on educating the one
The sun is there, but the ego gives that ego
If the Sun in the fifth house finishes
If you are giving ego to a person, then you will be given the most ego.
First of all, you should educate yourself on that education.
Because of this, he can kill his ego.
Here you will find theater like cinema.
You can also get fame in places that you
Work in a theater where you get fame.
If the sun can be found here with Rahu
If the person is concentric, then the person believes in other people.
Betrays and sits with
They should never build their trust with them.
I can't do it because what is Rahu here?
But to create a misunderstanding
Tries Sun Rahu in the fifth house
This is the wish of others from the seventh
The 11th house is the house of other people's desires.
Such a person who plays with them becomes such a person.
Such a person who breaks faith becomes such a person
The fifth house is your speculative markets.
It is also like stock market mutual.
Fund Gambling Lottery Investment Places
The person either earns fame or his wealth.
Tries to make if Jupiter's
If the aspect comes here, then the person here
He gets 100 percent fame when he
Uses things
Extracting Your Art of Theater Your Knowledge
As a teacher as a teacher
Doing transactions can be called the light of knowledge.
Spreading in a way is also because of that education.
They also get fame because of their hobbies
They get the fame of their souls in this life.
My duty is to educate yourself.
Bring out your arts that are yours
There is art inside, don't keep it inside you.
Show others and teach others a lot.
A good teacher can also be the one with the Sun Pancham
That such a person without ego can do his own education.
Eliminates the ego of yourself and others.
It becomes worthy of giving knowledge.
If the Sun is the fifth house, then the native has a stomach.
The disorder may be caused by a stomach rash.
Due to any acidity or due to gas, they
Trouble persists mostly which is Surya Pancham
If it happens in the house, then the love relationship of the person
There are many, but one thing is always remembered.
Keep the sun here ever to give you your true love.
He doesn't let him stay with his partner.
Separates here because look
There's so much light in the sun.
People get attracted to them inside
And it's because of more than one relationship.
They make it because of which they make their true love.
He didn't recognize them and walked away from them.
The attachment of the native goes to his
Too much for the first child
And that's the only thing you need to know here.
Trying to Teach or Your Soul
What she wants is that she wants me to be famous.
I got my self on the basis of my knowledge.
I got it on the strength of the efforts that I have done.
I can show it to others, but I can show it.
The way is the way, it is not in the ego.
It should be in a giving spirit.
I want to give it to them which I have
Gained knowledge or art in me.
I want to refine this art
I don't let anyone down in a sense of giving.
Show Sun in the Sixth House in the 6th House
When the sun is there, it is a hostile yoga.
Builds where sunlight
It is so much that they have enemies
They can't be hidden enemies themselves.
You come out and come out of their enemy.
And they recognize that they are
Who are my enemies?
They would have come to know
So the person is here because of his same sun.
From those because of his sunlight
The sun destroys enemies
It becomes strong here because if
If the sun is debilitated here, then in a relationship.
Maybe he'll get divorced, but the sixth
If you are low in price, then give a post like CO
Can be on an administrative post
It can be you or you can be yours.
Father, if the sun is debilitated here or
If you are an enemy in an enemy house, then you or
Your father is in a government sector
Physicians can be in the Lawyer Police like this
On administrative post where you
You resolve people's disputes and the sun
When it comes here in the 6th house, then the native's
Those who have had a slight difference of opinion with Ah Mata
Because the action of the mother is her life.
On top of that, he's a little dominating.
Maybe the mother has some guide to them.
You are trying to do it, but they are off.
Behavior is not good for them if the sun
Here, as if with Rahu, Rahu or Saturn.
If you are with the native many turn as you drive
Some are going in front of such a dog horse.
Or the cow coming in front of you because of which
Does it get into an accident or do they bite a dog?
Sometimes you have to face these things while walking.
fallow land
be with his maternal uncle uncle
Relations are very good if the sun is here.
But if it is good then if Rahu is above the sun.
If there is no effect, then only with maternal uncle
Do you have a grudge against money or land?
There is hatred for taking and because of which
They have to be humiliated many times.
Father's
In front of you, the nature of the native is here.
That the person is a problem-solving man or
They go where there is a fight
Because they think I'm talking to them.
Can I solve the sixth house which
The sixth house is as we see it as a lawyer.
Those who see that as police
Eliminates people's conflicts
So when the Sun is your soul karaka planet 6th house
If I come, then you are of other people.
Access to overcome conflicts
You go to remove their conflicts.
I can do it as a judge.
And as mentioned earlier, if the sun is deved.
If yes, then the spouse can get divorced here.
Can spoil the relationship with the
But that's the sun that makes you the CEO and the CEO.
Can also give administrative posts
Because the Sun is in the Trishadaya house
Even if you are degraded, Raja Yoga becomes a factor
3 6 11 Trishadaya Bhava is debilitated
The sun is here to try you again and again.
Tries to get you to try these
Engage in things by coming to the sinful planet sin house
It becomes very strong and that is the strong.
It takes so many efforts that you can make those efforts.
You learn everything by doing it and you
You become a self-made man from there.
Sun is placed here in the 6th house of the native.
It has teeth on it, either sometimes woody or
From the stone
There is something that they felt because of them.
Defects occur in the teeth.
Because of them, they go for surgery a lot.
And if the sun is here in a good sign.
It is in the sign of a benign planet i.e.
Gemini Virgo Taurus Libra is inside this sign
So the tooth is very beautiful if Jupiter
Aspect should come in Jupiter.
But the Sun below Libra is also very good for you.
Gives good teeth
And of these people who surround the surroundings.
People are mostly like this.
They get to prepare for the competition.
Do you like competitive exams?
You prepare for everything in life.
You consider it a competition with the same people.
Focus on your work environment and daily routine.
In the daily routine, we are surrounded by people.
Where we are sitting, where we are talking to whomever we are.
They're there all the time.
Do you keep talking about competition or this?
We have to go to the competition, we have only one life.
There is competition i.e. the sixth house for the Sun
That I just have to get ahead of this thought.
The system remains the sixth house of the Sun
oh great
The work that takes place in the Lawyer Safety Division
Physician doctors can be these and their
Parents are also in the same profession somewhere.
Where they are connected to other people.
Conflict is eliminated father
Lawyers can be in the police
Mother can be a very good physician
Where people are given counseling
Eliminate their conflicts
It goes in one way or the other.
In the 6th house Sun we can say that if
Suffering too much
The sun is either theirs.
Mami becomes widow at a very early age
Or there would be a grudge inside their maternal uncle
Which is their relationship towards divorce.
Takes the Sun in the Sixth House
The person must have a sense of service.
You should keep your routine good
Because the sixth house is of routine as much as the native.
He serves his father and mother.
The Sun here sits in the 6th house to the native.
Even by insulting him, he would make him respectable.
That is, you have to be humiliated again and again.
Because the soul is sitting in the sixth house and the sixth house
The feeling is of humiliation, the planet of honor is of humiliation.
If I sit here again and again, I have come and sat in the house.
When the sun will come after being humiliated
Then you will find that this service and this one that I have ...
This is the only way to keep your life in routine
Disgrace is a work equal to value for you one day.
It doesn't matter when you don't have to do that.
What do people say about me now?
The Seventh House Sun in the 7th House
Not good at classical text books
It has been said that the factor of divorce has been described here.
Whether it is fasting or Parashar, read the scriptures.
Read Deepika, read Laghu Parashari.
This is what is said in all the classical texts
That the Sun in the seventh house ends the relationship.
Makes and lacks of confidence
Shows why this happens now because
The seventh house is the west direction, where
The sun will see you.
If the sun is not rising, then the sun is going down.
When the sun is setting, the house in which it
All the factors of that emotion are being molded.
He is making your seventh house weak.
Relationship is the seventh house is your marriage.
What respect do other people give you?
He will give respect to the seventh house.
Your business too
The seventh house is the effort of your first child.
So here is when the sun factors your soul.
The planet is in this house irrespective of which house it is.
In the zodiac he is considered to be the same as the lowly
Except for Aries because there is his
The significator element of the zodiac becomes strong
But the sun is in any zodiac sign here.
Tries to bear the same fruit as the wretched
So what happens here is that the native and his
Ego with partner or front-runners
There is a clash of the native here.
Behavior or mood swings of the native
The mood that depends on the other person
It depends on the person that he or she will tell you.
How to treat
How does ego clash happen that you said something?
To your partner or to your
He didn't listen to your words
You are so attached to them from the bottom of your heart that this thing
It bothers you that the opinion given by me
Or why did they give me a point?
If you do not agree, then the Sun of the seventh house is here.
Divorce or love relationship due to ego clash
It also creates disputes in native.
That the year that is sol is the soul factor
She doesn't live inside her partner.
He becomes so conscious about her.
You can say to your partner that
His nature is sometimes skeptical.
Turns into maybe he's overpassive.
Yes for him, but the sun is here.
Here's what it's trying to explain.
Because the sun is a king, that is,
Time is the king in front of you, so the king
You will have to accept the decision that you take.
People don't believe in that decision.
Somewhere in your life, your partner.
Suppose in this life
If you had a domineering nature
The Sun is in your ascendant in this birth.
If you have got the Sun in your seventh house, then something
Nothing would have happened in a previous life that this
This spouse or partner has to be cut in birth
With what the spouse says,
Suppose it becomes the center of attraction when
You avoid them.
You will say their efforts well.
That you are correcting what you are doing to them.
If you show your efforts in front of the world, then
This partner is for you, for your soul.
Very good as a protective nature
Work in
Will do the behavior of the partner who becomes
Dictatorship becomes that the order command
They have to accept that, they don't.
If you believe it, egos clash with each other.
Native doing everything for his partner
Is it for the person in front of you?
Everything is going to happen, but sometimes
If the Sun is in the seventh house, then other people have it.
These people are unable to sleep due to fear and their
Sleep is not complete from the first child
They don't get a lot of happiness at first.
They have a grudge against their children.
They put orders on them or this
With them being so overpaced
Behave that they feel that they are imprisoned
They are living in their first child.
Relationship with whom gets spoiled
Overpossession of
If the moving Sun is with Venus here.
So either the spouse of the native has a lot of relation.
Or will you have more than one of your own?
You build a relationship due to which you
Creating disputes with your partner
And the same disputes are divorced or
Creating separation with each other
Here the native has to bear the insult again and again.
Because his fame is his soul.
Which is under the control of another person
That is, what is the other person who is there?
Will treat it, it depends on the other person.
And when those people repeatedly insult them.
Repeatedly give orders to an authority.
In the form of which the thing knocks them down.
Disputes arise with each other
Goes
These people are capable of doing a lot.
Hey ! stop that !
But they should be taken care of by their spouse or in front of you.
Need support of need a ladder due to which
Come out of that darkness and go into the light.
How will they get that letter?
By doing what the people in front of you are saying.
Instead of opposing them, yes Hazuri.
Do as much as you please, you will receive.
This sun is a very good one for you in life.
Can the seventh house take you to the position?
People with the sun are in a very good position.
You may not be able to find it.
But he did one thing in his life.
You may not agree to do your job.
But at that time, please do what you have done.
He said that if he said the truth, then such a person has his own words.
Saves your relationship in life
I remember a line here: Bend down.
The glory of the living is to bow down.
Pride is the identity of the dead
If it happens, then the one who is alive is bending and
The one who is bending is the same by running the relationship.
He is taking the sun in his life.
By aligning one's own fame goal ambition
Sun in the Eighth House is taking the Sun to the side
When in the eighth house, the father is either
Such spectacular activities would have been within
Because of which your family is big.
Is it hurting your dignity or your dignity?
Family reputation falls but if the sun
It's good to see the Malefic Planet here.
If you are, you will find a father or someone
Higher posts will be in the government sector
Inside can say inside sales tax
Inside the insurance company, you can say this.
Authoritative post where these people research
You do the work of the Father and in the eighth house.
Laws to the Sun Native who are inlaws
They are very supportive financially.
Support them
Do research with very good research.
The native's research can be inside the field
There is a big inclination but now you also
See, the eighth house is not a well of darkness
The planet came and sat there like the sun.
So if such a person wants to go into the research field.
He can be so proficient that he can be able to see others
He can also understand the thought system.
Can heal others due to research
The eighth house which
It is a research field called the eighth house sudden.
The sun is now like your soul.
If the planet sits here, then inside your life
You have to understand that there is a sudden change
But when the native is here in research or finance.
In the work of if a planet like Mercury is of the Sun.
Are you with me or watching mercury?
If you are either an astrologer or an astrologer researcher.
Work in occult work or research work
He is so accomplished that he finds his
Financial status would have improved so much.
Due to which he gets fame and
Here, there is a natural talent in the native.
She is in no way in the dark.
You can pick up something and bring it to light.
Any negative person will be considered positive.
Can change your way of behavior
Because or you can say it
Because of its Illuminate Lightning of the Sun
Wherever the sun goes, that house
It fills the people here with light.
It is very important to keep yourself positive
If the Sun is afflicting here, then the native
Thoughts like suicidal things to come to your
Persisting in the Pursuit of Ending Your Life
Cursing you, thinking of yourself negatively as your father
Hatred with the father of such activities
Be inside
As we can say, be inside the intoxicants or
Not having a good relationship with their mother
Due to which there was a lot of trauma on the family.
You reach the family who are members of the
If they are separated, then the sun is here.
There is a very important role in the eighth house.
Andar aur eighth house in sun wale ko hum kahn
The native may be a land lord
Where they get through rental income from people.
You run your wealth because the eighth house
It's also about making money with other people's money.
And here the sun sits on the eighth day.
In the house, it is sitting in the second house from the seventh house
That is, to increase your wealth from the wealth of others.
Add the Sun sitting in the eighth house to the second house
He sees the seventh and the sun with the fourth view.
If you sit in the fifth house, then such a person or something like this
The native's father may be a land lord
As a result, he can earn his
Do you generate wealth or your home?
Run
Ho Eighth House Very Good Understanding
Gives Hidden Things to Understand
It is human nature to do what others want.
Hidden Thoughts That Desires Are
Or what is the other person thinking?
Read what's going on in his mind.
Tries when the Sun is in the eighth house
And try to know the religion of others.
Sun is in the eighth house, which is
From the ninth to the 12th , that is, your religion
Not a man's attitude towards other's religion.
Too much attachment or trying to learn.
If he does this thing to the Sun of the eighth house, then
He should do what he wants in his life.
Changes happen to him to avoid it.
Identify yourself as an occult or researcher.
You have to put it in the field from where that research will have to be done.
You can bring gemstones by doing this.
There is hidden darkness inside the sea
But only pearls inside that secret darkness
So when you get inside this darkness
Only when you sink can the sun bring light.
Or can the sun give you that light?
You can do that thing by doing a lot of research and get it out.
Try it yourself.
Educate yourself about your religion
Do
Educate yourself about your wealth because
Looking at the second house from the seventh point of view
What professions do you want your wealth in?
Let's make the overall eighth house good.
It's just a little bit about the father.
Damadol Gets Son in the Ninth House
There is also the sun factor of the ninth house, like so
When the Sun is in the Ninth House
If I am not there, then to my father and my guru.
Such a person is a devotee much more than his father.
He is more attached to his guru and also to his guru.
In such a situation, it is very considerable.
If the native comes to Jupiter's aspect or
If the Sun alone is strong, then the person either
In the teaching profession or long diss.
Long distance in which one has to travel
Be it in law or medicine or medical.
The native tries to go to the field
Look at your morality which is the Ninth House.
Your soul will move in the sense where it is.
But don't let anything hurt your morals.
If there is any injury to their morals.
When he delivers, he receives a lot of pain.
That is, they think that this thing is wrong
But if this thing is not heard, then the native will have to
It hurts a lot if people say the same thing.
If they understand this, they get a lot of happiness.
Yes, what I thought, what I think is religion.
According to him, people believed that
So their sun is very happy there.
Moral Ethics of Sun Jataka in the Ninth House
They make big matters in life.
He can say that such a person can cut off his head.
But you can't fall from your ethics.
If the sun isn't suffering
So a person should always have motivation from his father or
The Ninth House meets its gurus
To the Sun and to such a person as his Father.
Or Miss Behave Anytime with Your Master
You shouldn't give them advice.
Sanjeevani is equivalent to herb that when it
If you follow them, that advice will be very good for them.
It will prove to be good fruitful and we will see.
Hain They Remain Grounded in the Good Times
And come in the bad times when their very
It's cool when you're having a good time.
Stay down and mean big grounded
They don't have ego there.
This is because this is the energy of the ninth house.
It connects a person with such spirituality
That the person knows about himself that
I have nothing that time to do and
If I have karma, then the person would have been very grounded.
If the sun is not afflicted, then if the sun is not afflicted.
If you are afflicted by a planet like Rahu, then it is a
Creating a paternalism that explains
That something from our father or his associate.
There has been a mistake that led to this paternal defect
hook
And see, you will not find this fatherhood of yours.
In children or of your brothers or sisters.
This is why it will be found in children.
That some mistake from those people is such a karmic mistake
Whose debt is still owed to you people.
Rahu is alone in the ninth house.
Be it Rahu with the Sun or the Moon
If you are rahu, then the native
On the new moon day I say five
Amavasya bath must be done continuously
What happens to him when you celebrate the new moon
If you take a bath, then you have a karmic depth.
There's a running water running over you.
Your negative aura flows through your
It is getting negative upstairs, pulling it away.
That's why bathing in Haridwar is the best.
It was said that sins would be washed away here
If you are a negative and a karmic person over you.
Depth is mounted on top of you, you for that.
Apologize and donate to him
There on that day of the new moon which
We may have made mistakes with our ancestors.
I apologize for this after which you
Luck will support you, you will understand the difference
That is the one of my life after doing this.
I understand your purpose.
There was a negative effect on the soul
There is no such thing as your incest above the sun.
Due to fault due to personnel depth
When you correct that mistake, from there.
The sun begins to show its brightness and
Then he opens the way to your destiny
They don't have a love affair for a long time.
Short Sleeves are Long Lasting
Their love relations do not live here.
Can't walk well and long distance
Foreign tours are very good for them and
Their inclusion is of spirituality
On the other hand, as much as possible, we are together.
Spiritual came after a long journey
Spouse's relationship with his sibling
They are not good because they are third to seventh.
Gone into the moon i.e. their own
With Spouse's Own Sibling
There is a misunderstanding due to which
If their relationship gets spoiled, then here
Sun's energy if positively affected
You're doing a lot with your father.
There will be a good relationship if there is a negative here.
If the effect is coming, then you will come here, father.
With this, the ego clashes.
Let you know your luck and your father's guru.
Spoil the relationship with the mentor
And the same relationship will give you in the future.
They violate morality, so the Ninth House
Surya's remedy is that of his father and
The advice of the mentor is always to be heard in the
10th
When the Sun is inside the 10th house,
They become desperate, they get the strength of direction.
The time of the sun is from 12  to 2.
Time is in full brightness, that is, to the sun.
No one could see that much light at that time.
It is at that time when the Sun is inside the tenth house.
If you come, then this person has so much inside him.
Build confidence that the native
Go to any extent to gain your fame
It can happen if Rahu joins here.
Sun and Rahu on the field of karma
The combination is such that the native can do any
By manipulating to the extent that he is able to manipulate his fame and his
The status quotient but the sun that
It is on the tenth house of the father's Markesh house.
When you sit down, it is often seen that
After the father, the native got fame i.e. when
He was with his father in his fame.
There were obstacles, but after the departure of the father.
After or after being away from the father, the native
You get fame and the person creates a status of his own.
Now finds  the native in the 10th house or someone
Government Sector Pay Administrative
Sun may be on the post  in the 10th house
If so, the native's hair will fall a lot
Their hair fall is quite high here.
Because the sun becomes very strong and
Here a person gets leadership quality.
Because of which he is a professional success.
Finds Leadership Quality
Like very good politicians who will be their
The sun is very strong, that is, the people.
Sun Tenth that sees the house of Janardana
It sits on the sentiment that the people are on their side.
That is, to attract other people.
Which is the Fourth House to attract you
It belongs to the masses, it belongs to the people, so the tenth house
When the sun sits, when you
You are in the profession to other people.
Through your work, through your efforts.
Attract people to your side
So here the sun will make the person famous very quickly.
Either he will get fame or else
In a government department, he has a lot of
Administrative can be called authoritative
Post will be found
But here the human being remains grounded
is necessary
The person who is here has big ground
Comes up from the level and there is a talent in it.
It happens that he can make gold from clay
Meaning it comes up from the ground level.
And give anything a big look.
It means that he can start any work.
It has been going to start from a very low level.
But after he started that work, he
It will take you to the extent where people think.
Can't
Now if the sun is in a good position here
There is no aspect of any mathematical planet.
Not with Ketu if with Ketu
So you'll find that the father has a snake at some point.
Have you cut it?
So that's the second topic if the sun is here.
He is in a good position inside Navmash
It is not inferior in Navmash and so we are here.
You will either find a police or a revenue officer.
It can be on the officer's post or your
The father will be in a post where karma
His fame on the field is the name when you go.
Your father will be in his office then.
only
One can say that they are seen with good eyes.
If there is a Scorpio sign here.
If there is a Sun, then we will find that either of the native
There will be more work of a physician in the career or
A surgeon's job can be too much.
These people can be good doctors of the sun.
Here the amount is also of great importance.
Which zodiac sign is the Sun in?
Accordingly, by taking those factors into his
If you get fame according to it, then what is the tenth house?
All the people of the sun get fame
It's not like that, understand one more thing when the sun
If it gets closer to a planet
Combusts it, sets it down.
So if the Sun is here with the Lagnesh.
If he sat down and set the lagnesh, then
Such a person has to endure humiliation many times
He never gets the fame he deserves.
For he yearns for Suppose Scorpio Ascendant
The Sun is the zodiac sign of Leo and the Sun is the zodiac sign of Leo
Inside the 10th House and also Mars inside the zodiac sign
I have come there, both are in both directions.
You get the strength of direction here.
They go here and come here, but the lagnesh who is there.
It has set from the sun, so what can we say?
It is possible that the person will not get fame.
No, because the lagnesha is the one who has to get the fruit.
If he sets, how can he get the fruit?
That's why it's a lot to see your placement.
What is more important is for your Ascendant?
The Sun is the right planet in your ascendant.
Are you sitting or where your ascendant is sitting?
You can work by joining that field or
The sun will make you in that field.
Make you a master and fame from that field.
Suppose it is on the 10th  house in the ascendant.
And if it is in the fifth house inside Navmash, then like this
The native should use his art, his knowledge, his skill.
You will get fame according to the calculation and this is why you will get passion and Navmash.
It would have been very important to add a lot of
Because it is for the placement of the sun.
Is the sun your soul?
Wants fame in the tenth house
If he wants, he can become a status fame only then
When you are in the house of the Sun and the house of Navmash
Connecting with the feeling in which you are inside.
If you bring the factors into your life.
From there we get fame and recognition
People in the overall society are very loyal to them.
I believe that it will be useful to others.
They are and can be trusted.
He never deceives anyone in time.
If the sun is not in the flick
Conflicts Will Be Seen With The Mother Like This
That's why they get a little bit with their mother.
Becomes irritable temperament because now
For the mother, which is the seventh house i.e. the tenth house
If the sun comes in it, then that means your nature.
He is dominating over the mother.
Do you go to any of your mother's things or
Whatever is your nature on any advice,
Gets a little irritable which isn't
It should be the same temperament if yours were right
You are the one who rules the hearts of the people.
Here can be the Sun of the 10th  House
Tells you this along with the spouse that we
It would be said that the mother of the husband is
You will also find that sometimes they behave.
Dictatorship is like a father
It happens that if you believe me, then their
If you take your nature as a guru, you walk
That the advice they are giving you
You can take the advice as a prominent guru.
If you take it as a big one, then it is big.
Overall Sun in the 10th House will be fruitful
Your ability to bring you fame
The soul wants you to get status and that
You will get only the factors of the Sun which are the father.
Mother, your guru, mentor by your morality.
Such a person should never be left in the sun
11th
When the Sun comes in the house 11th  house
The native has this mind that I have a community
I also have a status inside me.
People also know me that my social circle is.
There's something about me in between.
And the social circle of the native is very
It grows up everywhere.
There are jugaads because if there is
If the Sun is weak, then the native is afraid of many people.
If the sun is going to be found here.
If it is strong, then it is of the ego of the native.
Because of this, his social circle does not grow.
It is a matter of understanding that Trishadaya is the feeling of despicable
The sun of the native has become so big here.
The social circle will give them recognition everywhere.
That's where you get your work from.
Through which they can make a lot of their gains.
It is generating different sources of income.
Take
The sun is here from the ninth to the third.
The sun goes in with the Father
Conflicts arise here.
Either the father is in the job of tour and travel.
Or you can be in such a job.
In which they travel and with their father.
There should not be much interaction and this interaction
Due to this, his relationship with his father deteriorated.
Or after some time from the father.
They become as far away from them as if they ever did.
If you don't get it later too much.
Let the sun suffer here and here.
Their desire is that this is a
Leadership qualities are like those in them
But that leadership quality is not self-worthy.
If you are not able to express, then they need it.
It happens that four people sit near them.
Talk and the leadership that is inside them.
There is quality so that you can tell him that look.
We also know something, avoid them too.
People also understand their feelings i.e. Sun
In the 11th house, it only says that the native
The social circle that you have is within a limit.
You should keep as many circles as it is for them.
They are very protective of their desire.
Big protective of their desires
They are quite overpossessive.
For Friends
But because of that ambition, it has been able to find itself many times.
Many times they insult them.
Friends, their social circle many times.
They remove them from the same circles that are circles.
They have created what they call the human being.
The empire that you have built many times
If it is removed from the empire, then here it is
But the native tries to help his
Friends, or whatever they wish for.
To fulfill theirs, but he has that desire.
Because of the completion, it does not get that importance
Won't be found or the fame for which
He works so hard
Here if the sun suffers too much
In such a situation, the person who is his first
He has a child, he has a great hatred for him.
She can't get through her first child or her first.
The behavior of the child towards him
It's not a good education, it's very good.
The sun gives it here because the seventh
If you look at the fifth house from your point of view, you will see a lot of
Well-educated people are good people.
Education they have gained, hired
I try to go to education all the time.
If there is Saturn in their trine somewhere together.
If they come, such people would try to become lawyers.
Where they are associated with the government.
Conflict can be eliminated if Saturn is in their
How will it come in trine or
So, are you in the third house or Saturn is in the seventh house?
Whether it is in the house or Saturn is one house ahead of them.
Nevertheless, the combination of Sun and Saturn is a lover.
Could work as good as
Here's the full number of them.
Tries to fulfill the desires that are there
But try to tell them one thing here.
What does it take for you to be born?
It was done to fulfill your wish, but
For the fulfillment of that desire, you have given your morals.
Something like that in the force or something wrong in the force.
Don't want to do that because of which your fame is
Or are your desires in society?
Wish fulfillment is there, stop it, see ninth.
Went from the third to the Sun i.e. Joe
Morality is in your mind, how do you do that?
If you put effort into it, you put effort into it.
If you put it wrong, you spoiled the ninth house.
Spoiled the 11th house and the fifth house is also bad.
You did it only by following your moral strength.
I want to help someone with my family.
The more you do at this time, the more your
Wishes will be fulfilled because the Sun is a
It is a family in itself, that is, like the sun
That the planet that runs the family is the father, isn't it?
If it is very difficult, then it is here that the house runs
But because of the wishes of the native, those specials
He spent a good time with his children.
Unable to spend time with his family
Couldn't do it, keep it in your wishes.
Due to which he would degrade his sun.
Going i.e. your sun if
If you want to keep strong, then educate yourself.
Keep doing the same with your social circle.
Spend as much time as he does in your work.
Hang Na
The second from the tenth is the second from the tenth.
That is, the other has gone from the field of karma
If you do work, money will be made from there.
Money will also be made and you will do whatever you want.
You can fulfill your wish through your actions.
But that's what I would like to say about my father.
Relations with you can be a little bad
But never thinking of the father's disinterest
A man who thinks of his father's disinterest
The 11th house is full of his wishes.
It is complete, so what they did
Let it be your field of action and your ego.
Keep on fulfilling the desires as long as
You will keep thinking about fulfilling your desires.
You will continue the day you stopped thinking about desire.
On that day you will feel that the life of me
It's important that it's going to end and my
The soul is weakening, so the desires
It is also necessary to make and fulfill the desire.
It is also necessary to make efforts for the 12th
house
When the Sun  is in the 12th house, then in such a situation
The soul purpose of the native is only
Spirituality Meditation Charity and
Transformation happens that the soul of the native
Just want some change all the time or with it.
Changes automatically
It is his understanding that I
What do I understand about my life?
I have come here to do the 12th price loss.
The 12th house is of your foreign travel.
Sun is in good placement so you are foreign.
I go and work at a government post.
Sun can work in Embase
If good and if the Sun in Navmash is sixth
If you go into the house and suffer, then it is like this.
Many people may be in jail
Do you stay admitted in the hospital?
Any disease in the bones through fracture
Weakening of bones Calcium
Due to lack of hospitalization, they have to be hospitalized.
I have to go again and again if you
If you don't want to go to the hospital, then as much as you want.
Charity is as much as it is in your life.
It's a little bit of calming your soul.
If the soul does not let it suffer,
If the Sun becomes debilitated in the 12th  house, then it
First of all, your
Reduced disease and hospital visits
It does it because if it becomes despicable here.
That is, it has changed the sixth house from the seventh point of view.
See, through which you have a disease repu loan.
They end up living in insecurities.
You can't sit with four people.
He tries to isolate himself.
Keeps overly focused inside yourself
The person is going to think within himself that
What do I have to do to talk to him only?
It happens because don't look at the 12th  house.
Isolation means loss
What is the loss of own entity?
Loss is the loss of one's own personality.
When the person sees that it is mine.
Entity is losing again and again or it
He himself changes his personality again and again.
If so, he starts to understand what
What's happening in the world on this day?
Nature becomes such that again and again
Changing Personalities 12th House
If there's sun in it, if it's too off-flick.
If the sun has come in then you will find either the Father
Will be in foreign country if not in foreign
They are very much in health here.
There will be issues due to which the family will be on the native.
Too much burden of responsibilities
Then he comes and ends his desires.
By doing this, the responsibility of the entire family is yours.
Shoulder Takes
Sun is in the 12th house to the human being.
Asks you to work consistently.
Above your personality, you can define your personality.
Just keep changing this change.
Transformation of one personality of yours
Therefore,  the Sun of the 12th house will never be refined.
one
You shouldn't be the same work.
The Sun in the 12th  house should not be used.
You must meditate and do yourself.
Be sure to stick to spiritualism
And if the sun is low here, then?
This is a yoga factor Sun, for this you need to
Don't be afraid, Yoga Karaka means Sun
This is how the Libra Sun is.
The natives interact with a lot of people.
They must be Libra zodiac sign which is intellect.
They talk to foreign people.
Communicates more than the sun
It is also  in the 12th house, so more than you here.
The circle will be related to the foreigner
By visiting your family or Father Foreigner.
If you are working in the 12th house of the Sun, then you will be working in the 12th  house.
The person should not have his insecurities
I want to know what people will think of me.
People will insult me
People become sensitive to what others think.
This other man is very upset.
He's willing to give his all for him.
They do a lot of charity.
It's good to do charity, but you have also
Let's see if this will affect my family or
I am not having trouble with my wealth.
In sensitivity, sometimes you do so much.
Let me tell you that later on
If there is a problem, then understand the native here
That is by eliminating my insecurities.
I have to understand what my personality is.
Self-realization is made for the thing itself
I want to understand that I
What am I on this earth because God gave you that?
Sent that either you get up from here and go.
Change the place of change again and again.
The native has to place or he has to
You have to be so far away from your father at one time.
He understood the world again on this day.
It seems that  the 12th house Sun is the soul of the native.
The only thing that demands change is just any change.
One habit can't be kept by any one person.
Can't stay with you for a long time abroad
If you go away, try to settle there.
I won't spend too much time with my father.
Find these people who talk to us 12
All about the Sun in the houses of the Sun
Temperament needs to be understood
The sun flour in the sun is the wheat if the sun
If the sun is weak, then the native should
Wheat allergy is what we call it.
Whose native has a debilitated Sun in his horoscope
That person has to take a lot of sunlight.
It's more important because nowhere else.
Somewhere less the influence of the Sun in his horoscope
So when the native takes the sun rays on himself.
If so, he will find that in his confidence.
How is that sun range getting built?
When will he get out, when will he get out?
When he thinks that I need the sun.
You have to get the light and it will come out.
You will get out and meet people.
Will interact due to which his
Confidence will automatically build up to the low.
A person with the sun mostly isolates
Likes to be alone and
At the same time, the person who is the sun of the exalted
People interact with their emotions.
Understands their behavior adapts
And makes such a change in one's own soul.
That the native will expose himself in front of others.
He is able to make people feel attracted to him.
If it is
This is the fruit of the Sun  in the 12 houses that we have seen
If there is variation in fruits, then this person
Should see that the sun in my Navmash
Where is he in which zodiac sign is he in Navmash?
Where is the zodiac sign in my ascendant house?
The Sun has a very large domain of the Sun
There is no small domain in the sun body
Lungs are the factor of bones, the factor of the heart
of
The sun is the significator of the liver, the father's factor is food.
There is a factor of wheat in the weight factor
Sun is your ethics, the Sun is morals.
Your ego is the sun, your status is all these.
All these causative elements are included in the expression.
Add it to the house in which the Sun is
I got connected to this feeling and the fruits of the sun.
We will meet again and talk on some other session.
In the next video, you will see that
In which house is the Sun in my zodiac sign?
The factors of that amount are inside
Let's see it with the sun until then.
Thank you Jai Shri Ram Jai Shri Krishna