Jai Shri Ram Jai Shri Krishna Welcome to Our
YouTube Channel Refine Vedic Astrology
Today's session that we are going to understand is
About the Virgo sign. Virgo Sign
About Virgo when your 12 houses
What comes in for all the Ascendants?
We get to see the affected fruit Virgo
About the zodiac sign because see which is Virgo
Isn't that the only amount of such a thing?
Whose lord comes in his own zodiac
It is of high quality. Anyone you see the plan.
Collect. Sun is exalted in Aries
Venus inside the aries sign is Pisces
Inside the zodiac are exalted in pisces
s
Mars is in the sign. exalted in Capricorn
Saturn in
Libra's are exalted inside the zodiac.
gurus exalted in Cancer Sign
Cancers are exalted inside the zodiac sign.
The moon is there. Going exalted in Taurus
(a) Calculate the value of the product. Inside the Taurus sign and Rahu
Inside Gemini and Ketu in Sagittarius
inside.
But Mercury alone is the planet that has its own
They are higher only by coming into the zodiac sign.
It's a very understandable thing about that.
What is it that comes inside Virgo?
Possess the possession of the Self
Whoever has it, he comes to that zodiac sign and is high.
Becomes and Venus like Planet that zodiac sign
I go and become degraded. See Joe
Virgo is in classical text, isn't it?
It has been called the amount of Shad Ripu that means.
It includes lust, anger, greed, attachment, ego, service.
Everything is there. And Mercury which is the source of our intellect.
It also shows that when the intellect of a human being is in
When his intellect moves beyond things,
Working somewhere higher or higher
It is worthy. And this
Inside the zodiac that we see also the constellations
Those who come to Uttara Phalguni Hasta Nakshatra
chitra constellation comes i.e. of the Sun
Moon and Mars. When it comes to the three constellations
When you come, you will find the Sun Soul Factor
is. Moon is the thought factor and Mars is our significator
Shows the efforts. When the human intellect
Control him over all three of his things.
(a) Calculate the value of the product. He gives his soul his own accord.
It can run. That is, what is in your soul?
Ideas are to come up with ones that show that
In the soul, there is the mind, the intellect and the sanskars which
That is told. That is, such a person has his own
Souls can also be treated in this way through their intellects.
He can walk on the path where he does good deeds.
You can serve. What is the constellation of the Moon?
Hasta nakshatra which is the significator of the mind of the Moon
is. Such a connection between the human mind and the intellect
Make it so that he can serve. Mars
Nakshatra Nakshatra which is our efforts
(a) Calculate the value of the product. It is seen that the human being
The intellect can make such good efforts that
They serve others through their efforts.
Sak. That is, it is understandable that the intellect
The linkage of our soul, our mind and our
Karma, much more than our efforts
There is linkage. When the native does these three things.
On top of that, he would have strengthened his intellect so much.
That he got all three of them kind of good.
Align. Then the intellect of the native is supreme.
It happens. Where the planet Mercury comes exalted
They become them. Now if Mercury in Virgo
If we are of higher age, then we are normally as a lemon.
What would you say in the form? Humans Grow Up
It will be of analytical mind. Serving well
It will be. But even in that service, he
Will try to see the benefit.
That's what we try to see as nature.
But if on the side of a spiritualism
Let's see. What should a normal person do?
If Virgo is in your 12th house wherever
We're going to talk about that now.
Before that, it is very important to understand Virgo a little bit.
It's more important. Look at Virgo.
It is the nature of the way she will go into it.
Your work, anger, greed, attachment,
The ego will remain trapped in that emotion.
You get out of that lust, anger, greed, infatuation.
Can't come. As long as you have your intellectual
Intellectual intellect to you so high
Don't take to the level that you can take these three
The nature of the constellations is their
Lord's you make those temperaments your intellect
(a) Calculate the value of the product. Until then, that intellect
There is no sattvic intellect. Because Mercury
The planets that are shown somewhere in us
are.
Ah, Prince. Factors of Sun Father,
Factors of Mother Moon and
Mars, who is our general, means a king,
The queen and the commander. When Mercury is in this constellation
All three of them are found here.
It goes as a family, it is three.
Trying to protect the constellation Mercury
Do princes as given the method
It is the planet Mercury. That's why when a human being has his
Father, mother, respect for your elder siblings
Begins to respect somewhere.
The native has his
Balance Mercury in the natal chart
And your Virgo's nature is as age-a.
Align as a service. That's
The reason that today we chose that Virgo
Let us have a little discussion on that. This session
What is the meaning of Virgo
Varo Rashi When It Falls in the Nettle Chart.
Virgo can come anywhere in 12  houses
is. Everyone's ascendant is different. Shaad for everyone
Ripu will be different. Everyone's greed is tempted by Maya
It will be different. Someone to try your best
Greed is illusion. Someone has their own family.
It is from. Someone has it from his wife, someone has it.
It's from your son. Sleep Different Types
The attachment is Maya. That's what we try to understand.
How will the natives escape from this temptation?
You can choose a good path for yourself.
Where he also improves his physical intellect.
Align with and Virgo trades
They can also align.
There is one more thing to understand in this. See Joe
Saturn is a planet, isn't it, through Virgo?
When they leave, they are of the highest
Go to Libra. That is, in Libra
When Saturn is exalted, it is very service-doing.
It happens. A man who serves others.
It happens. But it is to be understood that the sixth house
Virgo, which is this zodiac sign, it is the first sign for you.
It teaches you how to serve. The Biggest Joe
Industrialists you will meet
NGOs will be somewhere high of their own.
They are sitting with a Saturn of the rank because
He served before, now he serves.
They employ other people.
Therefore, Saturn is exalted in Libra
Before that, when transiting from Virgo.
It comes out inside the personality of a human being.
A sense of service is attached. He was in the
A service by rising a little bit above the Ripu debt
Nature builds its mind above the intellect
is. That's the reason that Saturn in Libra
The karmic factor that goes and becomes of the higher
Planet in Libra then exalted
When he will have these three tendencies i.e.
It must have come out from inside the three constellations.
His intellectual intellect so smoothly
Will it be workable or Libra's
I have a nature to kiss the person in front of me.
In what tone or behavior to talk or
How do I serve him then over there?
Saturn is exalted. What we have just understood
That Saturn also passes through these three constellations.
It has to go through. When there is Libra
They have to be high. So when
Mercury-like planet in these three constellations
When you come, consider a person to be your original religion.
Should you have ah mercury exalted.
Unless you serve your wisdom which
It's not well aligned somewhere.
Somewhere you are stuck in fear debts.
Transit of Mercury whenever you are on a Jupiter-like planet
If you are in conjunction, then you will find that
You are able to understand yourself somewhere.
What exactly do I have to do with personality?
It has to be done. So that's the nature of Virgo.
We have to understand how this amount is going to be spent.
Be aligned within your life. Har
The zodiac sign has a different temperament. Individual
The constellations come inside them. So who is the girl?
The nature of the zodiac is that it shows up somewhere.
is. Seeing Age a Kaal in the Horoscope of a Male
are. The sixth house is that of the disease Ripu debt.
The sixth house is that of conflicts. 6th House
It is of service. That you as a service.
If you do a job or do you do service as a job?
In the form of that, you take a penny. Wealth
They generate their own. But the sixth house is that
There is also a service, in exchange for which you will get some service.
I don't get money in the form of
It adds to your actions. Because when
If Saturn passes through Virgo
The account of your deeds of Virgo
It will be inside i.e. as your service.
What did Saturn do to the person in front of you?
When you come out of that Virgo zodiac sign
Those deeds are accounted for and when Saturn
If you belong to the higher then which you serve as
If I did something, he would give you the result.
are.
Therefore, this amount should not be taken for granted.
Rashi causes quarrels. This amount is a loan.
She gives you it. Now, if a person has a
A very big industry has to create employment. When
If he does not take a loan, then one of his industries
Can't build. But if his mind
Let this thought sit on top of the intellect's sanskar.
That the industry I want to set up is employment.
You have to invest in order to give. So somewhere he
He is also aligning his Mercury and he is Saturn
You also have to align and this three
Whatever the lords are inside the constellations,
Moon and Mars are also their only one.
Through thought, he aligns me that
Employment has to be given. Something as a service to me
It has to be done for the people. It is a very profound thing.
Who understands the concept of this Virgo today?
Won't he understand to a great extent from his Shadri?
I'll find out why I did this and I
What should be done now? The sign that is the category
It's an emotionless sign. He is a practical sign.
We have to do a practical work.
Your emotions are that you have to serve.
Emotions won't help. Doing it with hands
It will be. You have to do it practically. As long as
If you don't do that work practically, then
It will add to your karma smoothly
Nope. Therefore
This amount will come in whatever price it will come from this amount
You will become emotionless from there. But
Practically, you work on it very much.
You will. For Example of the Topic
Leocentente is. Virgo in the 2nd House
It comes. This man has been for money all his life.
He will keep running. But in the end of money
Doesn't value. Becomes Emotionless
For money. Yes, I want to make money.
I want to serve my family.
I have to do it. Such a person, such a person
As an Servant for the Family
Works all his life. That he understands that
I have an obligation to give up my family.
There's a lot to do. Behind the Money
Will run. No doubt that money is not behind
Will run. But money is not value.
He is emotionless about money. Someone to take
Somebody is giving, give, give.
It becomes emotionless. Practically, he
Doing work. So we have given this amount to this.
The zodiac sign has to be understood something like this.
In which place of ours, in what house, how do we?
How are we emotionless and how we are practically
Let's work on that. See Kaal Purush.
It comes in the sixth house in the horoscope of
Amount. From where we say attachment to Maya
This is the amount. Man trapped in delusion
(a) Calculate the value of the product. As long as the native is tempted by this illusion
Until he leaves, he will be able to get out of his house somewhere.
Actions are not directed towards the higher. Such as
We initially explained how Saturn Libra
They are high in their zodiac signs. Now here
But if the factors that have been considered in this amount
If you look at the horoscope of Kalpurush, then Mars
There are factors here. Come in the sixth house.
That's because here Mars has these three
By the constellations i.e. King for
Exemplar King Queen and Own Nakshatra
is. Sun, King, Moon, Queen and Mars
The Senapati himself, that is, the Senapati, so much.
Freedom is found that they openly
Can serve. Fighting openly
Maybe. So Mars is the factor here.
So understand that a person gets freedom.
That is, if Mars is in the sixth house and Virgo is in the sixth house.
Mars is inside the zodiac. In your sense
Mars is in Virgo. You are not in that house.
I will work as a freedom that I will do this.
I won't come to the place and listen to anyone.
Like a king and queen telling me a commander.
You have been given the responsibility to do what you have to do.
Do. We only need this state to be secure.
should. So when Mars is in Virgo, someone
Even within the emotion, that emotion is a human being.
Tries to save as commander
And that freedom for him is like that for him.
It happens that he is in this house, i.e., the second house.
If I am like Leonant and of the second house
If Mars sits inside, then such a person will have his
Families protect their finances and their wealth
For he has so much freedom that he
It can go to any extent. That opposite time
It also has the ability to fight against.
It is the meaning of the Virgo sign. & Tue
There are factors here. That's because he
He is a warrior. To fight those who
You need an environment. Fight a warrior
What do you need for? Weapons are needed
Or do you want the freedom to do what you want to do?
Do. We just need to win. So, with a hundred weapons.
Even more freedom. So the sixth which is the zodiac sign
Virgo is Mars there as a significator
That's why they have freedom there.
It is found. So if you have a mangal
Mars in the Virgo sign is the house in which
You must have had the freedom to feel that
Securing the price you want
You have. It is the sign of calculation. It
Is the sign of analytical. Analysis
The feeling is that inside this zodiac sign, the person has his own mind.
Wisdom and scope according to your efforts
Begins to do an analysis inside that
How do I do this work? 4th House
If Virgo is coming in, then what do you?
We'll see how people are inside the house.
Analysis continues. Such a person
The intellect that is at home will not be outside.
Because he would have found such an atmosphere when he came home.
is. His mind starts to do such a thing
That he can make the biggest calculations comfortably.
It does. Even the biggest puzzle is very much
Can solve easily. Because he has
That atmosphere inside the house is found in Virgo
That's where these three constellations are in a way.
Align well with his intellect
Let's act.
The sixth zodiac sign, Virgo, is a routine sign.
It also shows that if the native has to take his shad ripu
You need to get rid of debts,  any of your bad things.
If you want to get rid of habit, then a routine should be removed.
You have to follow. If you want to be free from loan, then
You have to work in a routine. I am sick of the disease.
If I want to be free, then I have medicine in routine.
It has to be taken. Take care of health in routine
It will be. These people are health conscious.
Virgo will come in the house in which you will be
Whatever family relations you have towards
That person will be very health conscious. Jis
You will get a routine towards that house
Will be oriented. If it is coming in the fourth house, then
If you want to do housework, then stay in routine
Yes, I have to clean up here.
If I want to make changes in this house, then the routine
You will work in the form. Coming in the 7th House
is. You will find that you will have partners
There will be big routine oriented. What you'll find
Relationship with your partner is in a way
Someone in it as a routine for both of you.
You will work together and your nature is done.
I want to go here with my spouse.
If you want to go with your partner, then he should go into the routine.
If you want to go and serve with them, then
Will you talk to them in a routine way?
If you want to do it, then it will be a routine that we
We have time to communicate with each other.
I will talk to you nicely, whatever it means.
Virgo comes under the house. From there
You also get involved in the routine. This human being
Gives charming personality. Why
Gives? Look at having such a personality that
The person in front of you is attracted very quickly.
Go. Virgo comes in the sixth house.
Virgo who is in the 12th  of the relationship
It falls. Where Venus becomes debilitated
are. If a person is in lust, anger, greed
Get stuck
Off the Topic If only in lust, anger, greed
If you are stuck, Venus is debilitated there.
It becomes that this person is your
Leaving the comforts in your life
Comfort should be made by exploiting them,
Anger, greed, attachment, arrogance in these things
Trapped. Then go and Venus is debilitated.
goes. And one thing is when Venus is debilitated.
Is it? When the native hates his relationship
When someone else establishes a relationship
Venus becomes debilitated there.
Debilitated. Because Venus is a
It has been called a planet of character. Thanksgiving
It has been called the planet of indulgence. But
Indulgence from whom? Indulge Luxurious Your Spouse
For your family, for your partner. And Joe
The sixth zodiac sign is that it shows our Shad Ripu.
is. Sexual desire due to human work
He would have established a new relationship with him.
is. Under the influence of anger, the person in front of him
Ditch does. Man succumbed to greed
He takes advantage of the front. Ego
He started humiliating the person in front of him.
goes. That is, lust, anger, greed, attachment,
Under the influence of arrogance, such a person will turn his Venus
Somewhere, debilitated his
It does. Despicable. Hence Venus
It is the best remedy. If that Virgo
If the amount is debilitated within then in this case
The native should be able to deal with these five vices as much as possible.
You should try to control that much.
That I have my husband with my
Establishing a relationship with a partner
Physically it's a good thing. But apart from them
Doing it with someone else is degrading Venus.
Yes. You are destroying semen. Where Joe
When we have energy in the body, when we have energy in the body.
Semen
If we are joined in one form, then the human being is connected.
A great good connection with the intellect of
It is formed. A yogic intellect is formed and its
You see a look on a person's face.
There is an attraction. So when does that happen?
When Venus is exalted. When Venus is like this
Pisces is in the zodiac sign where
Vairaga attitude arises. See if
If Venus were to be exalted, Libra
Those who are high in the zodiac are those who are in front of
I want to meet people. Okay? Apni Swara
The amount could have been. But in Pisces
Venus is exalted. Why? Because of the
When a person has a detachment instinct. When
Let there be an instinct to leave in a human being. Joe
Pisces is the sign that shows loss. That
The human tendency in our instincts
What will happen?  Will it be to leave or to be caught?
Will it happen? The sixth amount is to be caught. 12th Zodiac
Pisces is about to leave. Then go high there.
What is Venus? And for the native who
Life's comforts are behind him.
They come running away. Because inside of him, these
He is a little out of lust, anger, greed, attachment,  ego.
He has risen so high that he has these disorders.
Doesn't get stuck inside. Even if you have
It will look like it works. He has luxury
There's a car, there's money. He is like this in talking.
But somewhere in his mind, he
The mind has abandoned those things. Now
Let's talk about all the Ascendants
That for every Lagna the Joyk sign of the Vargo
It comes into the feeling of what the fruit will be. Now this
You have to watch the video in such a way that you are married.
Also look at the basis of the Vargo Zodiac
Sign Virgo is coming in which house of yours
And also see the corresponding chart of D Namash
That what sign is my Virgo there?
Coming in. Which house are you coming into?
is. You don't have to do a little calculation with this.
It would be very easy for me to feel this way.
You also get to see the fruits of this feeling and of this house.
You can also see fruit. So both D1
According to both the and D9 charts, you can
Watch the video. Let's start now.
When Virgo comes inside the first house.
When Virgo comes within the first house,
This is the sign of Mercury. The prince's zodiac sign.
It is in the ascendant. So the nature of such a person
They will look much younger than their age.
There will be. They look young because
If you are a prince, you follow them from the beginning.
Nurturing that says that nurturing nature is what it is
She would have met her parents very well
is. Sharp-minded, calculative
(a) Calculate the value of the product. Routines are oriented.
Because the sixth house of Virgo, this
Your nature is to stick to a routine. Any work
We will do it in a routine manner. De R
Very good in the math and physics. These
It can be very good within the subjects.
And let's try to use this field.
You can choose your profession only
Because the calculations or analytics of theirs
The mind is very sharp. So,
It can help any business grow very quickly.
Let's calculate that this is in this business.
There will be such losses and such losses will be there. So, it
Their brains are the same things.
Remains more aware of where
But more work of calculation or analysis
It happens. These people quickly get along with someone.
Mix-ups can't happen. Why?
Because that is the nature of Virgo.
Libra is a two-year-old. So Joe
This is the 12th amount to be received.
Due to this mix-up quickly from someone
They can't be vibes unless someone else's vibes
There should be no match with the person in front. It
Let's try to have a lifestyle
Be very healthy. He was very health conscious.
are. Routines are oriented. These people are like this.
Those who like to eat a little bit of levish
They like eating those things a little bit.
Because the prince should not forget that
The planet that has this amount is in itself.
The prince is among the nine planets. So that factor
The element that is inside this zodiac sign is yours.
Definitely get it.
Let's try to be very hygienic.
Stay clean and try to do that.
Not everything can be done perfectly.
Because the sixth house which comes to Virgo
This would have been the basic principle of Virgo.
That is lust, anger, greed, attachment, ego
I have to overcome everyone and go towards service.
If then you are an ascendant, Virgo Ascendant.
And this constellation of yours falls in it.
It is the constellation of the moon. Meaning
That when you were born this Virgo axis
But she had gone so far from this earth that
Then he was exposed to the constellation of the moon.
Inside Virgo. You were born in it.
So, what will you see is your nature?
That would be a nurturing nature. Even if you're a Virgo
The natives of the zodiac are but those who have a nurturing nature.
The nature of the moon is what you have.
Inside you will definitely find because at the time when it
When the ascendant was rising, the moon
The constellation was inside Virgo at that time.
Actually, they are very emotional. It's so
They are emotional if they are with someone.
If there is a grudge, then it should not revenge it.
Their ability to take increases. On Ego
It comes to the point. It's for everything.
Let's sacrifice. Serving them
Sounds good, but hiding it from people.
Expose your service to others
They don't let it happen. And As I Said 20 to 30
At the age of
It's in the people around them.
Personality cannot be seen. Because
If you want to see the personality of the prince, then he
To see you at the age of 20 to 30  years.
It will be found. Sometimes it becomes greedy
That I have to fulfill my motive. That
To fulfill the motive of someone, it is someone's
Don't care. The one who is Shad.
From Ripu comes that greed. I want to use my
Desires have to be fulfilled. I wish
You don't have to complete it. That Wish Fulfillment
For me to hurt anyone's mind or...
I have to hold someone back because
They were always in preparation for the competition.
are. This is the zodiac sign of competition.
If it falls within the 6th house, then the 6th house here
Virgo's 6th house also shows your competition
It is that such a person is in this situation all the time.
I live in a competition arena
And I have to be ahead in everything. That
They have a tendency. This greed and infatuation
That I have to always put myself ahead. Me
You have to benefit yourself. First of all, this shad.
Ribu is always ready to harass them.
Stands. Get rid of this thing like this.
It can be found that when it serves as
Let's do that for the second first
Then I think about myself.
I'll take it. Let me serve the second first.
I'll give it to you and I'll think for myself. When
This feeling will not be revealed in the mind then.
Till the Virgo zodiac sign which is the shad ripu is somewhere.
Don't always see them in their personalities.
It will continue to be received. Now let's talk about Vargo
Sign in the Second House. It Means You Are
Leo Assentant. When inside the second house
When Virgo comes, this thing shows that
The native has a lot of interest in financial related things.
You have to struggle. In the 2nd House
Virgo is coming. Of the Daripu loan amount
There is a lot of debt on such a person.
Live. That is, more than the income of the native.
You will find that this is your own income.
They repay 50 to 60%  of it in the loan.
Live. Many sources of income are
These. It depends on different incomes from the source.
They create different sources. From where it comes from
Let's add up your money. It is also selected
That's what we do in the profession.
Can you get into a field like finance or
Where we talk through communication
Put it in front of other people.
Disputes happen with the family.
Just because of the main source of finance or
Wealth. With his family about this.
There are malices. See when Virgo
If it comes in the second house, then the native's no.
He becomes a sacrificial nature.
As a service to his family.
Does. But saw that service.
It doesn't go to the family. The same thing to them.
It knocks inside. Same thing for Shad Ripu
Forcing man to hate
She gives so much to the family that she
Sacrifices more, but that
Sacrifice is not seen. Such
The native is always very concerned about his finances.
He is very upset and worried that
How can they increase their savings? Butt Give
Are very well in the binance. It's also from the job.
Very good business
(a) Calculate the value of the product. Can do it very well
are. Where analysis is done,
It is the work of analytical work.
Very well in the field even within the job.
It can work. They Can Make Any Kind Off
Binance and They Can Indulge in the Family
Business Also. It's inside the family business.
They can also work very well. But the
One thing is through its efforts.
You can earn money. That's because the sixth
The sense is of service. As a Service
You can work for someone at work.
Whether you are in front of the service
They're giving people something. That too for service.
It is equal. That is also equal to service.
But if this feeling is added to that service.
That I'm doing something about it. And God
Do it well. So when this feeling comes to mind
If they join, they will find that their bank
Balance that increases their bank balance
He'll go into the people around him.
Nor will it be. That is, they are rich in speech
What people say is becoming true.
goes. When they begin to serve in this spirit
are.  Putting in a lot of effort in the beginning
They have to take care of their family and wealth.
These. They show that money is everything.
There is some. They show it, but from the inside.
They are emotionless for money or wealth.
Such a person does not value money.
Like a king, he is the giver of money.
He is liberated from the temptation of money. When
This nature seems to be the nature of these natives
So he is somewhere in the wealth for himself.
Different resources begin to open. Because
The Virgo zodiac sign that they have got in the second house
She shows that the native as long as the money
As long as he is attached to it,  he will be in pain.
It will remain. The Virgo that we started with
Talked about that it tries to inflict suffering
As long as you do these shad ripu work, anger, greed,
They don't come out of that feeling because of attachment or arrogance.
The day you get out of that disorder
If you are in your mind, then it will be positive for that feeling.
Starts treating because Joe
The same feeling of pain hurts.
It also does prevention. If this feeling hurts you.
If Ribu has the same feeling, then the same feeling is of service. When
As Charity as Human Service
When you start using your money
He sees that there are a lot of sources for me.
They start making income. Let's talk now
There are Virgo signs. Virgo when the third house
Let's come in. It Means You Are Cancer
Assentent. You will not find that people
Neither of their colleagues, relatives or siblings
More of their friends would have been of great use.
are. Colleagues who are where they work.
The people who are there are for them.
They remain very good. New to them
The path is always open. Now see Virgo
What is the nature of the zodiac in the 3rd house?
goes. The native wants to say a lot.
Venting your emotions wants a lot
But he can't say. Why? Because
When Virgo comes inside the 3rd house.
Virgo Sign When in the Third House Native
The native is trapped in these shad ripu that
If I speak from my heart, then
The person in front of me will use me. On
Most of the time you will find that people are using them.
They use it and go away. Whenever this is your
Let's try to speak our minds.
In the beginning, these people get irritated very quickly.
Let's go. When they have someone in front of them.
Humans come. They get irritated from there.
Or they become angry in nature. When
When Someone Is Tee Tees Them. And a lot of people
They take advantage of their emotions and go away.
are. See, the third house is of no effort and
Such people are not very good mechanical fields.
Virgo can work because
The nature of service is to give. In Virgo
Mars is a factor because of the effort to exert effort.
They go there and they come to the third house.
Which is also a sense of effort. So when
Virgo falls within the 6th 3rd house
So the native should do the work done by his hands.
Do you get popularity from the work itself?
He is able to sustain himself. So Doz
People Are Very Good In The Mechanical Work Where
But you do it with your hands. End
It shows that these people don't lose in argument.
Don't like it. If you argue with them.
If they are, they won't lose there.
Because competition has become the nature of it.
Virgo came in the third house, did it not?
The nature of Virgo is competition.
The sense of communication is the third house. So when
If you are able to communicate with them.
Talking about any other topic.
Saath tu tu main hogi so till you either shut up
Don't be till then.
Virgo Natives Coming to the Third House
People with cancer additives don't give up
Because there is competition for them.
How am I hiding. Yes, this is the new argument.
They take it out and bring it back. He will definitely do this service.
With your own hands. But where are you?
Communicating with you you just have to lose
It may be silent and lose, or it will go from there.
Go because the nature of the competition is their
Communication comes to mind
Through communication, you win from there.
It's very difficult to get them.
To show their knowledge that they have knowledge
Let's try to tell him friendly.
Nature is big with its neighbors and
With your colleagues, mostly with them.
They like to spend time.
Too much online chatting in today's era
Let's give it time because Virgo
Coming under the 3rd house is your 3rd house
Communication 3rd House Chatting and Virgo
Amount that is with other people
To speak to the form means to the seventh
It's 12th . Whether it's chatting secretly
Even if they chat openly, but they
Chatting definitely has to be done. You can chat with them.
What will you do if you stop it? Hatred against you
We'll do it. Why? Because I chatted.
Why did you take it? Because there is no third house, no media.
And in the media like House when Virgo
If the zodiac comes, then such a person should say his word.
Wants whether through communication
Say it through conversation, even in your speech.
Say it through, say it through chatting. But
He will definitely say. He won't be able to keep it in his mind
That's it. And that's why the ever-car
Harsh uses speech. Bad Words
Let's use it. Due to which their
Arguments are made. And that's it.
Arguments would turn into fights
are. Because of which there is a fight. Sleep
Virgo in the Third House for the Cancer
Ascendant, they should keep in mind that I
When and where to speak, how much measure. His
They should speak accordingly. Your Efforts
When you use the service with your own hands
Do anything with your own hands.
Feed it. Something to a needy person.
Give it to me. When They Use Their Hands As
A charity. Then they understand that their
How do blessings of the 3rd house work?
is. Because when the sixth zodiac sign in the 3rd house
If Virgo is coming, you will find it in front
Which is exactly Pisces coming to the ninth.
Inside the House. Pisces in the Ninth House
Coming means doing the work of blessings. When is that?
Will you meet? When you go from here to the third house.
Virgo is coming, leaving her Shad Ripu
That is, lust, anger, greed, attachment, ego
Doing online chatting linked to the third house
You are. You're using chatting in the bad
Habits. You use bad words with someone.
You are doing it. Harshly using words
to. You use your hands in the wrong things.
You are doing it. You can improve your communication skills.
If you are hurting someone through this, then here
You are spoiling your ninth house.
Because the amount that is coming in front of you is because
Zodiac signs also have vision. That's it.
Care should be taken. So try to do it
Les Talkative. Be a person who speaks less. Low
Speak up when you become a service-doer
So somewhere the people with cancer essences
Virgo falling in his third house
You will be able to use it well. And its factors
Element it is positive within your life.
You will be able to enhance. When Virgo Sign In The
Fourth House Now See Gemininai Ascendant's
For the natives of Gemini Ascendant who are Vargas
It is a sign that comes under their fourth house
Which shows that these people are very much
They are emotionally attached. From your comfort,
With his family and his mother.
But it is their mother who sometimes desires them.
They try to bind because they
There is one who is Shad Ripu, he is a mother somewhere.
It comes out in their lives through or
Through the comfort of home, these people are able to get that Shad Ripu.
They are stuck in that comfort at home.
You get so much that it
The mind that is above their mind is this.
Virgo is in the fourth house.
It becomes very sensitive. Gets emotional
There are too many and their mother is as old as A.
Always for them as a strict teacher.
Work as a mentor mentor mentor
are. Because of which with the mother of the Samaites.
Sometimes, there are grudges. A Negative
The point here is that for them.
Lust, anger, greed or it is inside your mind.
They continue to make it. Virgo when the fourth
If it comes inside the house, then the life of the person is not
I find him comforted in those comforts.
It is life that seems to be the same.
It's my life. So when it's time to struggle
If he comes, he has to give up this comfort
And where he understands that so far
What I was living and how do I live now?
is. So what this shad ripu is comfortable with this person
Let's meet through. Lust, anger, greed, attachment,
The ego that is trapped inside these comforts
He'  s big enough to get ahead in life.
Barely able to move. Therefore, their
As a Mother's Strict Teacher for them
It's a great job to work in and
Mother, we can say that you are of great sense of service.
You can. It means serving others.
Such people are very good to their mother.
You must see that his mother has very good service.
They are the ones who do it. It shows that the mother
He must have struggled too much. Lots
You must have gone through a bad time where they
Be blamed. Virgo who is the sixth
When the zodiac is coming on the fourth house, then the mother
Shows that the mother was ever blamed.
Or because of something or the other.
You are humiliated.
It shows that every comfort, comfort, house,
Car, house, every kind of comfort.
Increases all kinds of greed inside the mind
is. And this is something that they need to understand.
This is the thing that Virgo is inside the 4th house
The native should be guided by the mind and not by speech or intellect.
These things are obsessed with it. Him
She makes such a week out of her mind because her mind
Above it is not lust, anger, greed, mo, ego
There is a whole shadow. Due to which he
It becomes so emotional that your
Starts suppressing things inside
And as they walked, he found himself inside.
Inside, they say, "We keep burning." When he
When he starts to burn, his feelings of mind
All the burns begin and he begins to
Can't express good feelings
from. What should such a person do here?
Anytime with the comforts of his life.
You shouldn't have too much attachment. Infatuation here
What can we say that this is a part of infatuation?
Ribu is more in the mind of the native.
His attitude towards the comforts of his life
There shouldn't be too much temptation. As much as he did those
He abandons things in life as much as he does.
Things go on moving for him and the mind
Begins to have a positive impact on
is. Now let's understand that when the Virgo sign is the fifth
Comes in the sense for the Taurus Ascendant. It
It shows that the first nature of the native is not
It happens, he doesn't say a little bit about his words.
He is going to exaggerate, "Look!
I did it, look, I did it. Knowledge
Sometimes, such a person gets arrogant that
The fifth house is knowledge. The fifth house shows that
Such a person hides reality a little
That reality is something else and that is in front of you.
It shows something to a person. Fifth House
When it comes to Virgo. Here they have to
You get a chance that it will give your opponent or
So you can forgive him or take revenge on him.
You can. Now it depends on here.
How is the placement of Mercury? If Mercury's
If the placement is good, then it will be your opponent.
They forgive me many times.
Because Virgo is his nature.
It is about competition. So, it's a competition for everything.
As I take it as I can also compete.
I can. The thing you're learning.
I can learn too. Such a sense of competition
It comes above the intellect. It was the first child.
is. They are very sharp-minded. and
We can say very active. Which is their first
She will have a child to win every competition.
It stays ahead. Whether it's in dancing, whether
Music is in things, of any kind.
There is an art of entertainment, in which their
We can only say that the first child is big.
Artistic can make everything art.
Understanding and moving forward in it is the form of competition.
in. It shows that the first child has
It can be in the child conceiving of the native.
If there is a problem and it shows that if the first
Have a child through IVF or through surgery
Whether it happened due to these things or the first
There is a lot of pain in the child because
When Virgo has come, then your place is not here.
Attachment to his first child and
With your entertainment and your education
You start getting a little greedy
Here he is tempted that I am every
I want to get an education for my child.
Do something. I'm going to have any kind of
There is competition within the society because
Sit here and the zodiac sign in front of Virgo.
Pisces comes  in the 11th house. So
Sees different ways of socializing
How much is our social status in social?
The build is done. To create that status
Such a person talks a little long.
is. It shows that it is your entertainment
Never think about spending on it.
That where they want to keep their entertainment good.
You have to run from there,  you have to entertain yourself there.
But he doesn't even think about it for a turn.
Before spending money. When Virgo sleeps
If it comes inside the fifth house, then the person will get it.
I should see that I don't get into such competition.
Let me put down the person in front of me.
Should I start showing or am I the person in front of me?
Forget to value it. You have a knowledge.
Someone also has the knowledge. You Have Too
Respect other people's knowledge. You Have Too
Respect Other People Efforts. You Have Too
Respect other people wishes. Because the seventh
The one who is coming in the 11th  sign of Virgo, he
It will show you that the desires in front of you
You also have the ability to complete it.
is. If you have a sense of service. Now we
Let's talk about the Vargas when the 6th house
Comes in for Eris Ascendant. It shows
It is said that such people are very daring
Because the horoscope of Kaal Purush is also of Mars.
It starts with Aries and
If Virgo comes in the sixth house, then a lot
There are more darings. But De Also Have
High sexual desires. 7th to 12th
If you are a Virgo, then it is sexual.
Enhances desires so much that
Humans establish more than one relationship.
Or is he so far away from his partner?
He goes to the husband that he himself
Through meditation, you can help yourself in a chat charity.
Through NGOs Involved Somewhere
He makes those trades in his life.
From where such a person will serve very well.
It may be that this person who serves whomever
Will do it from his heart
It Also Shows They Always Worry About There
Finance, Job, Loan, Repayment. Because the sixth
Virgo came in the house itself. So, over here
Virgo's strength is a little different.
Why? Because in this house and in this house also
This amount is sitting in the same two things.
Let's show the thing. In loan repayment
It's hard to come, it also shows that you
Too much struggle related to finance
You have to do it. Above the mind of the native and
This thing always dominates the mind
That's how I can serve. Of their psyche
It is up above that I can do service. Because
Virgo in the third house from the 4th to the 3rd house
It's coming. Where will the efforts of the mind be?
This is determined by the lord of Virgo.
It will happen that where Mercury will sit, now you will be there.
They are indispensable to serve. You Service
You can do very well by connecting with that feeling.
Aldo You're Having a Very Good Charitable
Nature. Such a person has a charitable nature
That human sacrifice for the person in front of you
There is a lot to be done by doing this. It
Shows that sometimes such a person has his own
Anger creates conflicts
With the person in front. If Mercury Well
If you are placed inside the chart, then such a person
Communication Skill Boy Very Highly
They are active. And these people are not human beings.
Too much to invest in yourself
Let's convince quickly. Most of the
Time you will find that these people who help also
They get it. The luck that they get
You get the opposite sex. If You're Eris
If there is an ascendant male chart, then you will get lady luck.
There will be support. If you're a female and you're
S Ascendant. So the support you will get
Males Gender to Props as a Luck
You will get it. This happens because the seventh
The zodiac sign that is in the 12th  is not Virgo.
Shows you that the person in front of you
They get attracted very quickly.
They mingle very quickly. So nowhere
Somewhere you have the inclusion in front of you.
It happens with humans. Due to which you have to
Seems like it's a very lucky person for me.
is. Now the arrival of Virgo in the sixth house
Aries Assentant. It also shows that till you
As long as you keep the spirit of service in your mind, you will
Your finances, your diseases, your debts,  your
Loans will stay away from all this. But every now and then your
It will come to mind that the person in front of me
It is to be insulted. It is to be insulted. Me
You have to take the money of the person in front of you. Then
You will be surrounded by disease. Aldo you check.
If you've ever had someone's money.
Took it or never got it back.
If you have come from your mind, then you have not come anywhere.
Somewhere the same money must be on your illness.
It will be given. What do such people do otherwise?
There are a lot of hospitals in the form of charity.
They help a lot. Because the 6th house
Always remember that service is about you. As long as you use these
Shads will not be separated from the repo. In infatuation Maya
They will not be separated. Virgo in the 6th house
The zodiac sign is ahh establishing a relationship with the other.
Take. Job, finance, due to these you are other
Ditch people. As long as these things
You don't get good health until you move
Pati. So for a healthy life.
Always a spirit of service towards a human being.
Keep it. When the Virgo Sign Comes in the Seventh
House, So It Means You Are N Pies
Assentent. It shows that of the native.
They have husbands, partners,
Personality is very charming.
And Their Partner Having a High Desire of
Sexually Related Things. His towards him.
There are a little more desires. Now, this Joe
There are natives, by the way, when they are alone.
If you are sitting on top of them,  then someone from Shad or Ripu will be sitting on top of them.
It doesn't matter. Lust, anger, greed, mo,
It's far from arrogance because it's Pisces.
It doesn't matter if you are a native.
They are those who live in meditation. Thinking
They are. Living in your own separate world
They are. But when it's the front
When they meet a human being, they have all this in them.
Lust will awaken. Lust, anger, greed, attachment,
The ego wakes up everything. Why?
Because Virgo comes in the seventh house.
Who in you can grow these things?
When You Meet Someone. When it comes to the front
When you meet a human being, you receive all kinds of vices.
They awaken and do what they never did.
She doesn't even think about the person in front of her.
Let's think about it. A person who
A Practical or Saying Towards Relationship
There is an organized approach that
How to stay in a relationship. He
A little bit of running the relationship according to your own
Trys. This is also the case
See, the person in front of you is not there.
For you, Virgo is the one who
In front of you is this person who
The mind is its own practical mind
He has his own analytical mind if you are.
Spout if you are having a spouse married
If you are your spouse, then your spouse will be big.
He will be wealth-oriented about finance.
There will be more thinking about those who
Practical approach is towards the relationship
There is a grudge in him and when
If that malice happens, then you get trapped inside it.
Let's go. Virgo inside Shad Ripu
The nature of that you have temptation is Maya Kam,
You have to keep them trapped in anger and  greed.
In that sense. So it's those inside the relationship.
All vices come in when it
Relationship with a person in front of you
Establish or limit to it
They start doing more. But, that's it.
It also shows that such a person is in front of
Doing a lot of service to mankind
It can also happen. If the Mercury Is Well Placed
In the Chart. You will find that these are the natives
Pisis Ascendant Wale Ki Upar Us Shadari
It doesn't matter. But it is in front of
They serve people a lot.
It serves your spouse very much
There will be. We can say that people make money from them.
They take them away and never return them.
Because the amount that is coming in front of them is
A finance amount is coming. He is a
The amount of the transaction. In a way, someone from you.
It goes away after taking the loan and not returning it to you.
does. You can understand that. But as long as
You'll keep thinking about that money.
Until those vices are trapped in the disorder of greed.
It will remain. The day it is about that money.
They will stop thinking about their money on their own.
He comes back after turning around. So It Shows That
That this is also such a thing within the relationship.
Want discussion where practical
Matters are talked about. Finance
What do we have to do in daily routine life?
Is it? Most of them and their partners.
There must have been a discussion about how
We Can Communicate and Give Us Your Finance
How to run. How did we live a healthy life?
Jeannie. They are health conscious.
Spouse. So their spouses make them healthy.
Let's try to tell the lifestyle.
Virgo coming inside the seventh house is a
The thing I can tell you is that unless you ...
A sense of service to the person in front of you
Till then, you will stay away from these shadris.
It will remain. When you leave them with a sense of service.
Have an attraction or attachment to them.
Then you will take it towards the person in front of you.
You will find yourself in agony. Your Temperament
Live in your own world. Imagination's
Living in the world. So It Shows When You're
Having a Charity Nature for Other People You Will
Always Away from the Shadrapuran. Remember it
Keep it. When the Virgo Sign in the Eighth
House It Means You Are Not Aquarius
Assentent. This shows that such a person does not
Whatever you get as an inheritance
Whether it is a gift or a real estate, it is never received
Sometimes she can come up in a litigation court case.
They can have a quarrel with someone with him.
It's about that thing and it's about that thing.
They are so infatuated that they are obsessed with it.
They are not able to give. Is it land or is it yours?
He is a small child, you gave him a gift. He
He will be so infatuated with that gift.
That he won't be able to leave her.
He will fight for her. That's what we say.
Why? Because the one who is a girl in the eighth house.
The zodiac sign is the eighth house of inheritance.
The Virgo who sits in it will give you a chance.
Things are tied to Ripu inside that emotion
from. Therefore, of such a person who would also have been a spouse
They are very much about finance.
Let's struggle. His family also did a lot
You must have struggled more money and wealth.
Ranging.
There's a spouse you'll find that he's something like that.
You will not speak with words, but when you do speak,
Will say something like this to the person in front of you?
They say that they should set fire to the inside.
Virgo is in the second house for them.
The second house from the seventh is the eighth.
It also shows that their partners will be
His support for his finances and his family.
There will be a little more awareness. This thing also
They can sometimes get knocked like this. It shows
These people help a lot of people,
However, they do it very secretively. Or else
These people if they are not well placed, mercury
Establishing a relationship with another human being
We'll do it. The work behind concealing it,
Anger, Lo, Mohankar, all the vices of the whole
They will awaken. Because the eighth house
It's secrecy. Eighth House Sexual
There's also Dzire's. It can be such a person
Establish more than one relationship and
All the vices he had to hide
Wake up. It shows that the eighth
Virgo is sitting in the house. Amount of Service
She is sitting. They serve other people.
But never do that service.
Will show. They Are Helping Nature.
But he doesn't have to show off. It's like this.
Natives have specialties. In the same way, you have to
You will see it with your mind. Big Socializing
is. It's a cool dude. This is how to see you.
See you. But a very helpful nature.
What it consists of. Because that's their nature.
This is the nature of the Aquarius Ascendant,
But the one who sits in the eighth house is Virgo.
Yes, it makes a big impact on them.
They will do service, but they won't show it. Give
Somehow the focus on the shortcuts
I can make money quickly. The one who covets
He is now in the eighth house.
(a) Yes, Sir. What is the eighth house? Front-facing
It is the wealth of human beings. Give think that as much as he
Earning money, I can earn as much as I can. No
You can earn through shortcuts. Someone wrong with anyone
You can earn through work. It's If the Mercury Is
Not Well Placed in the Chart with Rahu
If so, you will believe that this person is not like this.
Maybe even involved in drug addiction
Go. If Saturn also influences from above.
Or if Mercury and Saturn are sitting in the eighth
The influence of Rahu comes. So these people are very
More people get into addictions that
It greatly affects their intellect.
Always remember one thing: Give have a pressure.
There is always pressure on them that
They have to change. Finances will change jobs
We will change something to make it. Your
They will continue to change in life because the eighth
The sense is that of transformation. Service also
If you do this, then serve this person today.
There are. Tomorrow, someone else's service.
Will do. Today in this charity this NGO
Doing charity. Tomorrow at another NGO.
Charity will do. That is, as long as it gives itself
Won't transform to service
Will not transform to serve
Until then, they will always be emotionally drained.
Meaning that the emotional that is their emotions is not anywhere.
Neither are they able to drain anywhere. Nickel
Not able to. When they do service, don't they?
So, above those emotions, that attachment to Maya.
That sense of service becomes so great that it
They rise a little above that. No difference
Who's taking their stuff then? Who
Are you playing with their things? Who are their things?
But it is taking a right. Because the spirit of service
It's connected somewhere inside the mind. Her show off
Don't. Working exactly like Ketu
They are engaged. When the Virgo Sign in the
Ninth House It Means You Are N Capricorn
Assentent. Such a person does not enjoy luxury.
Instinct increases. See Capricorn
It is ascendant, otherwise it is work oriented.
are. Too much of your work area
Some believe. But which is their ninth house?
The sixth zodiac sign comes in Virgo, isn't it?
The person becomes very luxurious
More and more of their fathers are great.
It will be service-oriented. Father's Temperament
It is a service
Jai Shri Ram.
It is the nature of the father to serve.
Wala.
They are having a spiritual nature. That would have been
They have to worship God.
is. Whether out of fear or out of spirit of service.
Do it in the form. But they definitely do.
Because above the spirit of spiritualism
The arrival of Virgo. These people for themselves.
They don't think so much about religion as they do.
Think too much. Believe in religion
But they don't show that we believe in religion.
are. Too much on their father.
It may be that the peak time on their peak is too much.
Have struggled and finance-related
You have struggled too much. Father Name
Fathers who are under some debt or the other
You are suppressed because Virgo is the ninth house.
Reflects on the father that the father
There could be a lot of debt if Mercury Planet
Sitting in the second house in your horoscope
The father will be service-oriented but somewhere.
Nowhere will you find that the father's ah.
The nature of being service-oriented is
At the same time, people used to take money from them or to them.
People must have taken a lot of debt
To meet your needs.
There are two natures to see here. A
Practically, a spiritually. It
They are practical as well as spiritually
(a) Calculate the value of the product. Moral wisdom says that
As a service to other people
Work in. Those who are in front of you,
Don't take advantage of his effort. That is the moral
The intellect is that Virgo says that in front of you.
The person who is making efforts, you are his
Take advantage of the efforts. In some way from him.
His shad ribu which is greed which is the person in front of him
Greed arises from man's effort
In his mind that I made something out of his effort.
And if the Lord is Very Well Placed.
In the chart, mercury is the spiritual of the native.
It becomes natural that I am the person in front of me.
The one who is making efforts like we are on the way.
leaving. What would such a person be? All of us
Let's go by the way. Capricorn
I am also the Ascendant. You are too. Value
I didn't help you get along the way.
Happened. Someone's mercury would be very good, wouldn't it?
He saw someone on the way.
Will see and stop there to help him.
To do that the person in front of you a little bit
He's working hard. In his efforts
Let me help myself. So, these are the same people.
There are those whose mercury is very good
Inside the horoscope. Such a person in Shad Ripu
Doesn't get stuck in front of the person
Seeing the Efforts of His Helping Nature
It awakens inside the mind or intellect.
inside. They Naturally Inclination Towards
Animal. Inclination towards Animals
Lives too much. They Can Be Wanted.
Inside firms like The Animal Rescue Inn
Inside NGOs like these where animals
There should be a shelter house as a service there.
I work and what happens to it?
That it doesn't discriminate it. Which is
The truth stands with him. Meaning
There is no longer a dilemma of bias
Inside the mind because of the Ninth House Wisdom
is. Vargos when they come here
When the energy of the Virgo sign comes here
So the personality of such a person
That conflict is relieved. Such
People in front of the native will come to their
With malice and here it is those people's
Let's try to eliminate malice.
The Ninth House is education. Wisdom's.
Moral Ethics. But the sixth amount which is their
She came to the Ninth House to show the change.
is. That these people are concerned about their morals and ethics.
It can change according to the situation. Today
His Moral, Ethics, Education,
This is about spiritualism. Be Tomorrow
It may change according to the situation.
This change is not a change for them.
Works. If you have a moral
Ethics, have you thought this to be true?
It is absolutely determined that
This aspect is absolutely correct. So on that side
Stand with it till the end or that morality.
Stand together until the end. As long as you
Change the morality from time to time.
Until then, you will be caught in these shenanigans.
It will remain. Until then, you'll be thinking that
The person in front of me has something or the other for me.
Do. When the Virgo Sign Comes in the 10th
House It Means You're Not Sagittarius
Ascendant Sagittarius is your ascendant. Now Virgo
Further in their tenth house, it shows that such
The natives are very hardworking, who do a lot of work
are. But they don't get the fruits of that hard work.
Get or do that hard work with the people in front of you.
It is not appreciated by the Registrar of Companies. De Manly
Deeply Involved in Their Profession and in
There is a field of action. But No One Is Admiring
Their Efforts. This would have been the largest shed repo
I do so much for these people.
For the people in front of me, however,
Efforts are not seen. Routine
They are oriented. Towards your work
People are so strong that I don't know about this routine.
I have to do it. I have to get up in this routine
So I have to get up and work hard. Me
If you want to work, you have to do it. Manly Focus
It remains that I have the people in front of me.
I can be seen so that they can see my deeds.
Appreciate the area somewhere.
Somewhere. That is Shadri. He greets them here.
There is infatuation. I'm fascinated by my work.
If I do, you see. Greed that I
If I do, you should appreciate it.
Virgo's nature is on the field of work
She has come somewhere in her full shad ripu.
Nor would she go anywhere trying to trap a person.
is. Greed creates here that the native
In the Nature of
A thing starts to arise that a
The feeling of 'I' starts coming. Look
I did. Look, I'm done. This is what
The feeling is not the feeling of the ego which is the emotion of the I.
It is arising here if the native
It's happening inside if there's nowhere to go.
Look somewhere
All these things are different things. First of all, one thing.
Understand it. Ravan was arrogant that he was arrogant about me.
No one bigger. Vibhishana explained, Hanuman
Ji explained. All his ministers
Explained. But due to arrogance, he could not listen
And his own self-immolation of his own death.
The cause made itself. If a person in front of you
Telling you that look a little bit more
Arrogance is arising. I'm a
I am not a worm
That I am everything. The One Who Produced
It is very important to end it.
is. What is otherwise? Always Your Karma
You'll be stuck on the field. Trapped in Shad Ripu
You will stay. Professionally on your field of work
Upliftment is not available. Same work
You will continue to do it again and again in the routine. You guys
They start getting bored with their own routines.
How many years have I been doing the same thing?
I am constantly there because it becomes routine.
No, as long as it doesn't get out of that routine.
Meaning that unless he thinks that I
I am doing it to serve everyone. Me
You have to do it for everyone. Until then, these people themselves
Will you continue to treat me negatively or serve me?
No one is watching. No Appreciate
doing. Too much for his father.
We have to struggle for wealth and we
You can say too much about his father.
It must have been a depth or that finance related
You have taken a lot of debt, which has to be repaid.
His father has a lot of problems.
It has happened. They Fight Alone. Don't let them be bad for you.
In Time When Life's Circumstesses
If you treat them negatively, then don't them.
You have to stand alone. That's the shad ripu
Teaches humans when the tough time
Hits You Have to Stand Alone Like the Sixth
Houses like Virgo 6th House of Kaal Purush
It comes to me that the human being has his
You have to fight for yourself. So here's their
Virgo, the sixth sign on the field of karma, which
It's showing you your karma.
You have to fight for the territory yourself. Someone is your
No one will appreciate you.
Won't help. When it comes to that fear from Ripu
They come out that I have to do the service of the same
As then, here it is very much like a seeker.
Work in the form. Because who Sagittarius
The nature of the zodiac is that of spiritualism
is. He's a mentor. It belongs to the Guru. He
Morality. Then their morality was awakened.
I have to do it for everyone.
This is the Majorly Challenge for them
Inside Professional Life and Personal Life
Balancing. That such a person is very difficult
I go to him that I am also professionally
I am working and also my personal life.
I'm taking over. He would have been caught in the shad repo
That's why I should do it. When you understand this
If I have to do it, then there is no grudge
It will remain in the mind and life will be easy going.
For you. Now let's talk about the Virgo sign
When Comes in the 11th House. It Means You're
N Scorpio Ascent. For such a person
Social phobia is not the biggest. One is
It's not social.
A little afraid to talk because no
They are afraid that I will be insulted from there
Because the sixth sign is Virgo
It also shows humiliation. It is from its own income
There is not much satisfaction. Give
Need More Greed arises there
And anger also arises inside that
When their income is not increasing or their
If the sources of income were not increasing, then this
They begin to get irritated. Overthinking
It's too much. Same in anxiety
Turns and it irritates and frustrated
They begin to happen. Here the native finds
That's a lot for the person in front of me.
I do more service. But when my
When the time comes, no one does it for me.
This is because  the 11th house is socializing.
Of. Socialize when they come out
People seek help from them. When they
First of all, they need help.
No one stands up. Such a person never
Don't be satisfied with your helping nature
Find. That's why.
He helps. Help from the front.
If you don't get it, then it is not satisfied that
I am the only one and no one helps me.
doing. With the social circle of
Conflicts happen because when
If they need someone, there is no one to stand up for them.
It doesn't. These people are about the future.
Think too much. Now in the 11th  house
If it has come, then the nature of Virgo has come there.
It also increases. Shad replenishment in every way
The Scorpio works on the send.
That's why you'll find Scorpio Sendant
There are people who are overthinkers.
They are those who live in anxiety. work,
So much disorder of anger, greed,  ego
It starts growing in the mind. At their wishes
It seems to be that it will give those desires.
Completing
Moving towards anxiety and overthinking
They have more to say about the future.
Something to think about. And when it comes to me
You have to do service. It's some of your wealth.
Part When Using It as a Charity
Let's begin. Use as Wealth
Let's start doing. So,  of the 11th house, which
The causative element is causing them anxiety.
Making overthinker. He is for them.
Starts treating positively that
I have to do it. Look, God has given me.
I chose to do it for everyone. How many can I
I work for people. When it comes to a
If the feeling arises, then they will never be able to get it.
It won't. He is never in depression.
Will go. Ever
They will not have such a grudge in their minds.
Why am I doing it for everyone? 11th
This is the nature of Virgo.
It creates conflicts.
is. When you assume that you have someone
Property Lee has moved from fourth to eighth
Virgo, will you come to the property
If there is a litigation court case, you will come that
You have taken property in that property
Any obstacle means connected to the fourth house
What are the factors that make you trade negatively?
Let's begin. What will happen positively?
I have taken it when the time comes.
It will be fine. My job is just work.
do. So when we join this karma
We need to connect with the nature of Virgo.
If you try, that's the first thing you do.
Shows the spirit of service towards whom.
You have to socialize and do service. As much as
Socialize and serve. Wealth K
Resources will increase automatically.
When the Virgo Sign in the 12th House 12th
Virgo Inside the House of Libra Ascendant
It comes for the natives. So it shows that
For such a person, lust, anger, greed, attachment,
The ego is all based on their thought system.
Depends. Because which is of the 12th  house.
The causative element is  that there is an imagination somewhere.
Of. Charity's. And come in
The amount of money that is shad, the amount of loan that is
It shows that such a person is a part of the thought system.
Inside, they are trapped in lust, anger, greed.
Such a person is not confused that emotionally.
He wants to uplift himself or
Wants to uplift spiritually.
Because  the 12th house is also of spiritualism.
is.  The 12th house is of loss. Identity loss
Somewhere it is there and when
If Virgo comes, then the person of Shad Ripu
I can't lose my identity.
It's somewhere. That's why it means change.
I can't. He is one of these shenanigans.
He remains trapped. Work inside Shad Ripu,
Anger, greed, attachment, ego wants to serve
It is from the mind. But sometimes it doesn't serve.
Because you will find such a person, don't you?
So much more than so many people.
He is impressed that he
Confusing goes into a state that
Where he doesn't understand that I
Whom to obey or whom not to believe.
Spiritualism would have been the main basis of such a person
is. Why? Because the natives of Libra Ascendant
For them, the amount that comes in the third house
She comes to Sagittarius. That is, these efforts
So let's go towards spiritualism, but
The Virgo zodiac sign that is coming in the 12th  house
You keep them in a confusing state.
Do you want to go towards spirituality or your own
I want to fulfill my desires in life.
Because greed arises from there.
There are many such people through investment.
Make good sources of your financial wealth.
You can. Very good through meditation
These people can be healers. Medical Field
Such people are good at their field of work.
I can work. These people are such professions.
Where solving the
Things like conflicts are seen
Yes. Where it solves conflicts
You do it for other people. Their subconscious
The mind that is outside their communication
Doesn't let it go. Because the 12th house
Neither shows your subconscious mind and
The arrival of Virgo there which
It shows that you speak your mind.
Want but in a subconscious mind
The absence of Virgo is so much that he
We say that human beings are not ashamed of society.
Shame is avoidable. i.e.
He is afraid of society.
What will he think about? By the way, many
People get attracted to them
Because their personality is like this and
Sometimes it can be a different one.
Do nothing wrong with people. Wanting to
Nope. It is so unhelpful that it is a mistake.
It is done. Due to that, a debt of theirs
I don't want to do this.
Should've. Then a Confusion State Story
It happens for them that I don't want to do it.
I should have done it, but I did. That is, it
It is seen that for such a person
The most difficult thing is spiritual.
Moving towards growth because it is his emotions.
They always dominate him. 12th House
Shows your foreigners. It could be people.
Go out with a loan. It shows that this
Go out and serve in the job and your home.
Run. And it also shows that such a person
It can also be in services like hospitals
Where he chooses his job or profession
You can. They're very good in the
Investment. If it is on the investment side.
If you try to leave, then from there it is your
They generate wealth. But Joe Maine
Our focus is how we can get rid of them.
Finish? There is no service for them.
They have this feeling, but they have to do service.
They don't get time. Routine
It is not possible because the sixth zodiac sign is
Routine is Virgo in the 12th house
It has arrived. That is, being routine oriented
It becomes a little difficult to serve. So
When they started tying the service into routine
Somewhere there is a Virgo who
The causative element is of routine and  of the 12th house which
It is the nature of service that both of them are together.
And in such a situation, you will find that
Spiritual growth is very good.
They Can Be a Very Good Healer for Others
Peoples. You can become a very good healer.
So all the things we just talked about are Virgos.
What  fruit does it give within the 12 houses?
The main motive of this video was that
Every human being is caught in some kind of shad ripu
It has happened. What is the nature of Virgo?
This shows that the emotion in which it is
Humans remain trapped. Let us try
You need to be in a routine towards that feeling.
Go. We have no grudge against that feeling.
Stay. When we are defiant to that emotion
Then it is a human responsibility to go away.
Increases towards themselves and society. Whose
He is a member of the society doing a service.
Creating one's own status and one's own status
is. That's why you will find Kalpurush's horoscope
In the 6th house if the honor is of respect. Virgo
If the zodiac sign is of honor, then the 10th zodiac sign
Shows your status. Capricorn
The sign which is always in the triangle of insult
There is always a amount of honor in the triangle.
is. That's why you'll find that a person is a man.
He rises above humiliation in society.
The status always goes up. Next Again
And we'll talk in the session. You can watch this video.
You will definitely see it like this. D One and D Nine Charts
According to the Virgo, you will see that your zodiac sign
Where is it coming up in the chart? Then and Next
We'll talk in the session. Till then jai
shree Ram. Jai Shri Krishna.