Jai Shri Ram. Jai Shri Krishna. Welcome To
Our YouTube channel Refine Vedic
Astrology.
[Music]
Today's session is like this.
Understand that this is a precap session that
We are working on the Nakshatra series right now.
What fruits do all the planets give in each constellation?
are. So what is Saturn in every constellation?
They bear fruit in the coming time.
You will see the video. But before that, a
There's a small precap for that. This precap
It is inside that every constellation is there, isn't it?
Someone or the other has taken energy. But that
There is also something in the energy of the Nakshatra Lord.
You get to see the difference.
When Saturn goes inside any nakshatra
So the lord of that constellation
How does Saturn work with energy?
Try or the one who is the Constellation Lord
How does he work with Saturn?
Let's try. Today we are trying to understand that
Will try. Usually we see that Saturn
Whichever constellation you go to or you go to
Understand this way
For example, the baby stays inside the womb for 9  months
So, whatever the mother sees, whatever the mother's action,
According to that action, that child's
It goes on and on in memory.
Then the child comes out and does his work.
But the one that gets saved in memory
Isn't it within 9 months when she is pregnant?
When it's inside, everything is absorbed in it.
Inside the memory. So that's how when the planet is somebody.
Sits inside the constellation of that constellation.
The kind of acts that the Lord performs or who
His attributes will be his memory.
It takes the planet in. So when Saturn
If you sit inside any nakshatra, then that
Too much of the Lord of the Constellation.
Important role plays there
How will Saturn give fruit or how will Saturn give results?
They will act in a way. Usually we all know
Saturn is the karmic planet. Saturn Joe
He shows it to Dillet. Saturn who is
Let's show the discipline. Now everyone's
Is that discipline and what is that delay?
Will it be in the same situation? Is every human being karma?
Will it be the same in doing? This difference comes
When he sits in the constellation which
The constellation lord who had his own personality
Isn't it his tendency to do one thing?
According to him, Saturn works here.
Let's try. In the deeds of Saturn
You need a slightly different type of one.
Alignment is seen that every human being
Karma in what form it does. as
Suppose Saturn is in the constellation of Mars
is. So what do you see here now?
The focus of the native will be on a routine.
Will be. The native who is above his diet,
In a discipline on top of your exercise
The one who follows these things by staying
Will be. Somewhere inside his body
Like a frustration for your profession
You will get to see the thing. Like that of his
He's working very hard with his body.
But the karmic factor of Planet Mars
The outcome of his energies in the constellation
In Delay, he shows that
Therefore, this person is very frustrated
Frustrated becomes very frequent. this
What a native looks for inside his profession
Who gets? Politics is seen
is. Or when it will go inside your profession
Otherwise, it will be very calm. when
Until no one
Don't treat it that way.
The energy was not aligned. i.e
It's like a person is working. His work
Can't get that recognition. That one
Acting as an authority
But there is no human being of that authority
Where is he working in the profession?
is. So here's where to see Mars' angerness.
Get it. The Saturn that will give you a delay
And he was trying to keep in discipline
It's your energy. So here we understand
Saturn is in the constellation of Mars.
It can also be so effective to be. here
But Mars is the factor of your energy.
Taken. What Saturn is is a factor of discipline
are. Saturn is what it says that you have
Channelize your energy through discipline in any way.
It has to be applied on the work area. So this person
Routine becomes much more important
is. Therefore, this person is very good technical.
There is also a hand. Like how you do woodwork.
Happening,  construction work happening,
Being an architect, a very good lawyer.
Advocate, going into the police, inside the army
Where to go, where law and order or where
Anything can be done through a technical hand.
It is designed there when Saturn is Mars.
If you are in the constellation of K, then very good
Forms work. Because what is Saturn?
Want to? You work with your hands.
Mars is the energy inside you. at that time
Any type of technical or mechanical
When the work Saturn is in the constellation of Mars
A very good person can do it. We see
How hard work is some in the life of the native.
I don't get to see him delayed. purpose
He doesn't pay out quickly enough that he
Karma is performing. He's putting in the energy
In any work area. He was very quick.
So pay out. I don't keep working hard
is. The native works hard again and again. Again and again
He works hard. Then there comes a time when
His deeds that he has afforded. who
He had the heart to pursue his profession.
He was there to settle out.
He is able to get it aligned. Only then
Saturn satisfies it that it should come on.
Now this work of yours is completely
It has been done. This person always has one thing.
Care must be taken. You have to do any work
You should not keep it uncomplete. because
Saturn says when you start a task
It has been done. Saturn is in the constellation of
The Lord is Mars, he is the Energy.
Factor. The work that has been started
You have to finish with the same energy. So that
Inside the project or that work, you will always have to
One success is definitely seen. Then we
Let's see Saturn in the constellation of the Moon
They come. Now the moon is not in itself.
There is a planet living in very fast motion.
That is, it shows emotions. This is a
Nurturing shows nature. Saturn that is
Karma has been a factor in itself. So Saturn now
They have gone and sat in that constellation.
Abha Mandal is associated with a mother. now
Here the native is one from his karma field
He remains attached to it in the form of love. i.e
His motherhood becomes too much for him.
From the work area. That emotional too much.
Gets attached to your work area.
So what do you see for this native?
This native is mostly known for his karma area or
Thinking about your profession
Will be. And in many cases, it can also be seen
It may be that he is going to live alone.
On the work field, that is, there is a team.
Living and working in. There is one. A native
Handle your entire profession alone
It has been. Leave your entire karma field alone
Handles. So, these are the people
When Saturn comes in the constellation of the Moon
are. Generally, what we have read is that this is a poison.
There is yoga. That is, whether it is the Moon or Saturn
Combine with Saturn or Saturn. of the moon
Moon in the constellations. Saturn of Ah
In the constellations, that is, the constellations
Change is there. So this is a poison yoga
Originates in which the native has a lot of
You can say overthinking is too much.
It goes. His subconscious mind all the time.
Goes on. But here, the situation
It is very important to understand that the moon
It's the travel factor. If this person travels
Join the work in some way or this person
Join the profession of healing. Saturn
When with the moon or with the moon
If you are in the constellation, then the Born Healer is born.
It happens that it can heal anyone.
Why? Because it saw a lot of misery
is. It would have made its wishes unfulfilled.
I have seen it. That's why this person in front of him
He understands. So Saturn is here in Karma.
What do you do as? Inside it
Motherhood is too much for anyone to
I don't even send them empty-handed. I help everybody.
I'm going to do it. Lady Luck for this Native
Gives a lot of support to its profession
Inside because the moon itself
The feminine factor is called planets. Sleep here
But you see that if the native has his
I want to align my profession or my karma.
So he needs a lady luck.
Whether it's his mother's blessings
She added her spousal to her profession.
Go either way. Most of the natives
About your wealth, family and finances
I'm mostly a thinker.
And here we see that he himself
He wants to educate. Educate in the Sense
That he wants me to make my family happy
Keep. What is attachment to which is attachment?
Has it happened? He is connected to the moon and
We all know the nature of the moon.
Nurturing is nature. That nurturing nature
To accomplish this, the native also educates himself.
does. Hence many of those with the Saturn Moon.
People will find you in that healing profession.
They will go. If Mars is also together or Mars
What is the expectation on that Saturn?
Very good surgeons turn out to be this conjunction
From or Saturn when in the constellation of the Moon
Yes. What should this native do
Mostly about your profession
I think his positive outcome started to come then.
Will it be when it forgets the karma it has done
I will go to see that I have done what was my karma.
Hmm. Now the outcome that has to come will come on its own.
It will come.
The moon shows your liquidity.
is. So this person is not marketing, finance,
In professions like travel, commission work in
Very good results if added
Removes. Because here
Liquidity is a very moving position.
It is good. Moon is here, Saturn is here.
Aligns in the constellation of the Moon.
There is one more thing to see. No to the natives here.
Emotional setbacks  are 100%  worth watching.
Because Saturn is this constellation of the Moon
I am not able to satisfy myself.
Because the moon itself is the speed of
The Moon is the most Saturn and the Moon which is the most
There are planets moving in slow motion. So Joe
It's a thought system and a profession and a karma.
The native now lives in a very fast pace. i.e
Just thought I'd leave for 1 second.
Inside the human being,  the person came out within 1  second.
Goes anywhere. If you are sitting, you are just sitting.
He will sit in one place for hours. but
If you want to leave, then leave with a minute.
It will go. Responsibilities on the native
They are always there. Remember. When Saturn
Be in the constellation of the moon. Now if Saturn
If it is in the constellation of Rahu, then it is called
It's vampire yoga.
Or be with Saturn Rahu. Saturn of Rahu
If you come in the constellation, then the vampire is of yoga
Originates. It is written in the Puranas
This shows that the native never has his deeds.
Don't be too satisfying towards
finds. Within his profession
Illusions are seen. He has his own
Illusions are seen in karma.
Now Saturn has come inside the constellation which
It's an out of the box in itself. her
The Lord who is Rahu
Always an illusion about one's karma
The person does not know that it means to stay.
Actually, that's what I want to do. that
Never settle out your profession
Finds quickly.
You see a fear in his actions.
will get. That they do any work
The first 100 times I think I won't.
I do. Or what you'll see when you do it.
Any karma must have been thought after that
Sits down what I did. therefore
Think and think before you do.
Time should not be afraid in the mind. Saturn
Which tells you that you don't have the same success.
I can give it inside this profession. But you
I think of negativity within my profession.
It has to be closed. Rahu is big in itself.
Tries to do and Saturn who is karma
Factor. So as long as this person performs his karma
Don't think of making it big,  your profession
I don't think of creating jobs.
Saturn who is
They show the labour class. Rahu is who he is
An unorthodox
That's something that people don't usually think. So when
If Saturn is in the constellation of Rahu, then you will have a
One should think about employment origination.
Or the state I'm living in.
You will have to go to another state. Or I
I'm living in another country.
You have to go and set up your work. then
Saturn is here in the constellation of Rahu
According to the factor of Rahu
They start working. Generali such a person
Many changes in your profession
We get to see him. No doubt if it
The native Saturn who is in the constellation of Rahu
If the MAC company is working according to the plan, then the company
networking
And thinking of opening a business of his own
I can start my own business. where i
I am my own king. Because Rahu is who he is.
He is not going to be under anyone's control
is. And Saturn who is there asks for discipline.
are. As far as working in the discipline,
But when he is somewhere inside the job.
I don't find a controller anywhere.
In front of Rahu, there is Rahu
It is your nature to cause pain to Saturn here.
He begins to give that karmic field
It begins to withdraw. Hence the natives
It changes many professions.
Here.
One more thing, this person is not an artist.
There is also a personality that is artistic.
By Personality in Your Workplace
It can be made. But when Saturn is Rahu's,
If you are in the constellation, then always keep one thing in mind.
It should be kept. It gives you a conflict
Always inside the relationship. Saturn when Jupiter
If you are in the constellation of Jupiter, then Jupiter is your
You have the biggest planets.
Their gravity is very high
Which pulls out the negativity. Now Saturn
They have gone into their constellation. That is, this
You will see wisdom in the karma of the native.
That is, he will be a person who performs sattvic actions.
There are no two opinions. If not
If it has been, then somewhere in its field of work.
It's spoiling. Whatever action you do, think
He will do it with understanding. Somewhere in its karma
It's going to do a lot of good for society.
Will be. The native should promote in his profession.
Laker will be mostly upset. because
Where is Saturn showing Delay now? As a
The organism factor that is Planet Jupiter promotes
Let's do it. That is, you have to move from one situation to another.
They lead to the situation. By taking it up
Let's go. So the natural factor of Saturn
It's delayed. So if this person is inside the job
Or if it is inside the business, then the person there
Unable to get a promotion or to myself
Unable to upgrade until he
Don't educate yourself until you get to know about it.
Don't know the profession so well that
I'm probably going to promote myself now.
I'm ready to be here in my profession.
The native gets to see a lot of change
is. The native changes the profession too much.
It happens. Not just because of growth
Getting. Hence the change in your profession
We get to see it.
The native tries me in that profession.
I try to go where I want to teach.
Be it work, research work,  or education.
Whether it's work or I'm going to go somewhere far away.
Should I pursue my profession or should I pursue my profession?
I can educate them.
It's not very good that advisors give
If you want to give advice to anyone, then a lot
You can give good advice. It's always
Thinking that I should expand my work.
I can. I mean, I don't have to spread the work.
You have to make it bigger. In spreading and enlargement
There is a difference between the two. Saturn Rahu Wala
Spreads the work. Saturn Jupiter work
Increases. Spreading means from one state to another.
The state is then the third, then the fourth, that is spreading.
Increasing means employment within the same state.
Too much of that which I probably
It couldn't even be given in four states. at that time
In Saturn Jupiter, you will need to have your karmic realm
Thinking of expanding your profession
It's not about spreading.
The factor which is the planet which is Jupiter is the factor
It's about education, it's about finance, and so on.
Saturn tries here that you
Trying to get inside these two streams
Do that where you educate yourself too.
Do also understand finance and this thing
Saturn can align you by joining you.
With karma. Now when Saturn is in his own constellation.
If I were here, it would have been the first thing to do.
It doesn't come to liberate you.
are.
When Saturn is in its own constellation, that is,
This salvation is good in the zodiac signs of the triangle
is. That is, in his constellation like Pushya
Anuradha  is a triangle of 4 8 12. at that time
The natives liberate themselves by their own deeds
does. He fights at home.
To make a domestic piece. Because this
Not for the natives who stop the workforce.
It's just a house thing.
There are responsibilities. Of this person
In a lot of time, you can see that
Responsibility at a very young age.
They come up. Because that's what
Responsibility is liberated one day
They do. Lots of Transformation in the
You get to see the profession. That one place.
It keeps going to another place. In one place
Can't be located. Lots of places
You have to change your profession.
If it's not changing, it's somewhere.
He is not traveling in his profession.
So this person is somewhere in his house.
Trapped in responsibilities. yet
The most important role play for this native
It happens that it is the responsibilities of your home
I want to get out of it to settle my profession.
for. So you will find this native a place
It is mandatory to change the second place. we
Let's see that there is no one inside this person
There is capability. It is also suitable for any product
It can be made. Now here's why I say
I'm going to make it or make it a
The production unit can be set up in which
Different types of assets are created.
Whether it's related to home, whether it's you.
You go inside the mine, or you
You are exporting something from abroad.
Saturn is very good work here in it.
Do that when you produce something
Thinking about. Saturn here
Let's talk about liberation. Profession
Related Any Kind of Art, Dance,
Entertainment,
Staying inside a profession like Music Inn
The native can settle his profession.
Now you will wonder how it got in the way?
It has no role in this salvation triangle.
It doesn't play. Now it has here.
It's something to think about. By the way, this constellation
We should have talked inside. But still, you have to
You should understand.
Moon sign, Mars sign and Jupiter
The zodiac sign of Saturn arrives. and
When Saturn is sitting inside these zodiac signs,
Somewhere, Saturn is somewhere.
Going towards the zodiac sign. Saturn that is going
Those who are traveling are ahead of themselves.
Zodiac sign Leo, Arius and Sagittarius
are. That is, what is your karma?
Moving towards the situation. Therefore, these people
If you want to go to the situation
Aligns your life in advance.
Along with education, music, art, healing, so it is.
The native gives very good results
In your profession. Generali Travel Lots
There is more involvement inside the profession.
And this is mostly what businesses prefer
Rather Job than Job. Because when Saturn is your
There is no employment in the constellation.
He is the Creator. This is any profession
They will be there to provide employment.
It must be that many people
They are giving employment. Natives from a very young age
There is a person who takes responsibility. therefore
The native is also very daring. Yes,
If Saturn is not in conjunction with the Sun, then your
In this nakshatra inside the chart, when your
In the constellation, the native should try
That's what I'm doing my responsibilities
I want to be detached from him. and with
In everything inside the life of this person
You'll see the delay. In Marriage
Delay,  delay in progeny,  delay in profession,
Delay in Professional Growth, in Every Way
Delay will give. Why? Because Saturn is its own when
They go into the constellation, that is, it will give you
They want to liberate through the delay. self
You can understand this directly. But you will get
Sure. We can't even deny that.
When Saturn is in the constellation of Mercury
What do you see in general? Don't do it in your home.
They are those who live outside. of Mercury
It's the nature of most Mercury speeds too much.
Inside the planetary position, which remains sharp.
So don't sit in one place,  one place to another.
Going to places, going there, doing commission work,
Through communication, it is your profession
Let's try to settle out. give
General focus on the smart work rather than den.
Hard work. Now here is Saturn, who is himself.
Factors of hard work, he is his constellation
I moved in. The Inspiration for Smart Work
does, i.e. Mercury. So, the natives are confused.
Do I live in a state that I do this job?
I have to do it,  I have to do it, can I?
Should I move to smart work? Am I hard?
Should I go to work? Saturn Mercury Person
Meaning, whether Saturn is Mercury or Saturn Mercury
It is in the constellation. In general, in their life.
Transformation to see a lot
They meet. Just because it's a
They can't think of things. It's one thing
Even when you sit to think, you think about it.
They start thinking about something else. Their
Which hobbies are very different to you.
Change will be seen. What else to look for
Me? Majorly, that will be their hobbies, isn't it?
The big ones will be such that there is no
Try that in my hobbies
Sit very comfortably and peacefully and watch those hobbies.
I can play. Generali here
Travels too much inside a relationship.
is. Where his domestic status is somewhere
There is no hurt anywhere. Now for Mercury
There are constellations, you understand that in this way too.
Cancer falls under this zodiac sign,
Scorpio and
. So the native stays from his home and runs a profession
Or the native goes far away from home.
He settles out his profession.
But when Saturn is in this nakshatra, this person
He is the one who speaks the truth. Your research
Work through your analytical mind.
He settles out his profession.
Because Saturn is in the constellation of Mercury
Research analytical power is very good for you.
give. You can stay in any discipline
If you do research, then Saturn will be very here.
You will give good results. What happens sometimes
Right? The native does not use the word 'Harsh'.
Which shows his truth-telling. who
The person will not always speak the truth.
Somewhere he uses the word "horse". And this
The natives do their profession very well.
It is known or we can say this.
The native does not have all kinds of remedies
That's how I want to make my profession or
Using Remedies Inside Your Life
is. Think of it this way.
When Saturn is in the constellation of Mercury, the native
There is a Bybone Healer. I know that
How do I do remedies? a lot
Good research works and no doubt
Such a person is not even a spiritual person who understands spirituality
It happens and travels through spirituality
There is also a doer. oh great
Meditation yoga means a motivation speaker
It doesn't happen that someone falls.
Even a person who has a different personality
You can pick up the fallen one and make him a king.
are. That's a quality when Saturn Mercury
They are in the constellation of . Now Saturn and Ketu
Are you in the constellation of
So that's a different yoga in itself
Because two such planets meet in a way
They have gone somewhere that separates us.
Let's try to give. So the person who
The state of mind is like this
That even while working in the society, he
Ditch tries to stay.
That is, you will find the intent power of the native
The intuition power that there is is a lot of
It is stronger. That is, Saturn and Ketu
One is that person. If it is someone
If you make a prayer, it will come to fruition. If it is any
If you give it to you, it will also be fruitful.
There will be. No one can stop him. General it
In the starting phase of life, you have to
Tries to give blockages.
Inside the profession, it means quickly stable.
It is not possible. Because the native has nowhere to go.
Somewhere in the profession or in its field of work
He can't feel his mind on the field of work.
is. But the Letter of the Life is for you to see.
will get. Stability in the profession here
It starts coming somewhere.
Financial a very important role.
Plays inside the profession of this person
And the work of the voice means a lot of speech.
Isn't it normal when Saturn is in the constellation of Ketu?
If they are in the Aries sign, that is.
Saturn is inside the debilitation. at that time
Your voice is very important here.
Role plays. Your communication skills
Too much role-play is what you do.
Setting the profession of your life in a way
will find. That is, you don't have to understand when
If you are talking to someone, then your point
It should be reflected in doing that I am a yogi somewhere.
I'm talking to a human. That is, one of these
Yogi is a human being. This is what a yogi horoscope is all about.
This yoga is seen when Saturn and Ketu
You are in the constellation. That is, while doing every task
He's also going to be detached from it. Dee R. Byborne
Healers resolve all kinds of conflicts.
There are doers. General this person is not
Those who do their profession also do commissions.
Do it as or what they do
Professions will be different. They are divided
It is a profession. If this native is somewhere
I don't try to do a profession somewhere.
Isn't he able to get results there?
Which is what he is doing in different professions.
You get the results. We'll see here.
It may be that this person is one such person.
Undiagnosed disease because Saturn is also
In itself, the suffering factor is called the planet.
That torments. And Ketu is also a
Shows undiagnosed disease. Body K
Inside a part of an undiagnosed disease
There is no way to break it.
Yes. So if that's the situation here, then here.
But you should see that when Saturn
What is inside the constellation are you social?
Well-use or towards society, which is one of yours
Is it the perspective of a yogi who gives it?
Equal? The yogi never takes it. yogi
Always gives. So this is one of the natives.
The mood and mindset should be such that
I'm just here to give. When I
If I think of taking it, I will somewhere in my
I will harm my body. in it
One has to struggle in the profession here
Inside. What is Ketu is not what it means?
The person who is Saturn planet is towards profession
Ketu tries to take him away
Spiritualism to Spirituality
Trys. So this is a struggle.
Whether I choose my profession or my
Should I choose the piece in life or I should choose the piece in life?
Give a little space to one of your spirituals. No
Doubt this person works too hard.
It is going to happen and it can be possible that like this.
The native may have someone inside the legs or feet.
The problem can be seen. When Saturn
In the constellation of Venus, that is, it is a different one.
The theory comes out because Saturn is a
You must have heard the saying that a guru asked
Tell me about Gurudev in Saturn and Venus.
What's the difference? So Gurudev said, "Shani ji."
It feels good when you go. the planet Venus
It feels good when you come. i.e
The two can't stay in one place. Remember this
Keep it. Either you enjoy your profession
Or you can do luxury life.
You can enjoy it. When Saturn and Venus
If you go into the constellation, then this thing is for sure
That through your profession, yours
Luxury life will be created. And who is also your partner
Whatever happens, it will be very work oriented.
It will be a personality. Because your charts
Saturn inside the constellation that
Venus shows up and Venus in itself
Indulgence and luxury and everyone knows about a partner.
Factor. But this is not the person here.
Loyalty will be the one to know. This is the person we
You can say that it will be loyal. any
The native goes to every extent to maintain the relationship
It can be done. Down your ego in it too.
Maybe. When Saturn is inside this constellation.
Saturn does a lot of matter when this
In the constellation how your speech is
Working. If Saturn is in this nakshatra
If you come, Aerys, Leo or your sagittarius.
It will be in the sign. Where your speech and
The knowledge that you have matters a lot that
Don't show ego on your knowledge.
Somewhere on top of your knowledge, like this.
Don't let others down, from where you want to go.
There are people who are below you, they have nowhere to go.
I had to see a little bit of trouble somewhere. here
But there is a lot of linkage to the native's speech.
more. And Saturn shows up in this constellation
When this person is going to enjoy
If you think about it, the work will be stuck in the middle. When it comes to
If you think of working, then enjoy in the middle
It will be on hold. That is, big for this person
It becomes difficult to keep your profession
Enjoy your luxury life. If it is
Keeps more stability towards the profession
If you have the luxury of your life, then from there it is a luxury.
Lives behind the Lives. But it
The person runs after as much luxury as there
This spoils its profession. So Saturn
When it is in the constellation of Venus, it is always the case
Remember. Not for you to recycle one
You should have a habit in your mind that I
I can recycle anything. I don't know
I can make a bad thing very well.
On your profession or your field of work
You should see that you can even look at broken things.
You can make it very good. Then he wants
A broken relationship is broken. He may be broken.
Futa is a profession. Whether it's a profession
Lift up from the down. Even if it is broken.
Futa should be someone's moral and ethic. You can also use him.
Motivate. It's a must when Venus
It occurs in the constellation of . It becomes necessary
is. You have to stay in discipline here.
More important. You've got to follow you.
Routine. Remember that. Saturn when the Sun
If you are in the constellation of K, it shows the native.
Inside your ambition a little bit
Have to see. That is, Saturn is now in that constellation.
I moved in. The deeds that this native will do ambition
For Fame Recognition Society Status
will. And this is where this person sees the delay
You will find that even after working very hard, every
Even though I have art in me,
I can't get that fame either. therefore
This person has to keep giving time to his art.
When Saturn is here, you are very much inside that art.
When you get proficient, then you have a
Recognition gets a high level of fame
What happens? That is, Saturn is the factor of delay.
If you have gone, then why are you delaying?
Show that as long as you value that thing
They don't want to understand when they meet you.
You don't have to be arrogant, so they delay you.
Show. Hence the work on top of your art.
Do your own thing that is very good in you.
It's Powers. Like the power of healing. u
Have a Power of Art. Every type of art
Art is what you know. A lot of education
They know very well. That is, you are your
Even while doing the field of karma, as long as you
Delay will be seen as long as you get its value.
Eventually, you don't understand and now you
Stop thinking. That is, it happens to me.
I need one thing. According to a time my age
It's growing, but I can't find that thing.
It has been. At an age, I would have understood
That's not necessarily what I was asking for.
is. Then you start getting that thing
Because Right Now Your Thought System is Complete
It has changed that I actually have.
I don't need this thing. You come to me.
Even if it comes, it doesn't matter to me.
Or I won't have any ego. Hence Saturn
When you are in the constellation of the Sun, you are trying
Authority recognition should be famous in
Instead of running after things, you can
Keep working on the work area. You are your
How to build a relationship with your father
It becomes more urgent. Fr. K
There will be issues in health. Father to
Health-related issues will be seen. or
Then the father settled into a very good profession.
Will be out. Where they have authority
There will be. A lot of people work under him.
There will be those. Which is also the first child.
When Saturn is first in the constellation of the Sun
If she has a child, she would have settled down immediately.
It's somewhere or that from one state.
It goes to another state. That is, which
The first child has a little bit of a separation
It goes inside the relationship of the native. So this
What was there is a precap that we have understood that
When the linkage with the Saturn Nakshatra Lord
It happens. The Lord of each constellation has his own
It is carrying energy. It would have been necessary
That you are the causative element of that Nakshatra Lord
How are you connecting it to Saturn? the planet mar
If Saturn is making you do hard work, then
Venus is making Saturn work for comfort.
is. Mercury if from there the through work of mind.
If the sun is making the native here, then the person is getting it done
He is getting the work done inside the society. the moon
If Saturn is working through travel.
So here, Rahu is making a pretentious gesture to the native.
Getting the job done. Through Ketu Spirituality
Saturn is getting the job done. That is, the one who
Saturn is the lord of the constellation, isn't it?
Trying to work. Because he
The aura of the constellation is inside Saturn.
It is absorbed. So that was a small topic
Which we have tried to understand. effort
You also do research it in your own way.
May. Mostly this topic is from any book.
Won't get in.
The more research I've done on this,
After researching the topic, the more you understand.
I came to know that the constellation which is the Lord,
He does a very fruitful job. Then when you
They join the Lord of that constellation.
By the Factor Element of the Planet. The Matter
Understand. This is a subject of a lot of research.
You should also do research on it yourself. Generally
We continue to do it. Someone else next.
We'll talk about the session in the next video. then
Thanks for that. jai Shree Ram Jai Shree Krishna.